[
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Ice Cold in Alex'?",
                "answer": "Christopher Landon"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'Ice Cold in Alex'?",
                "answer": "J. Lee Thompson"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'Mackenna's Gold'?",
                "answer": "J. Lee Thompson"
            },
            {
                "question": "What genre is the movie 'Mackenna's Gold'?",
                "answer": "Western"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie shares a genre with 'Django Unchained' and was directed by the same person who directed 'Ice Cold in Alex'?",
                "answer": "'Mackenna's Gold' was directed by J. Lee Thompson and shares the Western genre with 'Django Unchained'."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was written by Christopher Landon, directed by J. Lee Thompson, and shares a genre with 'Django Unchained'?",
            "answer": "'Ice Cold in Alex' was written by Christopher Landon, directed by J. Lee Thompson, and shares the Western genre with 'Django Unchained'. However, it is important to note that 'Django Unchained' is not a Western directed by J. Lee Thompson."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'Street Smart'?",
                "answer": "Jerry Schatzberg"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'Misunderstood'?",
                "answer": "Jerry Schatzberg"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Misunderstood'?",
                "answer": "Florence Montgomery"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was directed by Jerry Schatzberg and written by Florence Montgomery?",
            "answer": "The movie 'Misunderstood' was directed by Jerry Schatzberg and written by Florence Montgomery."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Batman Forever'?",
                "answer": "Nicole Kidman"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'The Golden Compass'?",
                "answer": "Nicole Kidman"
            },
            {
                "question": "What are the tags for the movie 'The Golden Compass'?",
                "answer": "nicole kidman"
            },
            {
                "question": "What are the tags for the actor 'Nicole Kidman'?",
                "answer": "The Interpreter"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'The Interpreter' released?",
                "answer": "2005"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actor starred in the movie 'Batman Forever' and also has a movie released in 2005 with the tag 'nicole kidman'?",
            "answer": "Nicole Kidman"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'The Battle of China'?",
                "answer": "Frank Capra"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'The Bitter Tea of General Yen'?",
                "answer": "Frank Capra"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'The Bitter Tea of General Yen'?",
                "answer": "Grace Zaring Stone"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Escape'?",
                "answer": "Grace Zaring Stone"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie starred actors from the movie 'Escape'?",
                "answer": "Norma Shearer"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actor starred in a movie directed by the person who also directed 'The Battle of China' and written by the person who wrote 'The Bitter Tea of General Yen' and 'Escape'?",
            "answer": "Norma Shearer"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Let's Go to Prison'?",
                "answer": "Dax Shepard"
            },
            {
                "question": "In which movie did Dax Shepard star along with Kristin Chenoweth?",
                "answer": "Hit and Run"
            },
            {
                "question": "What are some movies or tags associated with Dax Shepard?",
                "answer": "Idiocracy, Hit and Run"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie starred Dax Shepard and was also tagged with his name, and had Kristin Chenoweth as a co-star?",
            "answer": "Hit and Run"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'The Grand Seduction'?",
                "answer": "Michael Dowse"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was directed by Michael Dowse that was released in 2011?",
                "answer": "Take Me Home Tonight"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was 'The Well-Digger's Daughter' released?",
                "answer": "2011"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie starred Daniel Auteuil and was released in the same year as 'Take Me Home Tonight'?",
                "answer": "The Well-Digger's Daughter"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actor starred in a movie directed by Michael Dowse and also in a movie released in the same year as 'Take Me Home Tonight', which was written by the same person who wrote 'The Grand Seduction'?",
            "answer": "Daniel Auteuil"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "What is one of Chris Owen's character names?",
                "answer": "Angus"
            },
            {
                "question": "What genre is the movie 'Angus' associated with?",
                "answer": "Drama"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie falls under the genre of 'Doing Time on Maple Drive' and 'Drama'?",
                "answer": "Doing Time on Maple Drive"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'Doing Time on Maple Drive' that is associated with Chris Owen's character Angus?",
                "answer": "Ken Olin"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie, directed by Ken Olin and associated with Chris Owen's character named Angus, falls under the genres of Drama and 'Doing Time on Maple Drive'?",
            "answer": "Doing Time on Maple Drive"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie Love, Rosie?",
                "answer": "Sam Claflin"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie Love, Rosie?",
                "answer": "Christian Ditter"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was directed by Christian Ditter and starred Sam Claflin?",
            "answer": "Love, Rosie"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Species'?",
                "answer": "Ben Kingsley"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Harem'?",
                "answer": "Ben Kingsley"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'Harem' released?",
                "answer": "1985"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'Girls Just Want to Have Fun' released?",
                "answer": "1985"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'Girls Just Want to Have Fun' and in what year was it released?",
                "answer": "Alan Metter, 1985"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie starring Ben Kingsley was released in the same year as 'Girls Just Want to Have Fun' and who directed it?",
            "answer": "The movie 'Harem' starring Ben Kingsley was released in the same year as 'Girls Just Want to Have Fun' and it was directed by Alan Metter."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Swimming with Sharks'?",
                "answer": "George Huang"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'Trojan War'?",
                "answer": "George Huang"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie did Marley Shelton star in?",
                "answer": "Trojan War"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie did David Boreanaz star in?",
                "answer": "Valentine"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was written by the person who directed 'Trojan War' and in which that person also stars Marley Shelton, and further, David Boreanaz stars in a movie in which Marley Shelton also stars?",
            "answer": "'Swimming with Sharks' was written by George Huang, who directed 'Trojan War' where Marley Shelton stars. Also, David Boreanaz stars in the movie 'Valentine' where Marley Shelton also acts."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie Miranda?",
                "answer": "Googie Withers"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie Miranda?",
                "answer": "Denis Waldock"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was starred by Googie Withers and written by Denis Waldock?",
            "answer": "Miranda"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'The Girl He Left Behind'?",
                "answer": "Tab Hunter"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Polyester'?",
                "answer": "Tab Hunter"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Polyester'?",
                "answer": "John Waters"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Female Trouble'?",
                "answer": "John Waters"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie starred both David Lochary and was written by John Waters?",
                "answer": "Female Trouble"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actor starred in 'The Girl He Left Behind' and also appeared in a movie written by the same person who wrote 'Female Trouble'?",
            "answer": "Tab Hunter"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Charity Rahmer star in Cheerleader Massacre?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Tamie Sheffield star in Cheerleader Massacre?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actors starred in Cheerleader Massacre, featuring both Charity Rahmer and Tamie Sheffield?",
            "answer": "Charity Rahmer and Tamie Sheffield both starred in Cheerleader Massacre."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Was Ryosuke Hashiguchi written by Reiko Kataoka?",
                "answer": "No."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was starred by Reiko Kataoka?",
                "answer": "Hush!"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was written by Ryosuke Hashiguchi and starred Reiko Kataoka?",
            "answer": "Hush!"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in Subject Two?",
                "answer": "Dean Stapleton"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actor starred in Subject Two and what is the name of that movie?",
            "answer": "Dean Stapleton starred in the movie labeled as Subject Two."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Ringmaster'?",
                "answer": "Jerry Springer"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'The Defender'?",
                "answer": "Jerry Springer"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Command Performance'?",
                "answer": "Dolph Lundgren"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie, starred by Dolph Lundgren and in the language of Russian, also has Jerry Springer in its cast who has previously starred in a movie called 'The Defender'?",
            "answer": "Command Performance"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Factotum'?",
                "answer": "Charles Bukowski"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Tales of Ordinary Madness'?",
                "answer": "Charles Bukowski"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Bye Bye Monkey'?",
                "answer": "Marco Ferreri"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie did Geraldine Fitzgerald star in?",
                "answer": "Bye Bye Monkey"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actor starred in a movie written by the same person who wrote 'Tales of Ordinary Madness' and 'Bye Bye Monkey'?",
            "answer": "Geraldine Fitzgerald starred in 'Bye Bye Monkey' which was written by Marco Ferreri, who also wrote 'Tales of Ordinary Madness'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Joel Tobeck star in the movie Accidents Happen?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Harry Cook star in the movie Accidents Happen?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did both Joel Tobeck and Harry Cook star in the movie Accidents Happen?",
            "answer": "Yes, Joel Tobeck and Harry Cook both starred in the movie Accidents Happen."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "What movie has the tags 'kimiyoshi yasuda'?",
                "answer": "Zatoichi and the Fugitives"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was Zatoichi and the Fugitives released?",
                "answer": "1968"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was The Horse in the Gray Flannel Suit released?",
                "answer": "1968"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the genre of The Horse in the Gray Flannel Suit?",
                "answer": "Family"
            },
            {
                "question": "What genre of movie has 'Andy Hardy Meets Debutante'?",
                "answer": "Family"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "What family-genre movie was released in 1968, and was tagged by kimiyoshi yasuda and shares the same genre as Andy Hardy Meets Debutante?",
            "answer": "The Horse in the Gray Flannel Suit"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Was Howard McCain involved in writing the movie Outlander?",
                "answer": "Yes, Howard McCain was a writer for the movie Outlander."
            },
            {
                "question": "What genre does the movie Outlander have?",
                "answer": "The movie Outlander has the genre 'space'."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie shares the genre 'space' with Titan A.E.?",
                "answer": "The movie Outlander shares the genre 'space' with Titan A.E."
            },
            {
                "question": "In which movie did John Leguizamo appear?",
                "answer": "John Leguizamo starred in the movie Titan A.E."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie did John Leguizamo star in, that also features an actor from Vanishing on 7th Street?",
                "answer": "John Leguizamo starred in the movie Titan A.E., and an actor from Vanishing on 7th Street is also in that movie."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Was Howard McCain involved in writing a space-genre movie that starred John Leguizamo, who also appeared in a movie with an actor from Vanishing on 7th Street?",
            "answer": "Yes, Howard McCain was a writer for the space-genre movie Outlander, and John Leguizamo starred in that movie. Additionally, John Leguizamo appeared in the movie Titan A.E., which features an actor from Vanishing on 7th Street."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "What tags does the movie Brewster McCloud have?",
                "answer": "The movie Brewster McCloud has the tag 'bd-r'."
            },
            {
                "question": "What tags does the movie with the tag 'bd-r' have?",
                "answer": "The movie with the tag 'bd-r' has the tag 'Rocco and His Brothers'."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie Rocco and His Brothers released?",
                "answer": "The movie Rocco and His Brothers was released in the year 1960."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie with the release year 1960 released?",
                "answer": "The movie with the release year 1960 was released in the year 1960."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie starred actors in the movie Visit to a Small Planet that was released in 1960?",
                "answer": "The movie Visit to a Small Planet, which was released in 1960, starred the actor Jerry Lewis."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actor starred in a movie that was released in the same year as Rocco and His Brothers and has the tag 'bd-r' associated with Brewster McCloud?",
            "answer": "The actor Jerry Lewis starred in the movie Visit to a Small Planet, which was released in the same year as Rocco and His Brothers (1960) and has the tag 'bd-r' associated with Brewster McCloud."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Does the movie 'The Inbetweeners Movie' have the tag 'holiday'?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'The Inbetweeners Movie'?",
                "answer": "Ben Palmer."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Ben Palmer direct a movie about a holiday?",
            "answer": "Yes, 'The Inbetweeners Movie' is a movie about a holiday directed by Ben Palmer."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Ruby Cairo'?",
                "answer": "Liam Neeson"
            },
            {
                "question": "In which movie did Liam Neeson star?",
                "answer": "Coral Reef Adventure"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Coral Reef Adventure'?",
                "answer": "Howard Hall"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie connects Ruby Cairo, Liam Neeson, Coral Reef Adventure, and Howard Hall?",
            "answer": "Liam Neeson starred in Ruby Cairo and Coral Reef Adventure, and Howard Hall starred in Coral Reef Adventure. So, Coral Reef Adventure is the movie that connects all of them."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'The Doctor'?",
                "answer": "Randa Haines"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'Wrestling Ernest Hemingway'?",
                "answer": "Randa Haines"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie did Richard Harris star in?",
                "answer": "Wrestling Ernest Hemingway"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie did Richard Harris star in along with being a part of the national film registry?",
                "answer": "Unforgiven"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was directed by Randa Haines and starred Richard Harris, who also starred in a movie that is part of the national film registry?",
            "answer": "Wrestling Ernest Hemingway and Unforgiven"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'What's Love Got to Do with It'?",
                "answer": "Brian Gibson"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie has the tag 'angela bassett'?",
                "answer": "What's Love Got to Do with It"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie has the tag 'Strange Days' and who directed it?",
                "answer": "Strange Days, directed by Kathryn Bigelow"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'The Weight of Water' and which movie has the tag 'angela bassett'?",
                "answer": "Kathryn Bigelow, and the movie with the tag 'angela bassett' is What's Love Got to Do with It"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Who directed the movie 'The Weight of Water' and which movie has the tag 'angela bassett' in its credits?",
            "answer": "Kathryn Bigelow, and the movie with the tag 'angela bassett' in its credits is What's Love Got to Do with It."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'The Rare Breed'?",
                "answer": "Brian Keith"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'With Six You Get Eggroll'?",
                "answer": "Brian Keith"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'With Six You Get Eggroll' along with Barbara Hershey?",
                "answer": "Barbara Hershey"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Splitting Heirs' along with Eric Idle?",
                "answer": "Barbara Hershey"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actors Brian Keith, Barbara Hershey, Eric Idle are all connected by starring in movies together and who starred in which movie?",
            "answer": "Brian Keith starred in 'The Rare Breed' and 'With Six You Get Eggroll' with Barbara Hershey. Barbara Hershey starred in 'With Six You Get Eggroll' and 'Splitting Heirs' with Eric Idle."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Defiance'?",
                "answer": "Nechama Tec"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie did Jamie Bell star in?",
                "answer": "Defiance"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie has the tag 'jamie bell'?",
                "answer": "Retreat"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie has the tag 'Snowpiercer' and was starred by Jamie Bell?",
                "answer": "Snowpiercer"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was written by Nechama Tec and starred Jamie Bell, who has also been tagged in the movies 'Retreat' and 'Snowpiercer'?",
            "answer": "The movie is 'Defiance'. Jamie Bell was tagged in the movies 'Retreat' and 'Snowpiercer' and he starred in the movie 'Defiance', which was written by Nechama Tec."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie Dreamchild?",
                "answer": "Ian Holm"
            },
            {
                "question": "In which movie did Ian Holm star?",
                "answer": "The Emperor's New Clothes"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie The Emperor's New Clothes?",
                "answer": "Tim McInnerny"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actor starred in both Dreamchild and The Emperor's New Clothes, along with Tim McInnerny?",
            "answer": "Ian Holm and Tim McInnerny"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Leo Gregory star in the movie Stoned?",
                "answer": "Yes, he did."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie Stoned?",
                "answer": "Neal Purvis"
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Neal Purvis write the movie The World Is Not Enough?",
                "answer": "Yes, he did."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie The World Is Not Enough released?",
                "answer": "It was released in the year 1999."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie No One Writes to the Colonel released, and who wrote the movie Stoned?",
                "answer": "The movie No One Writes to the Colonel was released in the year 1999, and Neal Purvis wrote the movie Stoned.\n\nAnswer:"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "In what year was the movie No One Writes to the Colonel released, and who wrote the movie Stoned, which was starred by Leo Gregory?",
            "answer": "The movie No One Writes to the Colonel was released in the year 1999, and Neal Purvis wrote the movie Stoned, which was starred by Leo Gregory."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Whispers in the Dark'?",
                "answer": "Anthony LaPaglia"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Commandments'?",
                "answer": "Anthony LaPaglia, Aidan Quinn"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Return to Sender'?",
                "answer": "Aidan Quinn"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Return to Sender'?",
                "answer": "Neal Purvis"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie connects Anthony LaPaglia, Aidan Quinn, and Neal Purvis through the relations 'starred_actors' and 'written_by'?",
            "answer": "'Return to Sender' is connected to 'Anthony LaPaglia' and 'Aidan Quinn' through the 'starred_actors' relation, and it's connected to 'Neal Purvis' through the 'written_by' relation."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Marie Theisen star in The Other Side of Sunday?",
                "answer": "Yes, she did."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was The Other Side of Sunday released?",
                "answer": "The Other Side of Sunday was released in the year 1996."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was Beyond Hypothermia released?",
                "answer": "Beyond Hypothermia was released in the year 1996."
            },
            {
                "question": "What are the tags for Beyond Hypothermia?",
                "answer": "The tags for Beyond Hypothermia are 'hong kong'."
            },
            {
                "question": "What movies are tagged with 'hong kong'?",
                "answer": "The God of Cookery is tagged with 'hong kong'."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Marie Theisen star in a movie released in 1996 that has the tags 'hong kong'?",
            "answer": "No, she did not. Marie Theisen starred in The Other Side of Sunday, which was released in 1996, but that movie does not have the tags 'hong kong'. The only movie from 1996 with the tags 'hong kong' is Beyond Hypothermia, and Marie Theisen did not star in that movie."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Does E.T. have the tag 'Indiana Jones and the Kingdom of the Crystal Skull'?",
                "answer": "No, E.T. does not have the tag 'Indiana Jones and the Kingdom of the Crystal Skull'."
            },
            {
                "question": "In which movie did Cate Blanchett star?",
                "answer": "Cate Blanchett starred in 'Indiana Jones and the Kingdom of the Crystal Skull'."
            },
            {
                "question": "In which movie did Jay Baruchel star?",
                "answer": "Jay Baruchel starred in 'How to Train Your Dragon'."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie did Cate Blanchett and Jay Baruchel both star in, and is also tagged as 'Indiana Jones and the Kingdom of the Crystal Skull' or 'How to Train Your Dragon'?",
            "answer": "Cate Blanchett and Jay Baruchel both starred in 'How to Train Your Dragon', but it is not tagged as 'Indiana Jones and the Kingdom of the Crystal Skull'. It is, however, tagged as 'How to Train Your Dragon'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Chaos'?",
                "answer": "Coline Serreau"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'Chaos'?",
                "answer": "Hideo Nakata"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'Chatroom'?",
                "answer": "Hideo Nakata"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Chatroom'?",
                "answer": "Enda Walsh"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Disco Pigs'?",
                "answer": "Enda Walsh"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was directed by Hideo Nakata and written by Enda Walsh?",
            "answer": "The movie 'Chatroom' was directed by Hideo Nakata and written by Enda Walsh."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie Pompeii?",
                "answer": "Emily Browning"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie Magic Magic?",
                "answer": "Emily Browning and Catalina Sandino Moreno"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie Maria Full of Grace?",
                "answer": "Catalina Sandino Moreno"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie Maria Full of Grace released?",
                "answer": "2004"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actor starred in the movies Pompeii, Magic Magic, and Maria Full of Grace, and in which year was the movie Maria Full of Grace released?",
            "answer": "Emily Browning starred in the movies Pompeii, Magic Magic, and Maria Full of Grace, and Maria Full of Grace was released in the year 2004."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote 'The Testament of Dr. Mabuse'?",
                "answer": "Norbert Jacques"
            },
            {
                "question": "What genre is 'The Testament of Dr. Mabuse'?",
                "answer": "Crime"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie is of the genre 'Crime'?",
                "answer": "The Testament of Dr. Mabuse"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which genre does 'He Ran All the Way' belong to?",
                "answer": "Drama"
            },
            {
                "question": "What genre does 'Drama' include?",
                "answer": "He Ran All the Way"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie is of the genre 'Drama' and was written by the same person who wrote 'The Testament of Dr. Mabuse'?",
                "answer": "There is no movie that was written by Norbert Jacques and is of the genre 'Drama' in this knowledge graph."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie is connected to 'Doing Time on Maple Drive' through the genres Crime, Drama and the writer Norbert Jacques?",
            "answer": "There is no direct connection between 'Doing Time on Maple Drive' and the other entities given in the knowledge graph through the mentioned relations."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Get Real'?",
                "answer": "Patrick Wilde"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which person wrote the movie 'Get Real' and what is the name of that movie?",
            "answer": "Patrick Wilde wrote the movie 'Get Real'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Martha Nussbaum star in the movie Examined Life?",
                "answer": "Yes, Martha Nussbaum starred in the movie Examined Life."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie Examined Life?",
                "answer": "Astra Taylor wrote the movie Examined Life."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Martha Nussbaum, who starred in the movie Examined Life, have a role in a film written by Astra Taylor, the writer of Examined Life?",
            "answer": "Yes, Martha Nussbaum starred in the movie Examined Life, which was written by Astra Taylor."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Anne Hathaway star in Get Smart?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Get Smart star Alan Arkin?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Alan Arkin star in Slums of Beverly Hills?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Slums of Beverly Hills star Natasha Lyonne?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Natasha Lyonne star in Sleeping with Other People?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Anne Hathaway and Natasha Lyonne both star in a movie together, along with actors Alan Arkin and Steve Carell (who starred in Get Smart)?",
            "answer": "No, Anne Hathaway and Natasha Lyonne did not star in a movie together with both Alan Arkin and Steve Carell. While Anne Hathaway starred in 'Get Smart' with Alan Arkin, Natasha Lyonne did not. Similarly, Natasha Lyonne and Alan Arkin starred together in 'Slums of Beverly Hills', but Anne Hathaway and Steve Carell did not."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Does Freddie Highmore have any tags related to movies?",
                "answer": "Yes, 'The Art of Getting By' is one of the movies tagged with Freddie Highmore."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie did Emma Roberts star in?",
                "answer": "Emma Roberts starred in 'The Art of Getting By'."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was written by James Franco?",
                "answer": "James Franco wrote 'Palo Alto'."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie did James Franco star in and also wrote a different movie?",
                "answer": "James Franco starred in '127 Hours' and wrote 'Palo Alto'."
            },
            {
                "question": "Can you tell me about Freddie Highmore's movie connections to James Franco?",
                "answer": "Freddie Highmore and James Franco are connected through the movie 'The Art of Getting By', where Highmore starred and Franco wrote a different movie 'Palo Alto'. Furthermore, Franco starred in the movie '127 Hours'."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Question: Can you tell me about Freddie Highmore's movie connections to James Franco?",
            "answer": "Freddie Highmore and James Franco are connected through the movie 'The Art of Getting By', where Highmore starred and Franco wrote a different movie 'Palo Alto'. Furthermore, Franco starred in the movie '127 Hours'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Sam Waterston star in The Killing Fields?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "What genre is The Killing Fields associated with?",
                "answer": "Cambodia."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Holly star in Office Space?",
                "answer": "No."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Sam Waterston and Ron Livingston both star in a movie related to Cambodia?",
            "answer": "Yes, Sam Waterston starred in The Killing Fields which is associated with Cambodia and Ron Livingston starred in Office Space."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote 'Something New'?",
                "answer": "Kriss Turner"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed 'Something New'?",
                "answer": "Sanaa Hamri"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was directed by Sanaa Hamri in 2008?",
                "answer": "The Sisterhood of the Traveling Pants 2"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was 'Fifty Dead Men Walking' released?",
                "answer": "2008"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Who wrote 'Something New', and which movie directed by the same person was released in the same year as 'Fifty Dead Men Walking'?",
            "answer": "Kriss Turner wrote 'Something New'. The movie directed by Kriss Turner in the same year as 'Fifty Dead Men Walking' is 'The Sisterhood of the Traveling Pants 2'. Answer: < Kriss Turner, wrote_by, Something New, The Sisterhood of the Traveling Pants 2, directed_by, 2008 > is the chain of relations connecting the entities from the provided knowledge graph."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'Gods and Generals' released?",
                "answer": "2003"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'How to Lose a Guy in 10 Days' released?",
                "answer": "2003"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which actor starred in 'How to Lose a Guy in 10 Days'?",
                "answer": "Kate Hudson"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which actor starred in 'Fool's Gold'?",
                "answer": "Kate Hudson"
            },
            {
                "question": "What tags does 'Fool's Gold' have?",
                "answer": "kate hudson"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "In what year was 'Gods and Generals' released, and which actor starred in both 'How to Lose a Guy in 10 Days' and 'Fool's Gold' who also has a tag of kate hudson in 'Fool's Gold'?",
            "answer": "'Gods and Generals' was released in 2003, and Kate Hudson starred in both 'How to Lose a Guy in 10 Days' and 'Fool's Gold' who also has a tag of kate hudson in 'Fool's Gold'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Christine Adams star in Eye of the Dolphin?",
                "answer": "Yes, Christine Adams starred in Eye of the Dolphin."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote Eye of the Dolphin?",
                "answer": "Eye of the Dolphin was written by Wendell Morris."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Christine Adams star in a movie written by Wendell Morris?",
            "answer": "Yes, Christine Adams starred in Eye of the Dolphin, which was written by Wendell Morris."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie Prozac Nation?",
                "answer": "Erik Skjoldbj\u00e6rg"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie Prozac Nation?",
                "answer": "Elizabeth Wurtzel"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was directed by Erik Skjoldbj\u00e6rg and written by Elizabeth Wurtzel?",
            "answer": "Prozac Nation"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'Daisies' released?",
                "answer": "1966"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie \"Jesse James Meets Frankenstein's Daughter\" released?",
                "answer": "1966"
            },
            {
                "question": "What genre is the movie \"Jesse James Meets Frankenstein's Daughter\"?",
                "answer": "Western"
            },
            {
                "question": "What genre is the movie 'Django Unchained'?",
                "answer": "Western"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie starred Kerry Washington and was released in 1966?",
                "answer": "None. Kerry Washington starred in 'Django Unchained', which was released in a different year."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "In what year were the movies 'Daisies' and \"Jesse James Meets Frankenstein's Daughter\" released and which of them is a Western movie starring Kerry Washington?",
            "answer": "The movies 'Daisies' and \"Jesse James Meets Frankenstein's Daughter\" were both released in 1966. However, neither of them is a Western movie starring Kerry Washington. 'Django Unchained', a Western movie, was released in a different year and starred Kerry Washington."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'Plenty'?",
                "answer": "Fred Schepisi"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which actors starred in the movie 'Plenty'?",
                "answer": "Meryl Streep"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movies has Meryl Streep starred in?",
                "answer": "Plenty, It's Complicated"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the screenplay for 'It's Complicated'?",
                "answer": "Nancy Meyers"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movies has Nancy Meyers written?",
                "answer": "It's Complicated, I Love Trouble"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was directed by Fred Schepisi and starred Meryl Streep, who also starred in a movie written by Nancy Meyers who also wrote 'I Love Trouble'?",
            "answer": "Plenty"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Ayelet Zurer star in Adam Resurrected?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote Adam Resurrected?",
                "answer": "Yoram Kaniuk"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Ayelet Zurer star in a movie written by Yoram Kaniuk?",
            "answer": "Yes, Ayelet Zurer starred in the movie 'Adam Resurrected' which was written by Yoram Kaniuk."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote 'The Legend of the Lone Ranger'?",
                "answer": "Fran Striker and George W. Trendle"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who is the writer of 'The Green Hornet'?",
                "answer": "George W. Trendle"
            },
            {
                "question": "What genre is 'The Green Hornet'?",
                "answer": "Action"
            },
            {
                "question": "What genre of movie has 'The Green Hornet' as one of its films and is also a genre of the movie 'In China They Eat Dogs'?",
                "answer": "Action"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Who wrote 'The Green Hornet' and what genre is it, and what is a genre of a movie that shares this genre?",
            "answer": "George W. Trendle wrote 'The Green Hornet', and its genre is Action. A movie that shares this genre is 'In China They Eat Dogs'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Uncle Marin, the Billionaire'?",
                "answer": "Amza Pellea"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the genre of the movie 'Uncle Marin, the Billionaire'?",
                "answer": "Comedy"
            },
            {
                "question": "What genre does the movie 'Comedy' belong to?",
                "answer": "It is a genre itself, but it can be part of other genres such as 'O Lucky Man!'"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the genre of the movie 'O Lucky Man!'?",
                "answer": "Drama"
            },
            {
                "question": "What genre does the movie 'Drama' belong to?",
                "answer": "It is a genre itself, but it can be part of other genres such as 'Doing Time on Maple Drive'"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which genre does the movie 'Doing Time on Maple Drive' belong to, and who starred in the movie 'Uncle Marin, the Billionaire' that has the same genre as 'O Lucky Man!' which shares a genre with 'Doing Time on Maple Drive'?",
            "answer": "The genre of the movie 'Doing Time on Maple Drive' is Drama. Amza Pellea starred in the movie 'Uncle Marin, the Billionaire' that has the same genre as 'O Lucky Man!', which is Comedy."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "What genre is the movie 'Synecdoche, New York'?",
                "answer": "The movie 'Synecdoche, New York' is a Drama."
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the genre of 'Doing Time on Maple Drive'?",
                "answer": "The genre of 'Doing Time on Maple Drive' is Drama."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'Doing Time on Maple Drive'?",
                "answer": "The movie 'Doing Time on Maple Drive' was directed by Ken Olin."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie, classified as a Drama genre, was directed by Ken Olin and is also related to 'Synecdoche, New York' by having the same genre?",
            "answer": "The movie 'Doing Time on Maple Drive', which is directed by Ken Olin and shares the Drama genre with 'Synecdoche, New York'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Was Trey Callaway involved in writing The Young Americans?",
                "answer": "No."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed I Still Know What You Did Last Summer?",
                "answer": "Danny Cannon"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what genre is The Young Americans classified?",
                "answer": "Drama"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Trey Callaway, who wrote I Still Know What You Did Last Summer which was directed by Danny Cannon who also wrote The Young Americans that is a Drama genre movie, contribute to any other films in the Drama genre?",
            "answer": "Yes, Trey Callaway wrote Doing Time on Maple Drive which is also in the Drama genre."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Does Tesla have any relation to the movie The Prestige?",
                "answer": "Yes, Tesla has the tag 'The Prestige'."
            },
            {
                "question": "In which movie did Piper Perabo star?",
                "answer": "Piper Perabo starred in the movie The Prestige."
            },
            {
                "question": "In which genre does the movie The Lazarus Project fall?",
                "answer": "The Lazarus Project falls in the Drama genre."
            },
            {
                "question": "Can you describe the connection between Tesla, The Prestige, Piper Perabo, The Lazarus Project and Drama genre?",
                "answer": "Tesla has the tag 'The Prestige', which stars Piper Perabo. Piper Perabo also starred in 'The Lazarus Project', which falls in the Drama genre. The Drama genre also includes the movie 'Doing Time on Maple Drive'."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Can you describe the connection between Tesla, The Prestige, Piper Perabo, The Lazarus Project and Drama genre, and how it is related to the movie 'Doing Time on Maple Drive'?",
            "answer": "Tesla has the tag 'The Prestige', which stars Piper Perabo. Piper Perabo also starred in 'The Lazarus Project', which falls in the Drama genre. The Drama genre further includes the movie 'Doing Time on Maple Drive', creating a connection between Tesla, the movies 'The Prestige' and 'The Lazarus Project', Piper Perabo, the Drama genre and the movie 'Doing Time on Maple Drive'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Tamala Jones star in Little Richard?",
                "answer": "Yes, Tamala Jones starred in Little Richard."
            },
            {
                "question": "When was Little Richard released?",
                "answer": "Little Richard was released in the year 2000."
            },
            {
                "question": "When was Water Drops on Burning Rocks released?",
                "answer": "Water Drops on Burning Rocks was released in the year 2000."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote Water Drops on Burning Rocks?",
                "answer": "Water Drops on Burning Rocks was written by Fran\u00e7ois Ozon."
            },
            {
                "question": "What did Fran\u00e7ois Ozon write?",
                "answer": "Fran\u00e7ois Ozon wrote Water Drops on Burning Rocks and Swimming Pool."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Tamala Jones star in a movie written by Fran\u00e7ois Ozon?",
            "answer": "No, Tamala Jones did not star in a movie written by Fran\u00e7ois Ozon. Tamala Jones starred in Little Richard, which was released in the same year as Water Drops on Burning Rocks, but they are not the same movie and Fran\u00e7ois Ozon only wrote Water Drops on Burning Rocks and Swimming Pool."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Eric Idle star in the movie Splitting Heirs?",
                "answer": "Yes, he did."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie Splitting Heirs released?",
                "answer": "It was released in the year 1993."
            },
            {
                "question": "Was Addams Family Values also released in 1993?",
                "answer": "Yes, it was."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the screenplay for Addams Family Values?",
                "answer": "Paul Rudnick"
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Paul Rudnick write the movie \"Isn't She Great\"?",
                "answer": "Yes, he did."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Eric Idle star in a movie written by Paul Rudnick that was released in 1993?",
            "answer": "No, he did not. Eric Idle starred in Splitting Heirs, which was released in 1993, but it was not written by Paul Rudnick. Paul Rudnick wrote Addams Family Values and Isn't She Great, but neither of those movies starred Eric Idle."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Was Michael Schorr the writer of the movie Schultze Gets the Blues?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie Schultze Gets the Blues released?",
                "answer": "2003."
            },
            {
                "question": "Was the movie How to Lose a Guy in 10 Days also released in the year 2003?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Kate Hudson star in the movie How to Lose a Guy in 10 Days?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Kate Hudson also star in the movie Fool's Gold?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "In what year was the movie Schultze Gets the Blues, written by Michael Schorr, released and did Kate Hudson, who starred in the movie How to Lose a Guy in 10 Days which was released in the same year, also star in Fool's Gold?",
            "answer": "The movie Schultze Gets the Blues was released in the year 2003 and yes, Kate Hudson, who starred in the movie How to Lose a Guy in 10 Days which was also released in the year 2003, also starred in the movie Fool's Gold."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Was The Far Country written by Borden Chase?",
                "answer": "Yes, it was."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie starred Ruth Roman?",
                "answer": "The Far Country and Beyond the Forest"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was Beyond the Forest released?",
                "answer": "1949"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movies were written by Borden Chase and starred actors who also starred in movies released in 1949?",
                "answer": "The Far Country was written by Borden Chase and starred Ruth Roman who starred in Beyond the Forest which was released in 1949, the same year Always Leave Them Laughing came out."
            }
        ],
        "complex": null
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'Hypocrites' released?",
                "answer": "1915"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Hypocrites'?",
                "answer": "Lois Weber"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was written by Lois Weber, besides 'Hypocrites'?",
                "answer": "The Blot"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie did Margaret McWade star in?",
                "answer": "The Blot"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie written by Lois Weber, and released in 1915, stars Margaret McWade?",
            "answer": "The Blot"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Karen Colston star in the movie Sweetie?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie Sweetie?",
                "answer": "Gerard Lee"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Karen Colston star in a movie written by Gerard Lee?",
            "answer": "Yes, Karen Colston starred in the movie Sweetie, which was written by Gerard Lee."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Bird'?",
                "answer": "Joel Oliansky"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'The Competition'?",
                "answer": "Joel Oliansky"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie did Amy Irving star in?",
                "answer": "The Competition"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie did Amy Irving star in and who wrote it?",
                "answer": "Amy Irving starred in the movie 'The Competition' and it was written by Joel Oliansky"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Crossing Delancey' and who starred in it?",
                "answer": "The movie 'Crossing Delancey' was written by Susan Sandler and Amy Irving starred in it."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Bird' and which movie starring Amy Irving was written by the same person who wrote a movie starring someone who wrote a movie starring Amy Irving?",
            "answer": "Joel Oliansky wrote the movie 'Bird' and the movie 'The Competition' was written by Joel Oliansky, who also wrote a movie starring Susan Sandler, who wrote a movie starring Amy Irving."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie Trouble Man?",
                "answer": "Robert Hooks"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actor starred in the movie Trouble Man and can you name the movie?",
            "answer": "Robert Hooks starred in the movie Trouble Man."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie Caged Heat?",
                "answer": "Ella Reid"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actor starred in the movie Caged Heat and can you name the movie?",
            "answer": "Ella Reid starred in the movie Caged Heat."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'Pretty Maids All in a Row'?",
                "answer": "Roger Vadim"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie stars Rock Hudson?",
                "answer": "Pretty Maids All in a Row"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie does Rock Hudson star in, that was written by Julius J. Epstein?",
                "answer": "Send Me No Flowers"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was written by Julius J. Epstein, who also wrote Four Daughters?",
                "answer": "Send Me No Flowers"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was directed by Roger Vadim, and stars an actor who also starred in a movie written by Julius J. Epstein, who wrote Four Daughters?",
            "answer": "Pretty Maids All in a Row was directed by Roger Vadim and stars Rock Hudson, who starred in Send Me No Flowers, which was written by Julius J. Epstein, who also wrote Four Daughters."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Was Dogtooth written by Yorgos Lanthimos?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the language of the movie Dogtooth?",
                "answer": "Greek."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what language was the film \"Boy Eating the Bird's Food\" made?",
                "answer": "Greek."
            },
            {
                "question": "What genre is the movie \"Boy Eating the Bird's Food\"?",
                "answer": "Drama."
            },
            {
                "question": "What genre is the movie Doing Time on Maple Drive?",
                "answer": "Drama."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie, written in Greek, shares its drama genre with the movie Doing Time on Maple Drive and was also written by Yorgos Lanthimos?",
            "answer": "Dogtooth"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who directed The Care Bears Movie?",
                "answer": "Arna Selznick"
            },
            {
                "question": "In which movie did Jackie Burroughs star?",
                "answer": "The Care Bears Movie"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in The Grey Fox?",
                "answer": "Jackie Burroughs"
            },
            {
                "question": "In which movie did Richard Farnsworth star?",
                "answer": "The Grey Fox"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in Resurrection?",
                "answer": "Richard Farnsworth"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was directed by Arna Selznick and starred Jackie Burroughs, who also starred in The Grey Fox with Richard Farnsworth, who in turn starred in Resurrection?",
            "answer": "The Care Bears Movie, The Grey Fox, Resurrection"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Does Chris O'Dowd have any tags related to a movie?",
                "answer": "Yes, Chris O'Dowd has the tag 'Frequently Asked Questions About Time Travel' related to a movie."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which actor starred in 'Frequently Asked Questions About Time Travel'?",
                "answer": "Dean Lennox Kelly starred in 'Frequently Asked Questions About Time Travel'."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actor, Chris O'Dowd, has the tag 'Frequently Asked Questions About Time Travel' and also starred in this movie?",
            "answer": "Chris O'Dowd has the tag 'Frequently Asked Questions About Time Travel' and also starred in 'Frequently Asked Questions About Time Travel'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'The 39 Steps'?",
                "answer": "James Hawes"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the genre of the movie 'The 39 Steps'?",
                "answer": "Drama"
            },
            {
                "question": "What movie was directed by 'Ken Olin'?",
                "answer": "Doing Time on Maple Drive"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie, directed by the same person who directed 'Doing Time on Maple Drive', shares the same genre as 'The 39 Steps'?",
            "answer": "There is no movie that was directed by Ken Olin and shares the genre Drama with 'The 39 Steps', as James Hawes directed 'The 39 Steps' and Ken Olin directed 'Doing Time on Maple Drive'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'Doppelganger' released?",
                "answer": "1993"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'Addams Family Values' released?",
                "answer": "1993"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Addams Family Values'?",
                "answer": "Paul Rudnick"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Isn't She Great'?",
                "answer": "Paul Rudnick"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'Isn't She Great' released, which was written by the same person who wrote 'Addams Family Values' in 1993?",
                "answer": "2000\n\nComplex"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'Isn't She Great' released, which was written by the same person who wrote 'Addams Family Values' that was released in the same year as the release of the movie 'Doppelganger'?",
                "answer": "2000"
            }
        ],
        "complex": null
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Steve Howey star in the movie Supercross?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Mike Vogel star in the movie Wuthering Heights?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Christopher Masterson star in the movie Supercross?",
                "answer": "No."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Steve Howey and Christopher Masterson both star in any of the movies that Mike Vogel and Supercross share in common?",
            "answer": "No, Steve Howey and Christopher Masterson did not star in any of the same movies that Mike Vogel and Supercross share in common. While Steve Howey starred in Supercross and Christopher Masterson starred in Wuthering Heights, Mike Vogel is the only actor who starred in both movies."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'The Hoax'?",
                "answer": "Lasse Hallstr\u00f6m"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'Salmon Fishing in the Yemen'?",
                "answer": "Lasse Hallstr\u00f6m"
            },
            {
                "question": "What are the tags for the movie 'Salmon Fishing in the Yemen'?",
                "answer": "Lasse Hallstr\u00f6m"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the language of the movie 'My Life as a Dog'?",
                "answer": "Swedish"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie directed by Lasse Hallstr\u00f6m, who also directed 'Salmon Fishing in the Yemen', is in Swedish?",
            "answer": "My Life as a Dog"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who directed \"National Lampoon's Senior Trip\"?",
                "answer": "Kelly Makin"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed \"Mickey Blue Eyes\"?",
                "answer": "Kelly Makin"
            },
            {
                "question": "What genre is \"Mickey Blue Eyes\"?",
                "answer": "Crime"
            },
            {
                "question": "What genre is \"He Ran All the Way\"?",
                "answer": "Drama"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Who directed \"National Lampoon's Senior Trip\", and what genres are \"Mickey Blue Eyes\" and \"He Ran All the Way\"?",
            "answer": "Kelly Makin, \"Mickey Blue Eyes\" is of the Crime genre and \"He Ran All the Way\" is of the Drama genre."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie Crimetime?",
                "answer": "George Sluizer"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie starred Pete Postlethwaite?",
                "answer": "Crimetime"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which actor starred in The Age of Stupid?",
                "answer": "Pete Postlethwaite"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie The Age of Stupid?",
                "answer": "Franny Armstrong"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was directed by George Sluizer, starred Pete Postlethwaite, and was written by Franny Armstrong?",
            "answer": "The Age of Stupid"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Messenger of Death'?",
                "answer": "Charles Bronson"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Chato's Land'?",
                "answer": "Charles Bronson"
            },
            {
                "question": "What are the tags for the movie 'Chato's Land'?",
                "answer": "charles bronson"
            },
            {
                "question": "What are the tags for the actor 'charles bronson'?",
                "answer": "Death Wish 3"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Death Wish 3'?",
                "answer": "Ed Lauter"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actor, known for his role in 'Death Wish 3', also starred in a movie that has the tag 'charles bronson'?",
            "answer": "Ed Lauter starred in the movie 'Death Wish 3', and he also starred in 'Chato's Land', a movie with the tag 'charles bronson'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'The Hand'?",
                "answer": "Marc Brandel"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was written by 'Oliver Stone'?",
                "answer": "The Hand"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was written by the person who also wrote '8 Million Ways to Die'?",
                "answer": "The Hand"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the connection between 'Marc Brandel', 'The Hand', 'Oliver Stone', '8 Million Ways to Die', 'Lawrence Block', and 'A Walk Among the Tombstones' in terms of writing?",
                "answer": "Marc Brandel wrote 'The Hand', which was also written by Oliver Stone. Oliver Stone also wrote '8 Million Ways to Die', which was written by Lawrence Block, who in turn wrote 'A Walk Among the Tombstones'. Therefore, all these entities are connected through the relation of writing."
            }
        ],
        "complex": null
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Julianne Hough star in the movie Safe Haven?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "What genre is the movie Safe Haven?",
                "answer": "Romance."
            },
            {
                "question": "What genre is the movie John Tucker Must Die?",
                "answer": "The genre of the movie John Tucker Must Die is also Romance, as it is a sub-genre of the movie Safe Haven."
            },
            {
                "question": "What are the tags for the movie John Tucker Must Die?",
                "answer": "The tags for the movie John Tucker Must Die are 'high school'."
            },
            {
                "question": "What are the tags for 'high school'?",
                "answer": "The tags for 'high school' are 'Stand and Deliver'."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Julianne Hough star in a high school movie that can be related to Stand and Deliver through its genre?",
            "answer": "Yes, Julianne Hough starred in the movie Safe Haven which has the genre Romance, and Romance is a sub-genre of John Tucker Must Die which has the tags 'high school', and 'high school' is related to Stand and Deliver through its tags."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Hustle'?",
                "answer": "Catherine Deneuve"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'The April Fools'?",
                "answer": "Catherine Deneuve"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'The April Fools'?",
                "answer": "Stuart Rosenberg"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was directed by Stuart Rosenberg and released in the year 1986?",
                "answer": "Let's Get Harry"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie released in 1986 was directed by the same person who directed a movie in which Catherine Deneuve played an actor, and also features Catherine Deneuve as an actor?",
            "answer": "Let's Get Harry, directed by Stuart Rosenberg, who also directed 'The April Fools' where Catherine Deneuve played an actor, and Catherine Deneuve is an actor in 'Let's Get Harry'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'Amreeka' released?",
                "answer": "2009"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'He's Just Not That Into You' released?",
                "answer": "2009"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who is one of the writers of the movie 'He's Just Not That Into You'?",
                "answer": "Liz Tuccillo"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "In what year was 'He's Just Not That Into You' released, and who is one of the writers of this movie that was also released in 2009, which is the same year as the movie 'Amreeka'?",
            "answer": "'He's Just Not That Into You' was released in the year 2009, and Liz Tuccillo is one of the writers of this movie that was also released in 2009, the same year as the movie 'Amreeka'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'The Final Cut'?",
                "answer": "Mimi Kuzyk"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actors starred in the movie 'The Final Cut' along with Mimi Kuzyk?",
            "answer": "I'm unable to provide that information, as the provided tuple only specifies Mimi Kuzyk as one of the actors in 'The Final Cut'. To find out which other actors starred in the movie, you would need additional tuples containing the names of those actors."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "What movie did Mika Kaurism\u00e4ki have the tag 'The Worthless'?",
                "answer": "The Worthless"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'The Worthless' released?",
                "answer": "1982"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'They Call Me Bruce?' released?",
                "answer": "1982"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which actor starred in the movie 'They Call Me Bruce?'?",
                "answer": "Johnny Yune"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "In what year was the movie 'They Call Me Bruce?' released, and who starred in it?",
            "answer": "They Call Me Bruce? was released in 1982 and starred Johnny Yune."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Raffles'?",
                "answer": "Sidney Howard"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Gone with the Wind'?",
                "answer": "Sidney Howard"
            },
            {
                "question": "What tags does the movie 'Gone with the Wind' have?",
                "answer": "It has the tag 'national film registry'"
            },
            {
                "question": "What tags does the 'national film registry' have?",
                "answer": "It has the tag 'Swing Time'"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the release year of the movie 'Swing Time'?",
                "answer": "1936"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie, written by the same person who wrote 'Gone with the Wind', was released in 1936 and is also tagged as a film in the 'national film registry' along with 'Swing Time'?",
            "answer": "There is no such movie. Sidney Howard, who wrote 'Gone with the Wind', didn't write any movie released in 1936 that has the tag 'national film registry' along with 'Swing Time'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote 'The Fifth Estate'?",
                "answer": "Josh Singer"
            },
            {
                "question": "What format is 'The Fifth Estate' released in?",
                "answer": "bd-r"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was 'Rocco and His Brothers' released?",
                "answer": "1960"
            },
            {
                "question": "What other movie shares the same release year with 'Visit to a Small Planet' and is also tagged with 'bd-r' format along with 'Rocco and His Brothers'?",
                "answer": "The Fifth Estate"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Who wrote 'The Fifth Estate', which was released in the same year as 'Visit to a Small Planet' and shares the same format and tags with 'Rocco and His Brothers'?",
            "answer": "Josh Singer"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Gene Hackman star in Narrow Margin?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Anne Archer star in Narrow Margin?",
                "answer": "Yes, she did."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Anne Archer star in Patriot Games?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Does Patriot Games have a tag related to Thora Birch?",
                "answer": "Yes, it does."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Thora Birch star in Patriot Games or Now and Then?",
                "answer": "No, she did not star in Patriot Games, but she did star in Now and Then.\n\nComplex"
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Gene Hackman and Anne Archer star in Narrow Margin and Patriot Games, with Thora Birch having a connection to either movie?",
                "answer": "Yes, Gene Hackman and Anne Archer starred in Narrow Margin and Patriot Games, respectively. Additionally, Thora Birch has a connection to Patriot Games through a shared tag."
            }
        ],
        "complex": null
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Does the movie 'Night and the City' have a tag related to wrestling?",
                "answer": "Yes, it does."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'Night and the City'?",
                "answer": "Irwin Winkler"
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Irwin Winkler direct the movie 'Life as a House'?",
                "answer": "Yes, he did."
            },
            {
                "question": "Does the movie 'Life as a House' have a tag related to Irwin Winkler?",
                "answer": "Yes, it does."
            },
            {
                "question": "Has Irwin Winkler directed any movies related to 'The Net'?",
                "answer": "Yes, he has."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movies were directed by Irwin Winkler, and what tags are associated with those movies and the director himself?",
            "answer": "Irwin Winkler directed 'Night and the City', which has a tag related to wrestling. He also directed 'Life as a House', which has a tag related to him. Additionally, he directed 'The Net', and it appears that there is a tag related to him for this movie as well."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'Wrong Turn at Tahoe'?",
                "answer": "Franck Khalfoun"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the screenplay for Franck Khalfoun?",
                "answer": "P2"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who is the writer of the screenplay 'P2'?",
                "answer": "Alexandre Aja"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was written by Alexandre Aja?",
                "answer": "The Hills Have Eyes"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movies are associated with the writer Alexandre Aja?",
                "answer": "The Hills Have Eyes, Wrong Turn at Tahoe"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Who directed the movie 'Wrong Turn at Tahoe' and which movies are associated with the writer Alexandre Aja?",
            "answer": "Franck Khalfoun directed the movie 'Wrong Turn at Tahoe' and The Hills Have Eyes, Wrong Turn at Tahoe are associated with the writer Alexandre Aja."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie Congo?",
                "answer": "Dylan Walsh"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie Just Add Water?",
                "answer": "Dylan Walsh"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie Just Add Water released?",
                "answer": "2"
            }
        ],
        "complex": null
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Brad Pitt star in A River Runs Through It?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Tom Skerritt star in Redwood Highway?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the genre of Redwood Highway?",
                "answer": "Drama."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Brad Pitt and Tom Skerritt both star in a Drama movie?",
            "answer": "Yes, Brad Pitt starred in A River Runs Through It and Tom Skerritt starred in Redwood Highway, both of which are Drama movies."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'First Love'?",
                "answer": "Marco Mariolini and Massimo Gaudioso"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was written by Massimo Gaudioso?",
                "answer": "'First Love'"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which person is related to 'First Love' by the relation 'written_by'?",
                "answer": "Marco Mariolini and Massimo Gaudioso"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which people are related to the movie 'First Love' by the relation 'written_by'?",
            "answer": "Marco Mariolini and Massimo Gaudioso are related to the movie 'First Love' by the relation 'written_by'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Mario Van Peebles star in Full Eclipse?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Bruce Payne star in Full Eclipse?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Bruce Payne star in Passenger 57?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Wesley Snipes star in Passenger 57?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Wesley Snipes star in White Men Can't Jump?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Mario Van Peebles, Bruce Payne, Wesley Snipes all star in the same movies?",
            "answer": "No, they did not. Mario Van Peebles and Bruce Payne starred in Full Eclipse, Bruce Payne and Wesley Snipes starred in Passenger 57, and Wesley Snipes starred in White Men Can't Jump."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Ripley Under Ground'?",
                "answer": "Barry Pepper"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'The Three Burials of Melquiades Estrada'?",
                "answer": "Tommy Lee Jones"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Rules of Engagement'?",
                "answer": "Tommy Lee Jones"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actor starred in 'Ripley Under Ground', 'The Three Burials of Melquiades Estrada', and has a tag in 'Rules of Engagement'?",
            "answer": "Tommy Lee Jones has a tag in 'Rules of Engagement' and also starred in 'Ripley Under Ground' and 'The Three Burials of Melquiades Estrada'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "What director has the tags 'Picnic on the Grass'?",
                "answer": "Jean Renoir"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Picnic on the Grass'?",
                "answer": "Jean Renoir"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who is the writer of 'The Woman on the Beach'?",
                "answer": "Jean Renoir"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was starred by Charles Bickford?",
                "answer": "The Woman on the Beach"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which actor starred in 'Branded' and has a connection to Jean Renoir?",
                "answer": "Charles Bickford"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actor starred in a movie written by Jean Renoir and also appeared in a movie related to one of his films through the 'starred_actors' relation?",
            "answer": "Charles Bickford"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Does Stephen Sommers have a tag related to The Mummy Returns?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote The Mummy Returns?",
                "answer": "Stephen Sommers"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie did Stephen Sommers write that has a tag bd-r?",
                "answer": "The Mummy"
            },
            {
                "question": "Does the movie written by Stephen Sommers, The Mummy, have a tag related to Rocco and His Brothers?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Stephen Sommers write The Mummy Returns and is there a connection between The Mummy Returns and Rocco and His Brothers through movie tags?",
            "answer": "Yes, Stephen Sommers wrote The Mummy Returns and the movie The Mummy, written by Stephen Sommers, has a tag related to Rocco and His Brothers."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie Live Wire?",
                "answer": "Bart Baker"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which person wrote the movie Live Wire and what is the name of that movie?",
            "answer": "Bart Baker wrote the movie Live Wire."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "In what year was Law and Order released?",
                "answer": "1953."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was 99 River Street released?",
                "answer": "1953."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie starred Evelyn Keyes?",
                "answer": "99 River Street."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie starred Evelyn Keyes and Keenan Wynn?",
                "answer": "The Thrill of Brazil."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie starring both Evelyn Keyes and Keenan Wynn was released in the same year as Law and Order?",
            "answer": "The Thrill of Brazil, which was released in 1953, the same year as Law and Order."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote 'Tapestries of Hope'?",
                "answer": "Michealene Cristini Risley"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which actors starred in 'Tapestries of Hope'?",
                "answer": "Betty Makoni"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actors starred in the movie written by Michealene Cristini Risley?",
            "answer": "Betty Makoni starred in the movie 'Tapestries of Hope' which was written by Michealene Cristini Risley."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'The Floating Castle'?",
                "answer": "Shinji Higuchi"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'The Floating Castle' released?",
                "answer": "2012"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'How to Make Money Selling Drugs' released?",
                "answer": "2012"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie starred the actor Susan Sarandon?",
                "answer": "How to Make Money Selling Drugs"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie starred the actor Susan Sarandon and was released in 2012?",
                "answer": "How to Make Money Selling Drugs"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was directed by Shinji Higuchi and starred the actor Susan Sarandon, who was also in the movie 'The Great Waldo Pepper' released in the same year as 'The Floating Castle'?",
            "answer": "There is no such movie that meets all these criteria. Shinji Higuchi directed 'The Floating Castle' and Susan Sarandon starred in 'How to Make Money Selling Drugs' and 'The Great Waldo Pepper', but these movies were not directed by Higuchi and Sarandon did not star in these movies together. Additionally, 'How to Make Money Selling Drugs' was released in the same year as 'The Floating Castle' (2012), but 'The Great Waldo Pepper' was released in 1975."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Dan Duryea star in Scarlet Street?",
                "answer": "Yes, Dan Duryea starred in Scarlet Street."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote Scarlet Street?",
                "answer": "Scarlet Street was written by Georges de La Fouchardi\u00e8re."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Dan Duryea, who starred in Scarlet Street, act in a movie written by Georges de La Fouchardi\u00e8re?",
            "answer": "Yes, Dan Duryea starred in the movie Scarlet Street, which was written by Georges de La Fouchardi\u00e8re."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie '\u00c6on Flux' released?",
                "answer": "2005"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'Boy Eats Girl' released?",
                "answer": "2005"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'Boy Eats Girl'?",
                "answer": "Stephen Bradley"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "In what year was the movie 'Boy Eats Girl' released and who directed it?",
            "answer": "The movie 'Boy Eats Girl' was released in the year 2005 and it was directed by Stephen Bradley."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Under the Bridges'?",
                "answer": "Helmut K\u00e4utner"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which person wrote the movie 'Under the Bridges' and what is the title of that movie?",
            "answer": "Helmut K\u00e4utner wrote the movie 'Under the Bridges'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Knight of Cups'?",
                "answer": "Terrence Malick"
            },
            {
                "question": "What movie was written by Terrence Malick?",
                "answer": "The Thin Red Line"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie has the tag 'george clooney'?",
                "answer": "The Thin Red Line"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie has the tag 'Burn After Reading'?",
                "answer": "George Clooney"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which actor starred in the movie 'Burn After Reading' and also has the tag 'george clooney'?",
                "answer": "George Clooney"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actor starred in the movie 'Burn After Reading', which was written by the same person who wrote the movie 'Knight of Cups' and also has tags related to the movies 'The Thin Red Line' and 'Burn After Reading'?",
            "answer": "George Clooney"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie Big Fan?",
                "answer": "Robert D. Siegel"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which actors starred in the movie Big Fan?",
                "answer": "Marcia Jean Kurtz"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actors starred in the movie Big Fan, which was written by Robert D. Siegel?",
            "answer": "Marcia Jean Kurtz"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Robert Forster star in the movie Avalanche?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Mia Farrow star in the movie Avalanche?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Danny Glover star in the movie Be Kind Rewind?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Mia Farrow star in the movie Be Kind Rewind?",
                "answer": "No."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Robert Forster star in the movie Be Kind Rewind?",
                "answer": "No."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Danny Glover star in the movie Alpha and Omega?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Robert Forster, Mia Farrow, Danny Glover, and Jack Black (who starred in the movie Be Kind Rewind) all star in the movie Alpha and Omega?",
            "answer": "No, Jack Black did not star in the movie Alpha and Omega."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Juliette Goglia star in A Grandpa for Christmas?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Ernest Borgnine star in A Grandpa for Christmas?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Doris Roberts star in Another Harvest Moon?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Juliette Goglia star in Another Harvest Moon?",
                "answer": "No."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Ernest Borgnine star in Play the Game?",
                "answer": "No."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Juliette Goglia and Doris Roberts both star in a movie, and did Ernest Borgnine and Doris Roberts also star in a movie together?",
            "answer": "Yes, Juliette Goglia and Doris Roberts both starred in 'A Grandpa for Christmas', and Ernest Borgnine and Doris Roberts both starred in 'Another Harvest Moon'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'Diary of the Dead' released?",
                "answer": "2007"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'For the Bible Tells Me So' released?",
                "answer": "2007"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'For the Bible Tells Me So'?",
                "answer": "Daniel G. Karslake"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "In what year was the movie 'For the Bible Tells Me So' released and who wrote it?",
            "answer": "The movie 'For the Bible Tells Me So' was released in 2007 and it was written by Daniel G. Karslake."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Pushing Hands'?",
                "answer": "Ang Lee"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Tortilla Soup'?",
                "answer": "James Schamus"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was James Schamus a writer for?",
                "answer": "Hulk"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie starred Jennifer Connelly?",
                "answer": "Hulk"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actor starred in a movie written by the same person who wrote 'Pushing Hands'?",
            "answer": "Jennifer Connelly starred in the movie 'Hulk', which was written by James Schamus, who also wrote 'Tortilla Soup' and 'Pushing Hands' was written by Ang Lee."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Robert Wuhl star in the movie Mistress?",
                "answer": "Yes, he did."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie Mistress?",
                "answer": "J.F. Lawton"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Robert Wuhl star in a movie written by J.F. Lawton?",
            "answer": "Yes, Robert Wuhl starred in the movie Mistress, which was written by J.F. Lawton."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote 'The Imitation Game'?",
                "answer": "Graham Moore and Andrew Hodges"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which book was 'The Imitation Game' based on?",
                "answer": "The book was written by Andrew Hodges."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Who are the writers of 'The Imitation Game' and what is the book called that the movie is based on?",
            "answer": "The writers of 'The Imitation Game' are Graham Moore and Andrew Hodges, and the movie is based on a book written by Andrew Hodges."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did director Ted Demme use the tag 'Beautiful Girls' in any of his movies?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie starred Matt Dillon and has the tag 'Beautiful Girls'?",
                "answer": "Beautiful Girls"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie starring Matt Dillon has the tag '2'?",
                "answer": "There's Something About Mary"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie has the tag 'Sin City' and is connected to director Ted Demme through the actor Matt Dillon and the movie 'Beautiful Girls'?",
                "answer": "There's Something About Mary"
            }
        ],
        "complex": null
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in A Walk in the Clouds?",
                "answer": "Giancarlo Giannini"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote A Walk in the Clouds?",
                "answer": "Vittorio de Benedetti"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was starred by Giancarlo Giannini and written by Vittorio de Benedetti?",
            "answer": "A Walk in the Clouds"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'Hannah Arendt' released?",
                "answer": "2012"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'How to Make Money Selling Drugs' released?",
                "answer": "2012"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which actor starred in the movie 'How to Make Money Selling Drugs'?",
                "answer": "Susan Sarandon"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which actor starred in the movie 'The Great Waldo Pepper'?",
                "answer": "Susan Sarandon"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the genre of the movie 'The Great Waldo Pepper'?",
                "answer": "Drama"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "In what year was the movie 'Hannah Arendt' released, and which actor starred in both 'How to Make Money Selling Drugs' and 'The Great Waldo Pepper' which is a Drama?",
            "answer": "The movie 'Hannah Arendt' was released in the year 2012. Susan Sarandon is the actor who starred in both 'How to Make Money Selling Drugs' and 'The Great Waldo Pepper' which is a Drama."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "What movie has a tag of 'mouse'?",
                "answer": "The Rescuers"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie has the tag 'The Great Mouse Detective'?",
                "answer": "mouse"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'The Great Mouse Detective'?",
                "answer": "Eve Titus"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie, written by Eve Titus, has the tag 'mouse' and is also related to the movie 'The Great Mouse Detective'?",
            "answer": "The Rescuers"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Breaking Wind'?",
                "answer": "Craig Moss"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which actor starred in the movie 'Breaking Wind'?",
                "answer": "Heather Ann Davis"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actor was starred in the movie written by Craig Moss?",
            "answer": "Heather Ann Davis starred in the movie 'Breaking Wind' which was written by Craig Moss."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote 'The Flight of Dragons'?",
                "answer": "Peter Dickinson"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which author wrote the movie 'The Flight of Dragons'?",
            "answer": "Peter Dickinson wrote the movie 'The Flight of Dragons'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "What genre is the movie 'Who Framed Roger Rabbit' associated with?",
                "answer": "The genre of 'Who Framed Roger Rabbit' is fantasy."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which genre does the tag 'fantasy' belong to?",
                "answer": "The tag 'fantasy' belongs to the genre Fantasy."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which author wrote the movie 'At the Earth's Core'?",
                "answer": "The movie 'At the Earth's Core' was written by Edgar Rice Burroughs."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie, written by Edgar Rice Burroughs, shares a genre association with 'Who Framed Roger Rabbit' through the tag 'fantasy'?",
            "answer": "The movie 'At the Earth's Core', written by Edgar Rice Burroughs, shares the Fantasy genre association with 'Who Framed Roger Rabbit'. Answer: The Imaginarium of Doctor Parnassus"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Helen of Troy'?",
                "answer": "Hugh Gray"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which actor starred in 'Helen of Troy'?",
                "answer": "Cedric Hardwicke"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie did Cedric Hardwicke star in?",
                "answer": "Commandos Strike at Dawn"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Commandos Strike at Dawn'?",
                "answer": "C.S. Forester"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was written by C.S. Forester?",
                "answer": "The Pride and the Passion"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actor starred in a movie written by the same person who wrote 'The Pride and the Passion'?",
            "answer": "Cedric Hardwicke starred in 'Commandos Strike at Dawn' which was written by C.S. Forester, who also wrote 'The Pride and the Passion'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie '47 Ronin'?",
                "answer": "Carl Rinsch"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which director is responsible for the movie '47 Ronin' and what is its title?",
            "answer": "Carl Rinsch is the director of the movie '47 Ronin'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Emilio Estevez star in Loaded Weapon 1?",
                "answer": "Yes, he did."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Aidan Quinn star in Stakeout?",
                "answer": "Yes, he did."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Anthony LaPaglia star in Commandments?",
                "answer": "Yes, he did."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Emilio Estevez, Aidan Quinn, and Anthony LaPaglia all star in movies connected by the 'starred_actors' relationship?",
            "answer": "Yes, Emilio Estevez starred in Loaded Weapon 1, Aidan Quinn starred in Stakeout, and Stakeout is connected to Loaded Weapon 1 through the 'starred_actors' relationship. Furthermore, Aidan Quinn also starred in Commandments, and Commandments is connected to Stakeout through the 'starred_actors' relationship. Finally, Anthony LaPaglia starred in Commandments, thus linking all three actors together."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'The Proposal'?",
                "answer": "Anne Fletcher"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie stars Mary Steenburgen?",
                "answer": "The Proposal"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie stars Nick Offerman?",
                "answer": "A Walk in the Woods"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in 'Somebody Up There Likes Me'?",
                "answer": "Nick Offerman"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was directed by Anne Fletcher and stars Mary Steenburgen who also starred in a movie with Nick Offerman, who in turn starred in 'Somebody Up There Likes Me'?",
            "answer": "The Proposal and A Walk in the Woods"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'In Old Arizona'?",
                "answer": "O. Henry"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie did Warner Baxter star in?",
                "answer": "In Old Arizona"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie did Warner Baxter and Albert Hackett both work on?",
                "answer": "Penthouse"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Penthouse' and 'Naughty Marietta'?",
                "answer": "Albert Hackett"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actor starred in a movie written by the same person who wrote 'Naughty Marietta' and a movie written by the same person who wrote 'In Old Arizona'?",
            "answer": "Warner Baxter"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who directed Despicable Me 2?",
                "answer": "Pierre Coffin"
            },
            {
                "question": "What movie has the tag 'russell brand'?",
                "answer": "Despicable Me 2"
            },
            {
                "question": "What movie has the tag 'Get Him to the Greek'?",
                "answer": "Russell Brand"
            },
            {
                "question": "What movie has the tag 'elisabeth moss'?",
                "answer": "Get Him to the Greek"
            },
            {
                "question": "What movie has the tag 'Did You Hear About the Morgans?'?",
                "answer": "Elisabeth Moss"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was directed by Pierre Coffin and has the tags 'russell brand', 'Get Him to the Greek', 'elisabeth moss', and 'Did You Hear About the Morgans?'?",
            "answer": "Despicable Me 2 (however, only 'russell brand' is a correct tag for this movie)"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Noriko Hidaka star in My Neighbor Totoro?",
                "answer": "Yes, Noriko Hidaka starred in My Neighbor Totoro."
            },
            {
                "question": "What studio produced My Neighbor Totoro?",
                "answer": "Studio Ghibli"
            },
            {
                "question": "What language is The Cat Returns in?",
                "answer": "Japanese"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Noriko Hidaka star in a Japanese Studio Ghibli film that is also in the same language as Come See the Paradise?",
            "answer": "Yes, Noriko Hidaka starred in My Neighbor Totoro, which is a Studio Ghibli film and in Japanese, and Come See the Paradise is also in Japanese."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Futuresport'?",
                "answer": "Dean Cain"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Abandoned'?",
                "answer": "Dean Cain, Mimi Rogers"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'The Rapture'?",
                "answer": "Mimi Rogers"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'The Rapture' released?",
                "answer": "1991"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie starring Dean Cain was released in 1991, and who starred in that movie along with Dean Cain?",
            "answer": "There is no movie starring Dean Cain that was released in 1991. Dean Cain starred in the movie 'Abandoned' along with Mimi Rogers, but it was not released in 1991."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "In what language is the movie 'Alice and Martin' in?",
                "answer": "The movie 'Alice and Martin' is in the French language."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what language is the movie 'Two Men in Manhattan' in?",
                "answer": "The movie 'Two Men in Manhattan' is in the French language."
            },
            {
                "question": "What genre is the movie 'Two Men in Manhattan' in?",
                "answer": "The movie 'Two Men in Manhattan' is in the Crime genre."
            },
            {
                "question": "What genre is the movie 'He Ran All the Way' in?",
                "answer": "The movie 'He Ran All the Way' is in the Drama genre."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "In what language is the movie 'He Ran All the Way' in and what genre is the movie 'Alice and Martin' in?",
            "answer": "The movie 'He Ran All the Way' is in the English language and the movie 'Alice and Martin' is in the French language. The movie 'Alice and Martin' is in the Drama genre and the movie 'He Ran All the Way' is in the Crime genre."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie \"The Mirror Crack'd\"?",
                "answer": "Barry Sandler"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which person wrote the movie \"The Mirror Crack'd\" and what is that person's name?",
            "answer": "The movie \"The Mirror Crack'd\" was written by Barry Sandler."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Marjatta Raita star in Uuno Turhapuro?",
                "answer": "Yes, she did."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was Uuno Turhapuro released?",
                "answer": "It was released in the year 1973."
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the release year of Even Angels Eat Beans?",
                "answer": "Even Angels Eat Beans was released in the year 1973."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what language was Even Angels Eat Beans released?",
                "answer": "Even Angels Eat Beans was released in Italian."
            },
            {
                "question": "What language was the movie 'What Have They Done to Your Daughters?' released in?",
                "answer": "What Have They Done to Your Daughters? was released in Italian."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie did Marjatta Raita star in, that was released in the same year as 'What Have They Done to Your Daughters?' and in the Italian language, which is originally 'Even Angels Eat Beans' but was actually released as Uuno Turhapuro in 1973?",
            "answer": "Marjatta Raita starred in Uuno Turhapuro, which was released in the same year, 1973, as 'What Have They Done to Your Daughters?' and was originally an Italian film, but was released as Uuno Turhapuro."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "What film did Franco Zeffirelli direct that has the tag 'The Taming of the Shrew'?",
                "answer": "The Taming of the Shrew"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie stars Elizabeth Taylor that has the tag 'The Taming of the Shrew'?",
                "answer": "The Taming of the Shrew"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which film stars Elizabeth Taylor that has the tag 'Cat on a Hot Tin Roof'?",
                "answer": "Cat on a Hot Tin Roof"
            },
            {
                "question": "What format is 'Cat on a Hot Tin Roof' available in and what film in that format has the tag 'Rocco and His Brothers'?",
                "answer": "'Cat on a Hot Tin Roof' is available in the Blu-ray Disc format (bd-r) and the film 'Rocco and His Brothers' has the tag 'Rocco and His Brothers' in that format."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which film did Franco Zeffirelli direct that stars Elizabeth Taylor, who also starred in a movie that is available in the Blu-ray Disc format (bd-r) and has the tag 'Rocco and His Brothers'?",
            "answer": "Franco Zeffirelli directed 'The Taming of the Shrew' that stars Elizabeth Taylor, who also starred in 'Cat on a Hot Tin Roof' which is available in the Blu-ray Disc format (bd-r) and has the tag 'Rocco and His Brothers'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Michelle Rodriguez star in the movie 3 A.M.?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 3 A.M.?",
                "answer": "Lee Davis."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Michelle Rodriguez star in a movie written by Lee Davis?",
            "answer": "Yes, Michelle Rodriguez starred in the movie 3 A.M., which was written by Lee Davis."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Gilda Radner starred_actors Haunted Honeymoon'?",
                "answer": "Gilda Radner and Jonathan Pryce"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Jonathan Pryce starred_actors Hysteria'?",
                "answer": "Jonathan Pryce and Felicity Jones"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Felicity Jones starred_actors Like Crazy'?",
                "answer": "Felicity Jones"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actors starred in the movies 'Gilda Radner starred_actors Haunted Honeymoon', 'Jonathan Pryce starred_actors Hysteria', and 'Felicity Jones starred_actors Like Crazy'?",
            "answer": "Gilda Radner, Jonathan Pryce, and Felicity Jones"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie Jamesy Boy?",
                "answer": "Lane Shadgett"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was starred by Taissa Farmiga?",
                "answer": "Jamesy Boy"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was Taissa Farmiga and Vera Farmiga both in?",
                "answer": "At Middleton"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movies has Vera Farmiga starred in, that also had Taissa Farmiga in a different movie?",
                "answer": "Vera Farmiga starred in the movie At Middleton, and Taissa Farmiga starred in the movie Jamesy Boy."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Who wrote Jamesy Boy, and which movies has Vera Farmiga and Taissa Farmiga both appeared in, directly or indirectly through other movies?",
            "answer": "Lane Shadgett wrote Jamesy Boy. Vera Farmiga and Taissa Farmiga both appeared in the movie At Middleton, as Vera Farmiga starred in At Middleton, and Taissa Farmiga starred in Jamesy Boy."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'Wise Blood' released?",
                "answer": "The movie 'Wise Blood' was released in 1979."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'All Quiet on the Western Front' released?",
                "answer": "The movie 'All Quiet on the Western Front' was released in 1979."
            },
            {
                "question": "Does 'All Quiet on the Western Front' have the tag 'national film registry'?",
                "answer": "Yes, 'All Quiet on the Western Front' has the tag 'national film registry'."
            },
            {
                "question": "Does 'Swing Time' have the tag 'national film registry'?",
                "answer": "Yes, 'Swing Time' has the tag 'national film registry'."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'Swing Time' released?",
                "answer": "The movie 'Swing Time' was released in 1936."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "In what release years were the movies 'Wise Blood', 'All Quiet on the Western Front', and 'Swing Time' released, and which of these movies are tagged as 'national film registry'?",
            "answer": "The movie 'Wise Blood' was released in 1979, 'All Quiet on the Western Front' was also released in 1979, and 'Swing Time' was released in 1936. Among these, 'All Quiet on the Western Front' and 'Swing Time' are tagged as 'national film registry'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "What tags does The Wedding Banquet have?",
                "answer": "parents"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which actor starred in The Wedding Banquet?",
                "answer": "Sihung Lung"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie did Sihung Lung star in?",
                "answer": "Eat Drink Man Woman"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was Eat Drink Man Woman released?",
                "answer": "1994"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was released in the same year as Eat Drink Man Woman and what is the release year of The Wedding Banquet?",
                "answer": "I Like It Like That, 1994, The Wedding Banquet was released in 1994."
            }
        ],
        "complex": null
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Was Epidemic written by Lars von Trier?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the nationality of The Five Obstructions?",
                "answer": "The Five Obstructions is in Danish."
            },
            {
                "question": "What are some movies written by Lars von Trier?",
                "answer": "Epidemic and Dear Wendy are some movies written by Lars von Trier."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movies have the tag 'lars von trier'?",
                "answer": "Dear Wendy and The Five Obstructions have the tag 'lars von trier'."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which Danish-language movie was written by Lars von Trier, who also wrote Epidemic and has movies tagged with his name?",
            "answer": "The Five Obstructions is the Danish-language movie written by Lars von Trier, who also wrote Epidemic and has movies tagged with his name."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in RoboCop 3?",
                "answer": "Robert John Burke"
            },
            {
                "question": "In which movie did Robert John Burke star?",
                "answer": "Safe"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie Safe?",
                "answer": "Todd Haynes"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was written by Todd Haynes?",
                "answer": "Velvet Goldmine"
            },
            {
                "question": "What tags are associated with Velvet Goldmine?",
                "answer": "todd haynes"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actor starred in RoboCop 3 and appeared in a movie written by the same person who wrote Velvet Goldmine?",
            "answer": "Robert John Burke starred in RoboCop 3 and appeared in the movie Safe, which was written by Todd Haynes who also wrote Velvet Goldmine."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Eden Lake'?",
                "answer": "Kelly Reilly"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Heaven Is for Real'?",
                "answer": "Kelly Reilly"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'Heaven Is for Real' released?",
                "answer": "2014"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'A Girl Walks Home Alone at Night' released?",
                "answer": "2014"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie released in 2014 has the tag 'iran'?",
                "answer": "A Girl Walks Home Alone at Night"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actor starred in both 'Eden Lake' and a movie released in 2014 that has the tag 'iran'?",
            "answer": "Kelly Reilly"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "What genre is the movie 'Saving Mr. Banks'?",
                "answer": "The movie 'Saving Mr. Banks' is a Drama."
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the genre of 'Doing Time on Maple Drive'?",
                "answer": "The genre of 'Doing Time on Maple Drive' is Drama."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'Doing Time on Maple Drive'?",
                "answer": "The movie 'Doing Time on Maple Drive' was directed by Ken Olin."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "What genre of movie was directed by Ken Olin and also includes the movie 'Saving Mr. Banks' as one of its films?",
            "answer": "The genre of movie directed by Ken Olin and also including the movie 'Saving Mr. Banks' is Drama."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "What kind of entity is 'Romy and Michele's High School Reunion'?",
                "answer": "'Romy and Michele's High School Reunion' is a character. (Note: This is not accurate, but I'm following the knowledge graph provided.)"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie has the tags 'Romy and Michele's High School Reunion'?",
                "answer": "'Romy and Michele's High School Reunion' is a movie with the tags 'Romy and Michele's High School Reunion'."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed 'Romy and Michele's High School Reunion'?",
                "answer": "David Mirkin"
            },
            {
                "question": "What movie was directed by David Mirkin?",
                "answer": "'Romy and Michele's High School Reunion' was directed by David Mirkin."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote 'The Simpsons Movie'?",
                "answer": "George Meyer and David Mirkin"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was directed by the person who wrote 'The Simpsons Movie' and also has the tags 'Romy and Michele's High School Reunion'?",
            "answer": "'Romy and Michele's High School Reunion' was directed by David Mirkin, who also wrote 'The Simpsons Movie'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Elizabeth Banks star in The Next Three Days?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote The Next Three Days?",
                "answer": "Guillaume Lemans"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Elizabeth Banks star in a movie written by Guillaume Lemans?",
            "answer": "Yes, Elizabeth Banks starred in The Next Three Days, which was written by Guillaume Lemans."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who has tags 'Too Late the Hero'?",
                "answer": "Cliff Robertson"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in 'Too Late the Hero'?",
                "answer": "Harry Andrews"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in 'A Circle of Deception'?",
                "answer": "Harry Andrews"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was 'Too Late the Hero' released?",
                "answer": "1960"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was 'Visit to a Small Planet' released?",
                "answer": "1960"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actor starred in both 'Too Late the Hero' and 'A Circle of Deception', and which movies were released in the same year as 'A Circle of Deception'?",
            "answer": "Harry Andrews starred in both 'Too Late the Hero' and 'A Circle of Deception'. The movie 'Visit to a Small Planet' was released in the same year as 'A Circle of Deception'. Answer: Harry Andrews, Visit to a Small Planet, A Circle of Deception"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in The Five Man Army?",
                "answer": "Nino Castelnuovo"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was The Five Man Army released?",
                "answer": "1969"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was Don't Drink the Water released?",
                "answer": "1994"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was I Like It Like That released?",
                "answer": "1994"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie starring Nino Castelnuovo was released in the same year as Don't Drink the Water and I Like It Like That?",
            "answer": "The Five Man Army was released in the same year as Don't Drink the Water and I Like It Like That, which is 1994. (Note: This answer is incorrect due to a mistake in the fourth tuple. The correct release year for 'The Five Man Army' is 1969)."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'My Boy' released?",
                "answer": "1921"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'Seven Years Bad Luck' released?",
                "answer": "1921"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which actor starred in the movie 'Seven Years Bad Luck'?",
                "answer": "Max Linder"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "In what year was the actor Max Linder's movie 'Seven Years Bad Luck' released, and what was the release year of 'My Boy'?",
            "answer": "'Seven Years Bad Luck' was released in the same year as 'My Boy', which is 1921."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "What genre is Rashomon tagged as?",
                "answer": "I'm unable to provide the exact genre as it's not specified in the given tuple. However, 'masterpiece' suggests it's a highly-rated movie."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was Rashomon released?",
                "answer": "Rashomon was released in 1950."
            },
            {
                "question": "During which year was Chain Lightning released?",
                "answer": "Chain Lightning was released in 1950."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which actor starred in Chain Lightning?",
                "answer": "Eleanor Parker starred in Chain Lightning."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which actor also starred in Scaramouche?",
                "answer": "Eleanor Parker also starred in Scaramouche."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "In what year was Eleanor Parker's movie Rashomon, tagged as a masterpiece, released and in which movie did she act alongside an actor who starred in Scaramouche that was also released in 1950?",
            "answer": "Rashomon, tagged as a masterpiece, was released in 1950, the same year as Chain Lightning, in which Eleanor Parker starred. Additionally, Eleanor Parker acted alongside actor Mel Ferrer in Scaramouche, which was also released in 1950."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie Watercolors?",
                "answer": "David Oliveras"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which person wrote the movie Watercolors and what other information can be extracted from the knowledge graph?",
            "answer": "The movie Watercolors was written by David Oliveras. Currently, there is no additional information available from the given knowledge graph."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Was Steven Martini involved in the writing of Lymelife?",
                "answer": "Yes, Steven Martini was the writer of Lymelife."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie did Alec Baldwin star in, that was also written by Steven Martini?",
                "answer": "Lymelife"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie It's Complicated, in which Alec Baldwin starred?",
                "answer": "Nancy Meyers"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was written by Nancy Meyers, that was also written by a person who wrote Lymelife?",
                "answer": "I Love Trouble and Lymelife were both written by people who have written movies for Alec Baldwin - Steven Martini wrote Lymelife, and Nancy Meyers wrote I Love Trouble."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actor starred in a movie written by Steven Martini and a movie written by a person who also wrote a movie in which that same actor starred?",
            "answer": "Alec Baldwin starred in Lymelife, which was written by Steven Martini, and It's Complicated, which was written by Nancy Meyers. Nancy Meyers also wrote I Love Trouble."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie Taken?",
                "answer": "Jon Gries and Maggie Grace"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie Taken 2?",
                "answer": "Maggie Grace"
            },
            {
                "question": "What movies has Maggie Grace starred in?",
                "answer": "Taken, Taken 2, and Lockout"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movies have Jon Gries and Maggie Grace both starred in, and what is one of Maggie Grace's notable tags?",
            "answer": "Jon Gries and Maggie Grace both starred in the movie Taken. One of Maggie Grace's notable tags is 'maggie grace' from the movie Taken 2.\nAnswer: Jon Gries and Maggie Grace both starred in the movie Taken. Maggie Grace is also tagged with 'Lockout'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'All This, and Heaven Too'?",
                "answer": "Charles Boyer and Barbara O'Neil"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which actors did 'All This, and Heaven Too' star?",
                "answer": "Charles Boyer and Barbara O'Neil"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actors starred in 'All This, and Heaven Too' along with Charles Boyer?",
            "answer": "Barbara O'Neil"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'I Do'?",
                "answer": "Glenn Gaylord"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie stars Bernadette Lafont?",
                "answer": "I Do"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie did Bernadette Lafont star in, that was released in 1957?",
                "answer": "Les Mistons"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was 'Les Mistons' released, and who directed 'The True Story of Jesse James' which was released in the same year?",
                "answer": "Les Mistons was released in 1957, and Nicholas Ray directed 'The True Story of Jesse James' which was also released in 1957."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Who directed 'I Do', and which movie starring Bernadette Lafont was released in the same year as 'The True Story of Jesse James'?",
            "answer": "Glenn Gaylord directed 'I Do', and Les Mistons, a movie starring Bernadette Lafont, was released in the same year as 'The True Story of Jesse James' which is 1957."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Ex Drummer'?",
                "answer": "Koen Mortier and Herman Brusselmans"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movies were written by Herman Brusselmans?",
                "answer": "'Ex Drummer'"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which authors are associated with the movie 'Ex Drummer'?",
                "answer": "Koen Mortier and Herman Brusselmans"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Who are the authors associated with the movie 'Ex Drummer' and what is the title of the movie written by Herman Brusselmans?",
            "answer": "The authors associated with the movie 'Ex Drummer' are Koen Mortier and Herman Brusselmans, and the title of the movie written by Herman Brusselmans is 'Ex Drummer'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Seymour Hicks star in the movie Always Tell Your Wife?",
                "answer": "Yes, Seymour Hicks starred in the movie Always Tell Your Wife."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie Always Tell Your Wife released?",
                "answer": "The movie Always Tell Your Wife was released in the year 1914."
            },
            {
                "question": "Was the movie The Perils of Pauline released in the same year as Always Tell Your Wife?",
                "answer": "Yes, the movie The Perils of Pauline was released in the same year as Always Tell Your Wife, which is 1914."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Pat Boone star in the movie The Perils of Pauline?",
                "answer": "No, Pat Boone did not star in the movie The Perils of Pauline. Pat Boone starred in the movie Journey to the Center of the Earth."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Seymour Hicks and Pat Boone both star in any of the movies released in 1914, which are Always Tell Your Wife and The Perils of Pauline?",
            "answer": "No, Seymour Hicks and Pat Boone did not both star in any of the movies released in 1914. While Seymour Hicks starred in Always Tell Your Wife, Pat Boone starred in Journey to the Center of the Earth."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Monsters, Inc.'?",
                "answer": "Pete Docter"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Up'?",
                "answer": "Pete Docter"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie has the tag 'michael giacchino'?",
                "answer": "Up"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie has the tag 'The Incredibles'?",
                "answer": "The Incredibles"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie has the tag 'bd-r'?",
                "answer": "The Incredibles"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was written by Pete Docter and has the tag 'bd-r'?",
            "answer": "The Incredibles\nAnswer: The Incredibles was written by Pete Docter and has the tag 'bd-r'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote Brenda Starr?",
                "answer": "Dale Messick"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the genre of Brenda Starr?",
                "answer": "Adventure"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the genre of The Man in the Iron Mask?",
                "answer": "Adventure"
            },
            {
                "question": "What are the tags of The Man in the Iron Mask?",
                "answer": "adventure"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the complex question combining all tuples?",
                "answer": "Who wrote the Adventure genre that is also tagged as 'The Man Who Would Be King' and 'adventure' in the movie The Man in the Iron Mask?\nAnswer: Dale Messick"
            }
        ],
        "complex": null
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Cybill Shepherd star in the movie Hard Luck?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Wesley Snipes star in the movie White Men Can't Jump?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie Sumo Do, Sumo Don't released?",
                "answer": "1992."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Cybill Shepherd star in a movie with Wesley Snipes that was released in the same year as Sumo Do, Sumo Don't?",
            "answer": "No, Cybill Shepherd starred in the movie \"Hard Luck\" with Wesley Snipes, but it was not released in the same year as \"Sumo Do, Sumo Don't\". \"Hard Luck\" was released in a different year."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "What genre is the movie 'The Artist'?",
                "answer": "The Artist is a Drama."
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the genre of 'Doing Time on Maple Drive'?",
                "answer": "Doing Time on Maple Drive is a Drama."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'Doing Time on Maple Drive'?",
                "answer": "Ken Olin"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "What genre of movie was directed by Ken Olin and also includes 'The Artist' as one of its genres?",
            "answer": "Drama, as directed by Ken Olin, includes 'The Artist' as one of its genres, and also includes 'Doing Time on Maple Drive' as another movie of its genre."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Blake Lively star in Savages?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie Savages?",
                "answer": "Michael O'Donoghue"
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Michael O'Donoghue write the movie Scrooged?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Karen Allen star in Scrooged?",
                "answer": "No."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Karen Allen star in Until September?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Blake Lively work with Karen Allen in any movie, either by starring together or through a common writer?",
            "answer": "No, there is no such connection found in the given tuples."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Does the movie 'blackjack' have the tag '21'?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Does the movie '21' have the tag 'true story'?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Does the movie 'true story' have the tag 'Glory Road'?",
                "answer": "No."
            },
            {
                "question": "Does the movie 'Glory Road' have the tag 'jerry bruckheimer'?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Does the movie 'jerry bruckheimer' have the tag 'Pearl Harbor'?",
                "answer": "No."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Does the movie 'blackjack', which is tagged as '21', have a connection to the movie 'Pearl Harbor' through any common tags or producers?",
            "answer": "No, there is no direct or indirect connection found between the movie 'blackjack' and 'Pearl Harbor' through the given tuples."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie In China They Eat Dogs?",
                "answer": "Kim Bodnia"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie In China They Eat Dogs?",
                "answer": "Lasse Spang Olsen"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was starred by Kim Bodnia and directed by Lasse Spang Olsen?",
            "answer": "In China They Eat Dogs"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'Left Behind'?",
                "answer": "Vic Armstrong"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Left Behind'?",
                "answer": "Jerry B. Jenkins"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the genre of the movie 'Die Hard'?",
                "answer": "action"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the sequel to 'Die Hard'?",
                "answer": "Die Hard 2"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was 'Die Hard 2' released?",
                "answer": "1990"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was directed by Vic Armstrong and written by Jerry B. Jenkins?",
            "answer": "Left Behind\n\n[('Die Hard', 'genre', 'action'), ('Die Hard', 'sequel', 'Die Hard 2'), ('Die Hard 2', 'release_year', 1990)]\n\nQuestion: What is the genre of the movie 'Die Hard'?\nAnswer: action\n\nQuestion: What is the sequel to 'Die Hard'?\nAnswer: Die Hard 2\n\nQuestion: In what year was 'Die Hard 2' released?\nAnswer: 1990\n\nComplex: What is the genre of the movie 'Die Hard 2' which is the sequel to 'Die Hard'?\nAnswer: action"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Does the movie 'The Lucky Ones' have a tag related to a soldier?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Is there a tag 'soldier' in the movie 'The Crying Game'?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "What organization is associated with the movie 'The Crying Game'?",
                "answer": "IRA (Irish Republican Army)."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie is related to the organization 'In the Name of the Father' and was released in the year 1993?",
                "answer": "In the Name of the Father."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Does the movie 'The Lucky Ones', released with tags related to a soldier, have a connection to the organization 'In the Name of the Father', which is also linked to the movie 'The Crying Game', and was released in the year 1993?",
            "answer": "Although 'The Lucky Ones' shares a tag with 'The Crying Game' and 'The Crying Game' shares a connection with 'In the Name of the Father' through their linked tags, there is no direct connection between 'The Lucky Ones' and 'In the Name of the Father'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie Magic Man?",
                "answer": "Alexander Nevsky"
            },
            {
                "question": "What genre does the movie Alexander Nevsky belong to?",
                "answer": "Drama"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which genre does the movie Doing Time on Maple Drive belong to?",
                "answer": "Drama"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie Doing Time on Maple Drive?",
                "answer": "Ken Olin"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actor starred in the movie Magic Man, and who directed the movie Doing Time on Maple Drive, which belongs to the same genre as Alexander Nevsky?",
            "answer": "Alexander Nevsky starred in the movie Magic Man, and Ken Olin directed the movie Doing Time on Maple Drive, which belongs to the same genre as Alexander Nevsky, which is Drama."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Thirty Seconds Over Tokyo'?",
                "answer": "Robert Walker"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'See Here, Private Hargrove'?",
                "answer": "Robert Walker"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'See Here, Private Hargrove'?",
                "answer": "Donna Reed"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'They Were Expendable'?",
                "answer": "Donna Reed"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'They Were Expendable'?",
                "answer": "John Wayne"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actors have starred in movies with both Robert Walker and Donna Reed?",
            "answer": "John Wayne and Robert Walker have both starred in movies with Donna Reed (They Were Expendable). However, since Robert Walker passed away in 1951 and Donna Reed in 1986, they did not have any movies together after Robert Walker's death."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Boot Camp'?",
                "answer": "Peter Stormare"
            },
            {
                "question": "In which movie did Peter Stormare star?",
                "answer": "Small Town Murder Songs"
            },
            {
                "question": "When was the movie 'Small Town Murder Songs' released?",
                "answer": "2010"
            },
            {
                "question": "In which year was the movie 'Father of Invention' released?",
                "answer": "2010"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the genre of the movie 'Father of Invention'?",
                "answer": "Drama"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actor starred in the movie 'Boot Camp', released in the same year as 'Small Town Murder Songs', a movie that Peter Stormare starred in, and the genre of 'Father of Invention' is Drama?",
            "answer": "Peter Stormare"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Mathew St. Patrick star in Alien Raiders?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Rockmond Dunbar star in Alien Raiders?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Mathew St. Patrick and Rockmond Dunbar both star in Alien Raiders?",
            "answer": "Yes, both Mathew St. Patrick and Rockmond Dunbar starred in Alien Raiders."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Spy Kids'?",
                "answer": "Robert Rodriguez"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Four Rooms'?",
                "answer": "Robert Rodriguez, Alexandre Rockwell"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'In the Soup'?",
                "answer": "Alexandre Rockwell"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie did Steve Buscemi star in?",
                "answer": "In the Soup"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was written by the person who also wrote the movie 'Four Rooms' and was starred in by the actor who starred in 'In the Soup'?",
            "answer": "Spy Kids (written by Robert Rodriguez and starred in by Steve Buscemi)"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "What genre is the movie 'The Three Caballeros'?",
                "answer": "The movie 'The Three Caballeros' has the genre 'Animation'."
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the genre of the movie 'Meet the Robinsons'?",
                "answer": "The genre of the movie 'Meet the Robinsons' is 'Animation'."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which actor starred in the movie 'Meet the Robinsons'?",
                "answer": "Angela Bassett starred in the movie 'Meet the Robinsons'."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which actor starred in the movie 'Boyz n the Hood'?",
                "answer": "Angela Bassett starred in the movie 'Boyz n the Hood'."
            },
            {
                "question": "What tags does the movie 'Boyz n the Hood' have?",
                "answer": "The movie 'Boyz n the Hood' has the tag 'laurence fishburne'."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actor starred in the movie 'Meet the Robinsons' and what genre is associated with the movies 'The Three Caballeros' and 'Meet the Robinsons' as well as the tag related to the movie 'Boyz n the Hood'?",
            "answer": "Angela Bassett starred in the movie 'Meet the Robinsons' and the genres associated with the movies 'The Three Caballeros' and 'Meet the Robinsons' as well as the tag related to the movie 'Boyz n the Hood' are 'Animation' and 'laurence fishburne'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Mississippi Grind'?",
                "answer": "Ryan Reynolds"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Chaos Theory'?",
                "answer": "Ryan Reynolds"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Chaos Theory'?",
                "answer": "Daniel Taplitz"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Commandments'?",
                "answer": "Daniel Taplitz"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Commandments'?",
                "answer": "Anthony LaPaglia"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actor, starred in the movie 'Mississippi Grind' and also appeared in a movie written by Daniel Taplitz, who also wrote the movie 'Commandments'?",
            "answer": "Ryan Reynolds"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Guy Mitchell star in the movie Red Garters?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Rosemary Clooney star in the movie Red Garters?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Rosemary Clooney star in the movie White Christmas?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Does the movie White Christmas have the tag vistavision?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Does the movie The Ten Commandments have the tag vistavision?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Guy Mitchell and Rosemary Clooney both star in the movie White Christmas, which has the tag vistavision that is also shared by the movie The Ten Commandments?",
            "answer": "Yes."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Public Access'?",
                "answer": "Christopher McQuarrie"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was written by 'Bryan Singer'?",
                "answer": "Superman Returns"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is tagged with 'bryan singer' in the movie 'Superman Returns'?",
                "answer": "The tag for 'bryan singer' in the movie 'Superman Returns' is 'bryan singer'."
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the connection between 'Christopher McQuarrie', 'Public Access', 'Bryan Singer', and 'Superman Returns'?",
                "answer": "Christopher McQuarrie wrote 'Public Access', which was also written by Bryan Singer who also wrote 'Superman Returns'."
            }
        ],
        "complex": null
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Sergi L\u00f3pez star in the movie Leaving?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Kristin Scott Thomas star in the movie Man to Man?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was written by R\u00e9gis Wargnier?",
                "answer": "Man to Man."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was written by R\u00e9gis Wargnier and stars both Sergi L\u00f3pez and Kristin Scott Thomas?",
            "answer": "There is no such movie in the given tuples. Sergi L\u00f3pez starred in \"Leaving\" which was not written by R\u00e9gis Wargnier, and Kristin Scott Thomas starred in \"Man to Man\" which was written by R\u00e9gis Wargnier but there's no information about Sergi L\u00f3pez starring in it."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "In what year was \"The Pleasure Garden\" released?",
                "answer": "1925"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was \"Seven Chances\" released?",
                "answer": "1925"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which actress starred in \"Seven Chances\"?",
                "answer": "Ruth Dwyer"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "In what year were both \"The Pleasure Garden\" and \"Seven Chances\" released, and which actress starred in \"Seven Chances\"?",
            "answer": "Both \"The Pleasure Garden\" and \"Seven Chances\" were released in the year 1925, and Ruth Dwyer starred in \"Seven Chances\"."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie C\u00e9sar released?",
                "answer": "1936"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie Three Smart Girls released?",
                "answer": "1936"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie Three Smart Girls?",
                "answer": "Henry Koster"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie Three Smart Girls Grow Up?",
                "answer": "Henry Koster"
            },
            {
                "question": "Is there any connection between Henry Koster and the movie Three Smart Girls Grow Up?",
                "answer": "Yes, Henry Koster directed the movie Three Smart Girls Grow Up."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "In what year was the movie Three Smart Girls Grow Up directed by Henry Koster released and what other movie of his has the same tag?",
            "answer": "The movie Three Smart Girls Grow Up, directed by Henry Koster, was released in 1936 and the movie C\u00e9sar, released in 1936, has the same tag 'henry koster'. Answer: The movie Three Smart Girls Grow Up, directed by Henry Koster, was released in 1936 and the movie Three Smart Girls, directed by Henry Koster in 1936, has the same tag 'henry koster'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Is 'The Lady Eve' part of the national film registry?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Is the national film registry associated with the movie 'Swing Time'?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the release year of 'Swing Time'?",
                "answer": "1936."
            },
            {
                "question": "Was the movie 'Three Smart Girls' released in 1936?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed 'Three Smart Girls'?",
                "answer": "Henry Koster."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Is 'The Lady Eve' part of the national film registry, along with 'Swing Time' and 'Three Smart Girls', all of which are connected by their shared release year of 1936, and directed by Henry Koster?",
            "answer": "No, 'The Lady Eve' and 'Swing Time' are part of the national film registry, but 'Three Smart Girls' was released in 1936 and directed by Henry Koster."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie Roustabout?",
                "answer": "Allan Weiss"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was directed by John Rich?",
                "answer": "Roustabout"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was directed by the same person who directed Roustabout?",
                "answer": "Wives and Lovers"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the release year of Wives and Lovers?",
                "answer": "1963"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the release year of a movie that was released in the same year as Wives and Lovers and the title of that movie?",
                "answer": "A Child Is Waiting"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was written by Allan Weiss and directed by John Rich, and what is the release year of another movie that was released in the same year as the movie directed by John Rich?",
            "answer": "Roustabout was written by Allan Weiss and directed by John Rich, and the release year of another movie that was released in the same year as Roustabout is 1963. Answer to the second part of the complex question can be any movie from the input tuples that has a release year of 1963, in this case it is 'A Child Is Waiting'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie Wreck-It Ralph?",
                "answer": "Jim Reardon"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was starred by John C. Reilly?",
                "answer": "Wreck-It Ralph"
            },
            {
                "question": "In which movie did John C. Reilly act?",
                "answer": "Carnage"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie Carnage?",
                "answer": "Roman Polanski"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie Bitter Moon?",
                "answer": "Roman Polanski"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was written by Jim Reardon and starred by John C. Reilly, who also acted in another movie written by the same writer of Bitter Moon?",
            "answer": "Wreck-It Ralph and Carnage. The writer of Bitter Moon is Roman Polanski, and he also wrote Carnage in which John C. Reilly acted."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Kitten Natividad star in Beneath the Valley of the Ultra-Vixens?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote Beneath the Valley of the Ultra-Vixens?",
                "answer": "Russ Meyer"
            },
            {
                "question": "What movie was written by Russ Meyer in the year 1976?",
                "answer": "Up!"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was released in the same year as Up! and Two-Minute Warning?",
                "answer": "Up! and Two-Minute Warning were both released in the year 1976."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Kitten Natividad star in a movie written by Russ Meyer, who also wrote the 1976 movie Up!?",
            "answer": "Yes, Kitten Natividad starred in Beneath the Valley of the Ultra-Vixens, which was written by Russ Meyer, the same person who wrote Up! in 1976."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Was 'Point Blank' written by Donald E. Westlake?",
                "answer": "Yes"
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Fred Cavay\u00e9 write \"What's the Worst That Could Happen?\"?",
                "answer": "No, Donald E. Westlake wrote \"What's the Worst That Could Happen?\""
            },
            {
                "question": "In which movie did John Leguizamo star?",
                "answer": "Titan A.E."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Who wrote 'Point Blank', and did that writer also write \"What's the Worst That Could Happen?\", and did John Leguizamo star in that movie?",
            "answer": "'Point Blank' was written by Donald E. Westlake, and yes, he also wrote \"What's the Worst That Could Happen?\". However, John Leguizamo starred in Titan A.E., not in \"What's the Worst That Could Happen?\""
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'The Witnesses'?",
                "answer": "Andr\u00e9 T\u00e9chin\u00e9"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'The Girl on the Train'?",
                "answer": "Larry Brand"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movies were written by a person who also wrote a movie written by someone who wrote 'The Girl on the Train'?",
            "answer": "The Witnesses was written by Andr\u00e9 T\u00e9chin\u00e9, who also wrote 'The Girl on the Train'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Anne of the Thousand Days'?",
                "answer": "John Hale"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the language of the movie 'Anne of the Thousand Days'?",
                "answer": "English"
            },
            {
                "question": "What language is the movie 'Map of the Human Heart' in?",
                "answer": "English"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which actor starred in the movie 'Map of the Human Heart' and the language of 'Anne of the Thousand Days' is the same as the language of 'Map of the Human Heart'?",
                "answer": "Robert Joamie\n\nComplex"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Anne of the Thousand Days', which was released in English, and which actor starred in the movie 'Map of the Human Heart', which was also released in English?",
                "answer": "John Hale, Robert Joamie"
            }
        ],
        "complex": null
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who directed 'What Ever Happened to Aunt Alice?'?",
                "answer": "Lee H. Katzin"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed 'This Woman Is Dangerous'?",
                "answer": "Bernard Girard"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was written by Bernard Girard?",
                "answer": "'This Woman Is Dangerous'"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which actor starred in 'This Woman Is Dangerous'?",
                "answer": "David Brian"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which actor starred in 'Intruder in the Dust'?",
                "answer": "David Brian"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actor, known for their role in 'Intruder in the Dust', also starred in a movie written by the director of 'What Ever Happened to Aunt Alice?'?",
            "answer": "David Brian"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'The Great Northfield Minnesota Raid'?",
                "answer": "Cliff Robertson"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'The Honey Pot'?",
                "answer": "Rex Harrison"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Sidewalks of London'?",
                "answer": "Vivien Leigh"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actor starred in the movies 'The Great Northfield Minnesota Raid', 'The Honey Pot', 'Sidewalks of London' and also 'Sidewalks of London' starred Vivien Leigh?",
            "answer": "Cliff Robertson starred in the movie 'The Great Northfield Minnesota Raid' and Rex Harrison starred in the movie 'The Honey Pot', while 'Sidewalks of London' starred both Rex Harrison and Vivien Leigh."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'The Gorgeous Hussy'?",
                "answer": "Ainsworth Morgan"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'The Gorgeous Hussy' released?",
                "answer": "1936"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'Three Smart Girls' released?",
                "answer": "1936"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'Three Smart Girls'?",
                "answer": "Henry Koster"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'Three Smart Girls Grow Up'?",
                "answer": "Henry Koster"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Who directed the movie 'Three Smart Girls Grow Up' and also wrote the movie 'The Gorgeous Hussy' that was released in the same year as 'Three Smart Girls'?",
            "answer": "Henry Koster and Ainsworth Morgan"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'She's Gotta Have It'?",
                "answer": "Tracy Camilla Johns and John Canada Terrell"
            },
            {
                "question": "In which movie did Tracy Camilla Johns star?",
                "answer": "She's Gotta Have It"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who is the co-star of Tracy Camilla Johns in 'She's Gotta Have It'?",
                "answer": "John Canada Terrell"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie features both Tracy Camilla Johns and John Canada Terrell as actors?",
            "answer": "She's Gotta Have It"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Virginia Field star in Think Fast, Mr. Moto?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was Think Fast, Mr. Moto released?",
                "answer": "1937."
            },
            {
                "question": "Was Stanley Ridges a part of any 1937 release?",
                "answer": "Yes, Internes Can't Take Money."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Stanley Ridges star in The Suspect and was he also a part of a 1937 release that featured Virginia Field?",
                "answer": "Yes.\n\nComplex"
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Virginia Field star in Think Fast, Mr. Moto which was released in 1937, and did Stanley Ridges star in The Suspect and was he also a part of a 1937 release that featured Virginia Field?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            }
        ],
        "complex": null
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Does 'Blazing Saddles' have the tag 'satire'?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Does 'Wet Hot American Summer' have the tag 'satirical'?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did 'David Hyde Pierce' star in 'The Mating Habits of the Earthbound Human'?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Does 'Blazing Saddles', which has the tag 'satire', have anything in common with 'The Mating Habits of the Earthbound Human', in which 'David Hyde Pierce' starred, and also shares the tag 'satire'?",
            "answer": "Both 'Blazing Saddles' and 'The Mating Habits of the Earthbound Human' share the tag 'satire'. Additionally, 'David Hyde Pierce' starred in both 'Wet Hot American Summer', which has the tag 'satirical', and 'The Mating Habits of the Earthbound Human'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Blutzbr\u00fcdaz'?",
                "answer": "\u00d6zg\u00fcr Yildirim"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which person is responsible for writing the movie 'Blutzbr\u00fcdaz'?",
            "answer": "\u00d6zg\u00fcr Yildirim is responsible for writing the movie 'Blutzbr\u00fcdaz'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'The Tree'?",
                "answer": "Charlotte Gainsbourg"
            },
            {
                "question": "In which movie did Charlotte Gainsbourg star?",
                "answer": "The Science of Sleep"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the language of 'The Science of Sleep'?",
                "answer": "French"
            },
            {
                "question": "In which language is the movie 'Two Men in Manhattan' made?",
                "answer": "French"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the genre of 'Two Men in Manhattan'?",
                "answer": "Crime"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actress starred in 'The Tree' and appeared in a French crime movie along with another French-language film?",
            "answer": "Charlotte Gainsbourg (starred in 'The Tree', appeared in French movie 'The Science of Sleep' which is a different film from French crime movie 'Two Men in Manhattan')"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Last Action Hero'?",
                "answer": "Charles Dance"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Pascali's Island'?",
                "answer": "Charles Dance"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the book 'Pascali's Island'?",
                "answer": "Barry Unsworth"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the book 'The Reckoning'?",
                "answer": "Barry Unsworth"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the book 'The Reckoning' that was also written by John V. Soto?",
                "answer": "This is not accurate information, as John V. Soto is a film director and not an author."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actor starred in 'Last Action Hero', and whose book 'The Reckoning' was also written by a film director named John V. Soto, and was based on a book previously written by an author who also wrote 'Pascali's Island'?",
            "answer": "Charles Dance, but the information about 'The Reckoning' being written by John V. Soto is incorrect. The author who wrote 'The Reckoning' also wrote 'Pascali's Island', which is Barry Unsworth."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Does the movie 'The Friends of Eddie Coyle' have the tag 'criterion'?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Does the tag 'criterion' have the tag 'Harold and Maude'?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did the actor 'Bud Cort' star in the movie 'Harold and Maude'?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did the actor 'Bud Cort' star in the movie 'Electric Dreams'?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did the actor 'Virginia Madsen' star in the movie 'Electric Dreams'?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie that has the tag 'criterion' did the actor 'Bud Cort' star in, that also starred the actor 'Virginia Madsen' in the movie 'Electric Dreams'?",
            "answer": "The movie 'Harold and Maude' has the tag 'criterion', and the actor 'Bud Cort' starred in it, and it also stars the actor 'Virginia Madsen' who starred in the movie 'Electric Dreams'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Does the movie 'Oh, Susanna!' have the genre 'Western'?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Does the genre 'Western' apply to the movie 'Django Unchained'?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did the actor 'Kerry Washington' star in the movie 'Django Unchained'?",
                "answer": "No."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did the actor 'Kerry Washington' star in the movie 'She Hate Me'?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "What year was the movie 'She Hate Me' released?",
                "answer": "2004."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did the actor 'Kerry Washington', who starred in the movie 'She Hate Me' which was released in 2004, appear in the Western genred movie 'Django Unchained' or its genre 'Western'?",
            "answer": "No, 'Kerry Washington' did not star in 'Django Unchained', but she did appear in the 'Western' genre movie 'Oh, Susanna!'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Sean Harris star in Outlaw?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Rupert Friend star in The Outlaw?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Rupert Friend star in Mrs. Palfrey at the Claremont?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote Mrs. Palfrey at the Claremont?",
                "answer": "Dan Ireland"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed Living Proof?",
                "answer": "Dan Ireland"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Sean Harris star in a movie directed by the same person who wrote Mrs. Palfrey at the Claremont?",
            "answer": "The knowledge graph does not provide enough information to definitively answer this question."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Does Josh Trank have any tags related to the movie 'Chronicle'?",
                "answer": "Yes, Josh Trank has the tag 'Chronicle' related to the movie 'Chronicle'."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Chronicle'?",
                "answer": "The movie 'Chronicle' was written by Josh Trank."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Based on the given information, can you tell me who is the director of 'Chronicle' and what movie was written by Josh Trank?",
            "answer": "Yes, Josh Trank is the director of the movie 'Chronicle' and he also wrote the movie 'Chronicle'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote \"Mr. Magorium's Wonder Emporium\"?",
                "answer": "Zach Helm"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which person wrote \"Mr. Magorium's Wonder Emporium\" and can you provide the title of this movie?",
            "answer": "Zach Helm wrote \"Mr. Magorium's Wonder Emporium\"."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "What genre is 'The Sea Hawk'?",
                "answer": "The Sea Hawk has tags of 'rousing'."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed 'The Sea Hawk'?",
                "answer": "'The Sea Hawk' was directed by 'Frank Lloyd'."
            },
            {
                "question": "What film was directed by 'Frank Lloyd' and has the tag 'frank lloyd'?",
                "answer": "'Cavalcade' was directed by 'Frank Lloyd' and has the tag 'frank lloyd'."
            },
            {
                "question": "What other film was directed by 'Frank Lloyd'?",
                "answer": "'Frank Lloyd' also directed 'Mutiny on the Bounty'."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "What genre is 'Mutiny on the Bounty' and who directed it and what other film has the same director that has tags of the director's name?",
            "answer": "'Mutiny on the Bounty' has the genre 'rousing' and it was directed by 'Frank Lloyd' who also directed 'Cavalcade' which has tags of 'frank lloyd'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'Liliom' released?",
                "answer": "1934"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'Of Human Bondage' released?",
                "answer": "1934"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'Of Human Bondage'?",
                "answer": "John Cromwell"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'I Dream Too Much'?",
                "answer": "John Cromwell"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the release year of 'I Dream Too Much'?",
                "answer": "1935"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "In what year was the movie 'Liliom' released and who directed the movies 'Of Human Bondage' and 'I Dream Too Much'?",
            "answer": "The movie 'Liliom' was released in 1934 and John Cromwell directed both 'Of Human Bondage' and 'I Dream Too Much'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'Sparrows' released?",
                "answer": "1926"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'Tell It to the Marines' released?",
                "answer": "1926"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which actor starred in 'Tell It to the Marines'?",
                "answer": "William Haines"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which actor starred in 'Are You Listening?'?",
                "answer": "William Haines"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'Are You Listening?' released, and which actor starred in both 'Tell It to the Marines' and 'Are You Listening?'?",
                "answer": "The movie 'Are You Listening?' was released in 1932, and William Haines starred in both 'Tell It to the Marines' and 'Are You Listening?'."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "In what year were the movies 'Sparrows' and 'Are You Listening?' released, and which actor starred in all three movies - 'Tell It to the Marines', 'Sparrows', and 'Are You Listening?'?",
            "answer": "The movie 'Sparrows' was released in 1926, and the movie 'Are You Listening?' was released in 1932. William Haines starred in all three movies - 'Tell It to the Marines', 'Sparrows', and 'Are You Listening?'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Devil's Knot'?",
                "answer": "Mara Leveritt"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was starred by Alessandro Nivola?",
                "answer": "The Devil's Knot"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie did Alessandro Nivola and Phil Morrison both work on?",
                "answer": "The movie 'Junebug' was starred by Alessandro Nivola and directed by Phil Morrison.\n\nComplex"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie starred by Alessandro Nivola and directed by the same director as the movie 'All Is Bright'?",
                "answer": "Mara Leveritt, who wrote 'Devil's Knot', a movie starring Alessandro Nivola, was directed by Phil Morrison, who also directed 'All Is Bright'."
            }
        ],
        "complex": null
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie Letters to Santa?",
                "answer": "Mitja Okorn"
            },
            {
                "question": "What language is the movie Letters to Santa in?",
                "answer": "Polish"
            },
            {
                "question": "What language is the movie 300 Miles to Heaven in?",
                "answer": "Polish"
            },
            {
                "question": "What genre is the movie 300 Miles to Heaven?",
                "answer": "Drama"
            },
            {
                "question": "What genre is the movie Doing Time on Maple Drive?",
                "answer": "Drama"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie directed by Mitja Okorn is in Polish and shares the same genre as a movie called Doing Time on Maple Drive?",
            "answer": "Letters to Santa and 300 Miles to Heaven are both in Polish, but only 300 Miles to Heaven shares the same genre (Drama) as Doing Time on Maple Drive."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Knock on Wood'?",
                "answer": "Mai Zetterling"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'The Girls'?",
                "answer": "Mai Zetterling"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'The Girls'?",
                "answer": "Gunnel Lindblom"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'The Silence'?",
                "answer": "Gunnel Lindblom"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'The Silence'?",
                "answer": "Jan Costin Wagner"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actor starred in 'Knock on Wood' and also appeared in a movie written by the same person who wrote 'The Silence'?",
            "answer": "Mai Zetterling starred in 'Knock on Wood' and also appeared in 'The Girls', which was written by Mai Zetterling, the same person who wrote 'The Silence'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Queen of Blood'?",
                "answer": "Dennis Hopper"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Alpha and Omega'?",
                "answer": "Dennis Hopper"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Alpha and Omega'?",
                "answer": "Steve Moore"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actor starred in the movie 'Queen of Blood' and also acted in a movie written by Steve Moore?",
            "answer": "Dennis Hopper starred in the movie 'Queen of Blood' and also acted in the movie 'Alpha and Omega', which was written by Steve Moore."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'Center Stage'?",
                "answer": "Stanley Kwan"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'Lan Yu'?",
                "answer": "Stanley Kwan"
            },
            {
                "question": "What are the tags for the movie 'Lan Yu'?",
                "answer": "Stanley Kwan"
            },
            {
                "question": "What are the tags for the director 'Stanley Kwan'?",
                "answer": "Rouge, stanley kwan"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Who directed the movie 'Center Stage' and what are the tags for the movies directed by him and also tagged with 'stanley kwan'?",
            "answer": "Stanley Kwan directed the movie 'Center Stage'. The other movie directed by him and also tagged with 'stanley kwan' is 'Lan Yu'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Kiss the Bride'?",
                "answer": "Philipp Karner"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'Kiss the Bride'?",
                "answer": "C. Jay Cox"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Latter Days'?",
                "answer": "C. Jay Cox"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Latter Days'?",
                "answer": "Wes Ramsey"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was directed by the person who wrote 'Latter Days' and in which movie did that writer's star actor appear?",
            "answer": "C. Jay Cox directed the movie 'Kiss the Bride' and Wes Ramsey, who is a star actor in one of Cox's movies ('Latter Days'), appeared in it."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Does Kevin McKidd have any tags related to the movie Trainspotting?",
                "answer": "Yes, Kevin McKidd has the tag Trainspotting."
            },
            {
                "question": "Does the movie Trainspotting have any tags related to Robert Carlyle?",
                "answer": "Yes, the movie Trainspotting has the tag Robert Carlyle."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Robert Carlyle star in the movie Flood?",
                "answer": "Yes, Robert Carlyle starred in the movie Flood."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Robert Carlyle star in the movie Go Now?",
                "answer": "Yes, Robert Carlyle starred in the movie Go Now."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movies have tags related to both Kevin McKidd and Robert Carlyle?",
            "answer": "The movie Trainspotting has tags related to both Kevin McKidd and Robert Carlyle.\nAnswer: Note: The provided tuples only show a direct relation between Kevin McKidd and Trainspotting, and between Robert Carlyle and Trainspotting. However, based on the given information, there is no direct relation between Kevin McKidd and Robert Carlyle."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'Million Dollar Legs'?",
                "answer": "Edward F. Cline"
            },
            {
                "question": "What genre is the movie 'My Little Chickadee' associated with?",
                "answer": "The genre of 'My Little Chickadee' is not explicitly mentioned, but Edward F. Cline, who directed 'Million Dollar Legs', also directed 'My Little Chickadee'. Based on the available information, we cannot infer the genre of 'My Little Chickadee'."
            },
            {
                "question": "Does the movie 'Million Dollar Legs' have any tags related to Edward F. Cline?",
                "answer": "Yes, 'Million Dollar Legs' has the tag 'edward f. cline' as Edward F. Cline directed this movie."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie directed by Edward F. Cline shares a genre with the movie 'Django Unchained'?",
            "answer": "Based on the available information, we cannot directly associate a movie directed by Edward F. Cline with the genre of 'Django Unchained'. However, since the genre of 'Django Unchained' is 'Western' and 'My Little Chickadee' has the director tag 'edward f. cline', it can be inferred that 'My Little Chickadee' shares a genre with 'Django Unchained' indirectly through their shared director."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Tracy Coogan star in Zombie Honeymoon?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Graham Sibley star in Zombie Honeymoon?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Tracy Coogan and Graham Sibley both star in Zombie Honeymoon?",
            "answer": "Yes, Tracy Coogan and Graham Sibley both starred in the movie Zombie Honeymoon."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'Gardens of Stone'?",
                "answer": "Francis Ford Coppola"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'Supernova'?",
                "answer": "Francis Ford Coppola"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which tags are associated with the movie 'Supernova'?",
                "answer": "Francis Ford Coppola"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which tags are associated with Francis Ford Coppola?",
                "answer": "Youth Without Youth"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'Youth Without Youth' released?",
                "answer": "2007"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie directed by Francis Ford Coppola, released in or after 2007, has the tag 'francis ford coppola' associated with it?",
            "answer": "The movie 'Supernova' directed by Francis Ford Coppola, associated with the tag 'francis ford coppola', was released in or after 2007. However, there is no information provided about the release year of 'Supernova', so it cannot be confirmed if it was released in or after 2007."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Joanna Lumley star in Innocent Lies?",
                "answer": "Yes, Joanna Lumley starred in Innocent Lies."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Adrian Dunbar star in Widows' Peak?",
                "answer": "Yes, Adrian Dunbar starred in Widows' Peak."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed Widows' Peak?",
                "answer": "John Irvin"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed When Trumpets Fade?",
                "answer": "John Irvin"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Joanna Lumley and Adrian Dunbar both star in movies directed by John Irvin?",
            "answer": "Yes, Joanna Lumley starred in Innocent Lies and Adrian Dunbar starred in Widows' Peak. Both movies were directed by John Irvin."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "What movies does Audrey Hepburn have a tag in?",
                "answer": "How to Steal a Million and Wait Until Dark"
            },
            {
                "question": "What are the tags for the movie How to Steal a Million?",
                "answer": "The tags for the movie How to Steal a Million are Audrey Hepburn and audrey"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie Wait Until Dark?",
                "answer": "Robert Carrington"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "What movies does Audrey Hepburn have a tag in, and who wrote the movie Wait Until Dark?",
            "answer": "Audrey Hepburn has a tag in the movies How to Steal a Million and Wait Until Dark, and the movie Wait Until Dark was written by Robert Carrington."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "In what year was 'The Big Empty' released?",
                "answer": "2003"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was 'How to Lose a Guy in 10 Days' released?",
                "answer": "2003"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which actor starred in 'How to Lose a Guy in 10 Days'?",
                "answer": "Kate Hudson"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie stars Kate Hudson and has the tag 'kate hudson'?",
                "answer": "Fool's Gold"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "In what year was 'How to Lose a Guy in 10 Days', starring the same actor (Kate Hudson) who also starred in 'Fool's Gold', released?",
            "answer": "2003"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Does The Counterfeiters have any tags related to a concentration camp?",
                "answer": "Yes, The Counterfeiters has a tag of 'concentration camp'."
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the genre of The Counterfeiters?",
                "answer": "The Counterfeiters is a Drama genre movie."
            },
            {
                "question": "What genre is Drama?",
                "answer": "Drama is a genre of Doing Time on Maple Drive."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed Doing Time on Maple Drive?",
                "answer": "Doing Time on Maple Drive was directed by Ken Olin."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Is there a movie directed by Ken Olin that is related to a concentration camp through its tags?",
            "answer": "No, there is no movie directed by Ken Olin that is related to a concentration camp through its tags."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie Kambakkht Ishq?",
                "answer": "Sylvester Stallone"
            },
            {
                "question": "In which movie did Sylvester Stallone star?",
                "answer": "Nighthawks"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie has the tag 'sylvester stallone'?",
                "answer": "Nighthawks"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie has the tag 'Driven'?",
                "answer": "Driven"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'Driven' which has the tag 'sylvester stallone'?",
                "answer": "Renny Harlin"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was directed by Renny Harlin and starred Sylvester Stallone, who was also a star in the movie Kambakkht Ishq that has the tag 'sylvester stallone'?",
            "answer": "Driven"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'The Valet'?",
                "answer": "Kristin Scott Thomas"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Man to Man'?",
                "answer": "Kristin Scott Thomas"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Man to Man'?",
                "answer": "R\u00e9gis Wargnier"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Indochine'?",
                "answer": "R\u00e9gis Wargnier"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'Indochine' released?",
                "answer": "1992"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie starring Kristin Scott Thomas was written by R\u00e9gis Wargnier and released in 1992?",
            "answer": "Indochine"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Finola Hughes star in the movie Staying Alive?",
                "answer": "Yes, Finola Hughes starred in the movie Staying Alive."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Steve Inwood star in the movie Staying Alive?",
                "answer": "Yes, Steve Inwood starred in the movie Staying Alive."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Finola Hughes and Steve Inwood both star in the same movie, Staying Alive?",
            "answer": "Yes, both Finola Hughes and Steve Inwood starred in the movie Staying Alive."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Boyhood'?",
                "answer": "Patricia Arquette"
            },
            {
                "question": "In which movie did Patricia Arquette star?",
                "answer": "The Badge"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'The Badge'?",
                "answer": "Robby Henson"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was directed by Robby Henson?",
                "answer": "House"
            },
            {
                "question": "What are the tags for the movie 'House'?",
                "answer": "nobuhiko obayashi"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was directed by the person who wrote 'The Badge', where Patricia Arquette starred in both this movie and the movie 'Boyhood' that was tagged by nobuhiko obayashi?",
            "answer": "House"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Does the movie 'Fahrenheit 9/11' have any tags related to 'history'?",
                "answer": "Yes, the movie 'Fahrenheit 9/11' has the tag 'history'."
            },
            {
                "question": "Does the movie 'Mr. Smith Goes to Washington' have any tags related to 'political'?",
                "answer": "Yes, the movie 'Mr. Smith Goes to Washington' has the tag 'political'."
            },
            {
                "question": "Does the movie 'Swing Time' have any tags related to 'national film registry'?",
                "answer": "Yes, the movie 'Swing Time' has the tag 'national film registry'."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Is the movie 'Fahrenheit 9/11', which has the tag 'history', also connected to the 'national film registry' tag through its political themes and the movie 'Mr. Smith Goes to Washington'?",
            "answer": "No, 'Fahrenheit 9/11' is not directly connected to the 'national film registry' tag through 'Mr. Smith Goes to Washington'. However, both 'Fahrenheit 9/11' and 'Mr. Smith Goes to Washington' share the common tag 'political'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Dans Paris'?",
                "answer": "Guy Marchand"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Entre Nous'?",
                "answer": "Guy Marchand"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'Entre Nous' released?",
                "answer": "1983"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'Trading Places' released?",
                "answer": "1983"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie released in 1983 stars Jamie Lee Curtis?",
                "answer": "Trading Places"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actor starred in both 'Dans Paris' and a movie released in the same year as 'Trading Places' that also stars Jamie Lee Curtis?",
            "answer": "Guy Marchand"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'The Perils of Pauline'?",
                "answer": "Paul Panzer and Pat Boone"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Journey to the Center of the Earth'?",
                "answer": "Pat Boone"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'The Perils of Pauline' released?",
                "answer": "I cannot determine the release year of 'The Perils of Pauline' directly from the provided tuples."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'Journey to the Center of the Earth' released?",
                "answer": "2008"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'Fifty Dead Men Walking' released, and who starred in 'Journey to the Center of the Earth'?",
                "answer": "The movie 'Fifty Dead Men Walking' was released in 2008, and Pat Boone starred in 'Journey to the Center of the Earth'."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "In what year were the movies 'The Perils of Pauline' and 'Journey to the Center of the Earth' released, and who starred in both of these films?",
            "answer": "I cannot determine the release year of 'The Perils of Pauline' directly from the provided tuples. However, Pat Boone starred in both 'The Perils of Pauline' and 'Journey to the Center of the Earth', which was released in 2008."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Jeremy Suarez star in Brother Bear 2?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Patrick Dempsey star in Brother Bear 2?",
                "answer": "Yes, he did. However, it's worth noting that he lent his voice to a different character than Jeremy Suarez."
            },
            {
                "question": "What movies has Patrick Dempsey starred in besides Lucky 7?",
                "answer": "Patrick Dempsey also starred in Brother Bear 2."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Jeremy Suarez and Patrick Dempsey both star in Brother Bear 2, and what other movies has Patrick Dempsey been in that are tagged with his name or have romantic themes?",
            "answer": "Yes, Jeremy Suarez and Patrick Dempsey both starred in Brother Bear 2. Additionally, Patrick Dempsey appeared in Lucky 7, and based on the knowledge graph, there is a tag associated with Lucky 7 that includes his name. Another movie associated with Patrick Dempsey is \"Can't Buy Me Love,\" which may have romantic themes."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "What city is tagged in the movie 'Dog Days'?",
                "answer": "Vienna"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Dog Days'?",
                "answer": "Ulrich Seidl"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was written by Ulrich Seidl and has the tag 'ulrich seidl'?",
                "answer": "Import/Export"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was written by the person who also wrote the movie 'Dog Days', and is tagged with the same term as a city tagged in 'Dog Days'?",
            "answer": "Import/Export"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Aaron Goodwin star in Ghost Adventures?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Nick Groff star in Ghost Adventures?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did both Aaron Goodwin and Nick Groff star in Ghost Adventures?",
            "answer": "Yes, they did."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "What movies has Judd Nelson played in?",
                "answer": "From the Hip and Steel"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the tag for the movie The Breakfast Club?",
                "answer": "Judd Nelson"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie stars Shaquille O'Neal?",
                "answer": "Steel"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie, starring Shaquille O'Neal, shares a co-star with The Breakfast Club?",
            "answer": "Steel and The Breakfast Club share the co-star Judd Nelson."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie Sister Act?",
                "answer": "Emile Ardolino"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie Sister Act released?",
                "answer": "1992"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie \"Sumo Do, Sumo Don't\" released?",
                "answer": "1992"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie \"Sumo Do, Sumo Don't\"?",
                "answer": "Masayuki Suo"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie \"I Just Didn't Do It\"?",
                "answer": "Masayuki Suo"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "In what year was the movie Sister Act released, and who wrote the movies \"Sumo Do, Sumo Don't\" and \"I Just Didn't Do It\"?",
            "answer": "The movie Sister Act was released in 1992, and Masayuki Suo wrote the movies \"Sumo Do, Sumo Don't\" and \"I Just Didn't Do It\"."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [],
        "complex": null
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote \"It's Kind of a Funny Story\"?",
                "answer": "Ned Vizzini"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was \"It's Kind of a Funny Story\" released?",
                "answer": "2010"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was \"Father of Invention\" released?",
                "answer": "The relation (2010, 'release_year', 'Father of Invention') does not provide the information on who wrote \"Father of Invention\"."
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the genre of \"Father of Invention\"?",
                "answer": "Drama"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is a drama released in 2010?",
                "answer": "The tuple ('2010', 'release_year', 'Father of Invention') indicates that \"Father of Invention\", a drama, was released in 2010. However, it does not provide information about whether there are other dramas released that year.\n\nAnswer:"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "What is the connection between Ned Vizzini, \"It's Kind of a Funny Story\", \"Father of Invention\", and \"Doing Time on Maple Drive\"?",
            "answer": "Ned Vizzini wrote \"It's Kind of a Funny Story\", which was released in the same year (2010) as \"Father of Invention\". This drama shares a common genre ('Drama') with the movie \"Doing Time on Maple Drive\"."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'Authors Anonymous'?",
                "answer": "Ellie Kanner"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie stars Teri Polo?",
                "answer": "Authors Anonymous"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie stars Paul Gross?",
                "answer": "Aspen Extreme"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Men with Brooms'?",
                "answer": "Paul Gross"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was directed by Ellie Kanner and stars Teri Polo, who also starred in a movie with Paul Gross who in turn starred in 'Men with Brooms'?",
            "answer": "Authors Anonymous and Aspen Extreme"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Big Wednesday'?",
                "answer": "John Milius"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was starred by Gary Busey?",
                "answer": "Big Wednesday"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was Gary Busey and Yancy Butler both in?",
                "answer": "Drop Zone"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Big Wednesday', and which movie was starred by both Gary Busey and Yancy Butler?",
            "answer": "John Milius and Drop Zone, respectively."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Things We Lost in the Fire'?",
                "answer": "Allan Loeb"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which actors starred in the movie 'Things We Lost in the Fire'?",
                "answer": "Benicio Del Toro"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which actors starred in the movie 'The Way of the Gun'?",
                "answer": "Benicio Del Toro"
            },
            {
                "question": "What are the tags for the movie 'The Way of the Gun'?",
                "answer": "benicio del toro"
            },
            {
                "question": "What are the tags for the actor 'benicio del toro'?",
                "answer": "21 Grams"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actors, according to the knowledge graph, have appeared in movies written by Allan Loeb and have the tag '21 Grams' associated with them?",
            "answer": "Benicio Del Toro"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "What genre is 'Another Thin Man' tagged with?",
                "answer": "I cannot provide the exact genre as 'has\\_tags' relation for 'nick and nora charles' indicates it's about the characters, not the movie genre."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was 'Another Thin Man' released?",
                "answer": "'Another Thin Man' was released in the year 1939."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was 'Three Smart Girls Grow Up' released?",
                "answer": "'Three Smart Girls Grow Up' was released in the year 1939."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed 'Three Smart Girls Grow Up'?",
                "answer": "Henry Koster directed 'Three Smart Girls Grow Up'."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed 'Three Smart Girls' and in what year was 'Another Thin Man' released?",
                "answer": "Henry Koster directed 'Three Smart Girls' and 'Another Thin Man' was released in the year 1939.\nAnswer: Complex. Answer: Henry Koster, who directed 'Three Smart Girls', also directed 'Three Smart Girls Grow Up', released in the same year as 'Another Thin Man' - 1939."
            }
        ],
        "complex": null
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Is 'The Son of the Sheik' a part of the national film registry?",
                "answer": "Yes, 'The Son of the Sheik' is a part of the national film registry."
            },
            {
                "question": "Is 'national film registry' associated with 'Swing Time'?",
                "answer": "Yes, the 'national film registry' is associated with 'Swing Time'."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was 'Swing Time' released?",
                "answer": "'Swing Time' was released in the year 1936."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was released in the same year as 'Three Smart Girls'?",
                "answer": "'Swing Time' was released in the same year as 'Three Smart Girls'."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed 'Three Smart Girls' which was released in 1936?",
                "answer": "'Three Smart Girls', which was released in 1936, was directed by Henry Koster."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie directed by Henry Koster in 1936 shares the distinction of being a part of the national film registry along with 'Swing Time'?",
            "answer": "'Three Smart Girls' was directed by Henry Koster in 1936 and shares the distinction of being a part of the national film registry along with 'Swing Time'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Does the movie 'The Bone Collector' have any tags related to 'new york city'?",
                "answer": "Yes, 'The Bone Collector' has the tag 'new york city'."
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the tag related to 'divorce' in the movie 'Definitely, Maybe'?",
                "answer": "The tag related to 'divorce' in the movie 'Definitely, Maybe' is 'divorce'."
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the genre of the movie 'Under the Tuscan Sun'?",
                "answer": "The genre of the movie 'Under the Tuscan Sun' is 'Comedy'."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Can you name a movie that has a connection to 'new york city', and has a theme related to 'divorce', while also being a Comedy?",
            "answer": "The movie 'Definitely, Maybe' has the tag 'new york city', and has a theme related to 'divorce'. However, it is not a Comedy. Unfortunately, I cannot find a movie that meets all the criteria."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'Distant Voices, Still Lives' released?",
                "answer": "1988"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'Stand and Deliver' released?",
                "answer": "1988"
            },
            {
                "question": "What kind of setting does the movie 'Stand and Deliver' have?",
                "answer": "High school"
            },
            {
                "question": "What kind of setting does the movie 'John Tucker Must Die' have?",
                "answer": "High school"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which actor starred in the movie 'John Tucker Must Die'?",
                "answer": "Sophia Bush"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "In what year were the movies 'Distant Voices, Still Lives' and 'Stand and Deliver' released, and which actor starred in the movie 'John Tucker Must Die' that was set in the same environment as these two movies?",
            "answer": "The movies 'Distant Voices, Still Lives' and 'Stand and Deliver' were released in the year 1988, and the actor Sophia Bush starred in the movie 'John Tucker Must Die' which was set in a high school like the other two movies."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'Win a Date with Tad Hamilton!'?",
                "answer": "Robert Luketic"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie '21'?",
                "answer": "Robert Luketic"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the genre of the movie '21'?",
                "answer": "It is a true story"
            },
            {
                "question": "What other movie has the tag 'true story'?",
                "answer": "Glory Road"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who is associated with the movie 'Glory Road'?",
                "answer": "Jerry Bruckheimer"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was directed by Robert Luketic and is also associated with Jerry Bruckheimer through a tag of 'true story'?",
            "answer": "There is no such movie, as Robert Luketic and Jerry Bruckheimer are connected through different movies: '21' and 'Glory Road' respectively."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'Thirst' released?",
                "answer": "1949"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'Always Leave Them Laughing' released?",
                "answer": "1949"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which director helmed the movie 'Always Leave Them Laughing'?",
                "answer": "Roy Del Ruth"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was directed by Roy Del Ruth, who also directed 'The Maltese Falcon'?",
                "answer": "Always Leave Them Laughing"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which director, known for directing 'The Maltese Falcon' and having a movie tagged as 'roy del ruth', released the movies 'Thirst' and 'Always Leave Them Laughing' in the same year as 'The Maltese Falcon'?",
            "answer": "Roy Del Ruth released 'Thirst' and 'Always Leave Them Laughing' in 1949."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Georg'?",
                "answer": "Asta Ots"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was written by Asta Ots?",
            "answer": "Georg"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Does Paul Weitz have a connection to Little Fockers?",
                "answer": "Yes, Paul Weitz has the 'has\\_tags' relation to Little Fockers."
            },
            {
                "question": "What movie is Jessica Alba associated with?",
                "answer": "Jessica Alba is associated with the movie 'Little Fockers'."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which film shares a connection with Jessica Alba?",
                "answer": "Sin City shares a connection with Jessica Alba through the 'has\\_tags' relation."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who is linked to the movie Sin City?",
                "answer": "Clive Owen is linked to the movie Sin City through the 'has\\_tags' relation."
            },
            {
                "question": "Is there a movie related to Clive Owen?",
                "answer": "Yes, The Boys Are Back is related to Clive Owen through the 'has\\_tags' relation."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Who are the people associated with the movies connected to Paul Weitz, Little Fockers, Jessica Alba, Sin City, and The Boys Are Back?",
            "answer": "Paul Weitz is associated with Little Fockers, which is also connected to Jessica Alba who is linked to Sin City, and Sin City shares a connection with Clive Owen who is related to The Boys Are Back."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "What film has the tag 'The Old Lady and the Pigeons'?",
                "answer": "Sylvain Chomet's film 'The Old Lady and the Pigeons'"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the genre of 'The Old Lady and the Pigeons'?",
                "answer": "The genre of 'The Old Lady and the Pigeons' is Short."
            },
            {
                "question": "What location is associated with the genre Short?",
                "answer": "The location associated with the genre Short is H\u00f4tel des Invalides."
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the genre of H\u00f4tel des Invalides?",
                "answer": "The genre of H\u00f4tel des Invalides is Documentary."
            },
            {
                "question": "What film is associated with the genre Documentary?",
                "answer": "The film associated with the genre Documentary is '10 Questions for the Dalai Lama'."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Can you connect Sylvain Chomet's film 'The Old Lady and the Pigeons' to '10 Questions for the Dalai Lama' through genres and locations?",
            "answer": "Yes, 'The Old Lady and the Pigeons' is a Short film by Sylvain Chomet, which is associated with the location H\u00f4tel des Invalides. This location is connected to the Documentary genre, which is then connected to the film '10 Questions for the Dalai Lama'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Querelle'?",
                "answer": "Brad Davis"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Rosalie Goes Shopping'?",
                "answer": "Brad Davis"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Rosalie Goes Shopping' along with Judge Reinhold?",
                "answer": "Rosalie Goes Shopping"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie did Judge Reinhold star in, that is also part of the national film registry?",
                "answer": "Fast Times at Ridgemont High"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie that starred Brad Davis is also connected to a movie that Judge Reinhold starred in, that is part of the national film registry?",
            "answer": "The movies are 'Querelle' and 'Fast Times at Ridgemont High' respectively."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'The Ten'?",
                "answer": "Ken Marino"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie does Ken Marino star in, that has a tag related to him?",
                "answer": "Diggers"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was written by Ken Marino, and who stars in that movie which also has a tag related to Ken Marino?",
            "answer": "The Ten was written by Ken Marino, and he stars in the movie Diggers which also has a tag related to him."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie Ironclad?",
                "answer": "Kate Mara"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie Tadpole?",
                "answer": "Robert Iler"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actor starred in the movies Ironclad, Tadpole, and also was in a movie with Robert Iler?",
            "answer": "Kate Mara starred in the movie Ironclad and Tadpole, and was also in a movie with Robert Iler, who starred in Tadpole."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Was Kario Salem involved in writing The Score?",
                "answer": "Yes, Kario Salem was a writer for The Score."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie starred Angela Bassett?",
                "answer": "The Score starred Angela Bassett."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie did Angela Bassett star in?",
                "answer": "Boyz n the Hood is a movie where Angela Bassett starred."
            },
            {
                "question": "What are the tags for Boyz n the Hood?",
                "answer": "The tags for Boyz n the Hood include laurence fishburne."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie did laurence fishburne appear in and is also tagged with Assault on Precinct 13?",
                "answer": "Assault on Precinct 13 is a movie where laurence fishburne appeared and it shares the tag with Boyz n the Hood."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Who wrote The Score, which movie starred Angela Bassett who also starred in a movie with laurence fishburne who was tagged in Assault on Precinct 13?",
            "answer": "Kario Salem wrote The Score, which movie starred Angela Bassett who also starred in Boyz n the Hood with laurence fishburne who was tagged in Assault on Precinct 13."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie Paperman?",
                "answer": "John Kahrs"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie Paperman released?",
                "answer": "2012"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie How to Make Money Selling Drugs released?",
                "answer": "2012"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie How to Make Money Selling Drugs?",
                "answer": "Susan Sarandon"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie The Great Waldo Pepper?",
                "answer": "Susan Sarandon"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie starring Susan Sarandon was released in the same year as Paperman?",
            "answer": "How to Make Money Selling Drugs"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Was Daniel Fuchs a writer for Love Me or Leave Me?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Isobel Lennart write East Side, West Side?",
                "answer": "Yes, she did."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie starred Van Heflin?",
                "answer": "East Side, West Side"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which writers were involved in the movies where Van Heflin was one of the starred actors?",
                "answer": "Daniel Fuchs, Isobel Lennart."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Who are the writers involved in the movies where Van Heflin starred, and what is the chain of movies connecting Daniel Fuchs and Isobel Lennart through these movies?",
            "answer": "Daniel Fuchs and Isobel Lennart are both writers involved in the movies where Van Heflin starred. The chain of movies connecting them is Love Me or Leave Me (written by Daniel Fuchs) -> Van Heflin (starred in East Side, West Side) -> East Side, West Side (written by Isobel Lennart)."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'Of Human Bondage' released?",
                "answer": "1934"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie \"The Cat's-Paw\" released?",
                "answer": "1934"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie \"The Cat's-Paw\"?",
                "answer": "Clarence Budington Kelland"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who also wrote the movie 'Mr. Deeds Goes to Town'?",
                "answer": "Clarence Budington Kelland"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'Mr. Deeds Goes to Town' released, which was written by the same person who wrote \"The Cat's-Paw\" in 1934?",
                "answer": "1936"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie released in 1934 was written by the same person who wrote 'Mr. Deeds Goes to Town' which was released in 1936?",
            "answer": "\"The Cat's-Paw\" was written by Clarence Budington Kelland who also wrote 'Mr. Deeds Goes to Town' which was released in 1936. The movie \"The Cat's-Paw\" was released in 1934."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie Upstairs and Downstairs?",
                "answer": "Anne Heywood"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie An Alligator Named Daisy?",
                "answer": "James Robertson Justice"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie An Alligator Named Daisy released?",
                "answer": "1955"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie Many Rivers to Cross released?",
                "answer": "1955"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie starring Anne Heywood was released in the same year as a movie starring James Robertson Justice?",
            "answer": "The movie 'Upstairs and Downstairs', starring Anne Heywood, was released in the same year as the movie 'An Alligator Named Daisy', starring James Robertson Justice. Both movies were released in 1955."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'Revenge for Jolly!'?",
                "answer": "Chadd Harbold"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which person directed the movie 'Revenge for Jolly!' and can you name that movie?",
            "answer": "The movie 'Revenge for Jolly!' was directed by Chadd Harbold."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote 'Silent Night, Deadly Night'?",
                "answer": "Michael Hickey"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which actor starred in 'Silent Night, Deadly Night'?",
                "answer": "Robert Brian Wilson"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actor was written by Michael Hickey in the movie 'Silent Night, Deadly Night'?",
            "answer": "Robert Brian Wilson was written by Michael Hickey in the movie 'Silent Night, Deadly Night'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "What genre is Rachel Nichols known for in the movie 'Conan the Barbarian'?",
                "answer": "Rachel Nichols is known for the pulp genre in the movie 'Conan the Barbarian'."
            },
            {
                "question": "What style is associated with the movie 'Conan the Barbarian'?",
                "answer": "The style associated with the movie 'Conan the Barbarian' is pulp."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie shares a common style with the movie 'Pulp Fiction'?",
                "answer": "The movie 'Conan the Barbarian' shares a common style with the movie 'Pulp Fiction'."
            },
            {
                "question": "What genre is known for being ironic, with the chain of relations from Rachel Nichols to the movie 'Conan the Barbarian' and then to the style 'pulp'?",
                "answer": "The ironic genre is associated with Rachel Nichols through the movie 'Conan the Barbarian' and the style 'pulp'."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "What style is associated with Rachel Nichols, through the movie 'Conan the Barbarian', and is also known for being ironic?",
            "answer": "The style associated with Rachel Nichols, through the movie 'Conan the Barbarian', and is also known for being ironic is 'pulp'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "What genre is 'The Umbrellas of Cherbourg'?",
                "answer": "The genre of 'The Umbrellas of Cherbourg' is 'bd-r'."
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the genre of 'Rocco and His Brothers'?",
                "answer": "The genre of 'Rocco and His Brothers' is 'bd-r'."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was 'Rocco and His Brothers' released?",
                "answer": "'Rocco and His Brothers' was released in the year 1960."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was 'Visit to a Small Planet' released?",
                "answer": "'Visit to a Small Planet' was released in the year 1960."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie starred Jerry Lewis and was released in 1960?",
                "answer": "'Visit to a Small Planet' starred Jerry Lewis and was released in 1960."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "What genre of movie starring Jerry Lewis was released in the same year as 'The Umbrellas of Cherbourg'?",
            "answer": "The genre of movie starring Jerry Lewis that was released in the same year as 'The Umbrellas of Cherbourg' is 'bd-r'. The movie is 'Visit to a Small Planet'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Rupert Graves star in Different for Girls?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Steven Mackintosh star in The Land Girls?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did David Leland write Made in Britain?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Rupert Graves and Steven Mackintosh both star in a movie that was written by David Leland?",
            "answer": "Yes, Rupert Graves starred in \"Different for Girls\" and Steven Mackintosh starred in \"The Land Girls\". Both of these movies were written by David Leland."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Betty Makoni star in the movie Tapestries of Hope?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Does the movie Tapestries of Hope have the tag 'rape'?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Does the movie The Last House on the Left have the tag 'rape'?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Garret Dillahunt star in the movie The Last House on the Left?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Garret Dillahunt star in the movie Burning Bright?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Betty Makoni and Garret Dillahunt both star in movies that have the tag 'rape'?",
            "answer": "Yes, Betty Makoni starred in Tapestries of Hope and Garret Dillahunt starred in The Last House on the Left, both of which have the tag 'rape'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie Empire?",
                "answer": "John Leguizamo"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie Titan A.E.?",
                "answer": "John Leguizamo, Matt Damon"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie The Adjustment Bureau?",
                "answer": "Matt Damon, Emily Blunt"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actors starred in the movies Empire, Titan A.E., The Adjustment Bureau, in that order?",
            "answer": "John Leguizamo, John Leguizamo, Matt Damon, Emily Blunt"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie My Brother the Devil?",
                "answer": "James Floyd"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie My Brother the Devil?",
                "answer": "Sally El Hosaini"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was starred by James Floyd and written by Sally El Hosaini?",
            "answer": "My Brother the Devil"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who directed 'The Grudge 3'?",
                "answer": "Toby Wilkins"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed 'Splinter'?",
                "answer": "Toby Wilkins"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie did Shea Whigham star in?",
                "answer": "Splinter"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie did Shea Whigham and Paul Schneider both star in?",
                "answer": "All the Real Girls"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was directed by the person who also directed 'The Grudge 3' and had Shea Whigham and Paul Schneider as actors?",
            "answer": "All the Real Girls was directed by the person who also directed 'The Grudge 3' and had Shea Whigham and Paul Schneider as actors."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'In the Blood'?",
                "answer": "John Stockwell"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie did Christine star in, that was directed by John Stockwell?",
                "answer": "In the Blood"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie did Keith Gordon star in, that was directed by Alan Metter?",
                "answer": "Back to School"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was directed by John Stockwell and stars both Christine and Keith Gordon, who also starred in a movie directed by Alan Metter?",
            "answer": "In the Blood, directed by John Stockwell, stars both Christine and Keith Gordon. Keith Gordon also starred in Back to School, directed by Alan Metter."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie Skippy?",
                "answer": "Percy Crosby"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie Skippy released?",
                "answer": "1931"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie Charlie Chan Carries On released?",
                "answer": "1931"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie did Marguerite Churchill star in?",
                "answer": "Charlie Chan Carries On"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie did Marguerite Churchill and the actor in Dracula's Daughter star in together?",
                "answer": "Charlie Chan Carries On and Dracula's Daughter"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was written by Percy Crosby and starred Marguerite Churchill, who also starred in Dracula's Daughter, and was released in the same year as Charlie Chan Carries On?",
            "answer": "Skippy and Charlie Chan Carries On"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Barlow Jacobs star in Shotgun Stories?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "What tags does Shotgun Stories have?",
                "answer": "bd-r"
            },
            {
                "question": "What other movie shares the bd-r tag?",
                "answer": "Rocco and His Brothers"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was Rocco and His Brothers released?",
                "answer": "1960"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was Visit to a Small Planet released?",
                "answer": "1960"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Barlow Jacobs star in Rocco and His Brothers, and in what year was it released along with Visit to a Small Planet?",
            "answer": "No, Barlow Jacobs did not star in Rocco and His Brothers. Rocco and His Brothers and Visit to a Small Planet were both released in the year 1960."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Enemy at the Gates'?",
                "answer": "Rachel Weisz"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'The Shape of Things'?",
                "answer": "Rachel Weisz and Gretchen Mol"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Music from Another Room'?",
                "answer": "Martha Plimpton"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actors starred in the movies 'Enemy at the Gates', 'The Shape of Things', 'Music from Another Room' and 'Gretchen Mol'?",
            "answer": "Rachel Weisz starred in 'Enemy at the Gates' and 'The Shape of Things', Gretchen Mol starred in 'The Shape of Things' and 'Music from Another Room', and Martha Plimpton starred in 'Music from Another Room'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Anthony Anderson star in Barbershop?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed Barbershop?",
                "answer": "Tim Story."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was directed by Tim Story and starred Ice Cube?",
                "answer": "Ride Along."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was starred by Ice Cube and he also starred in 'Are We Done Yet?'?",
                "answer": "Ride Along."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Anthony Anderson star in a movie directed by Tim Story, who also directed a movie starred by Ice Cube, who in turn starred in a movie with Anthony Anderson?",
            "answer": "Yes, Anthony Anderson starred in Barbershop, which was directed by Tim Story, who also directed Ride Along, where Ice Cube starred, and Ice Cube starred in Are We Done Yet? with Anthony Anderson."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'Heart Like a Wheel' released?",
                "answer": "The movie 'Heart Like a Wheel' was released in the year 1983."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'Trading Places' released?",
                "answer": "The movie 'Trading Places' was released in the year 1983."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie has the tag 'jamie lee curtis'?",
                "answer": "The movie 'Trading Places' has the tag 'jamie lee curtis'."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie has the tag 'A Fish Called Wanda'?",
                "answer": "The movie 'A Fish Called Wanda' has the tag 'A Fish Called Wanda'."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie features the actor 'Kevin Kline'?",
                "answer": "The movie 'A Fish Called Wanda' features the actor 'Kevin Kline'."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "In what year was the movie 'Heart Like a Wheel' released, and which actor features in the movie that also shares a tag with the movie 'A Fish Called Wanda'?",
            "answer": "The movie 'Heart Like a Wheel' was released in the year 1983, and the actor 'Kevin Kline' features in the movie 'A Fish Called Wanda' which shares a tag with the movie 'Trading Places' that also has the tag 'jamie lee curtis'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote 'The Secret Life of Words'?",
                "answer": "Isabel Coixet"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote 'Map of the Sounds of Tokyo'?",
                "answer": "Isabel Coixet"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was 'Map of the Sounds of Tokyo' released?",
                "answer": "2009"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was 'He's Just Not That Into You' released?",
                "answer": "2009"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movies were written by Isabel Coixet and Liz Tuccillo?",
                "answer": "Isabel Coixet wrote 'The Secret Life of Words' and 'Map of the Sounds of Tokyo'. Liz Tuccillo wrote 'He's Just Not That Into You'.\n\nComplex"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie written by Isabel Coixet was released in the same year as a movie written by Liz Tuccillo?",
                "answer": "'Map of the Sounds of Tokyo' and 'He's Just Not That Into You' were both released in the year 2009."
            }
        ],
        "complex": null
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'My Father and the Man in Black' released?",
                "answer": "2012"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'How to Make Money Selling Drugs' released?",
                "answer": "2012"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which actor starred in the movie 'How to Make Money Selling Drugs'?",
                "answer": "Susan Sarandon"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which actor starred in the movie 'The Great Waldo Pepper'?",
                "answer": "Susan Sarandon"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the genre of the movie 'The Great Waldo Pepper'?",
                "answer": "Drama"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "In what year was the movie 'The Great Waldo Pepper', starring the actor who also starred in 'How to Make Money Selling Drugs' and is also part of the 2012 release 'My Father and the Man in Black', released and what is its genre?",
            "answer": "The movie 'The Great Waldo Pepper', in which Susan Sarandon starred, was released in the year 1975 and it is a Drama genre film."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Was Mort W. Elkind involved in writing The Internecine Project?",
                "answer": "Yes, Mort W. Elkind wrote The Internecine Project."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was starred by James Coburn?",
                "answer": "The Internecine Project and In Like Flint are some of the movies starred by James Coburn."
            },
            {
                "question": "What are the tags for James Coburn?",
                "answer": "James Coburn is tagged with In Like Flint and Affliction."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was starred by James Coburn, who was also involved in writing The Internecine Project, and has tags related to one of his movies?",
            "answer": "The Internecine Project was starred by James Coburn, who was involved in writing the movie, and it has the tag 'james coburn' associated with it. Additionally, In Like Flint is also one of the movies starred by James Coburn and is tagged 'in like flint'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Was John Carney involved in the writing of On the Edge?",
                "answer": "Yes, John Carney was a writer for On the Edge."
            },
            {
                "question": "What are the tags associated with On the Edge?",
                "answer": "The tags associated with On the Edge are 'john carney'."
            },
            {
                "question": "What movies has John Carney been tagged with?",
                "answer": "John Carney has been tagged with 'Begin Again'."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movies has Mark Ruffalo starred in?",
                "answer": "Mark Ruffalo has starred in 'Begin Again'."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie has Mark Ruffalo starred in that was written by John Carney?",
                "answer": "Mark Ruffalo has starred in 'Begin Again', which was written by John Carney."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was written by John Carney, who also has a tag associated with it, and where Mark Ruffalo, who starred in a movie written by John Carney, has appeared?",
            "answer": "Mark Ruffalo has appeared in 'Begin Again', which was written by John Carney who is also tagged with 'Begin Again'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie Project X?",
                "answer": "Matt Drake"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which actor starred in the movie Project X?",
                "answer": "Jonathan Daniel Brown"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actor was written by Matt Drake in the movie Project X?",
            "answer": "Jonathan Daniel Brown was written by Matt Drake in the movie Project X."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Does Barry Pepper have any tags related to movies?",
                "answer": "Yes, 'The Three Burials of Melquiades Estrada'"
            },
            {
                "question": "What movie starred Tommy Lee Jones?",
                "answer": "The Three Burials of Melquiades Estrada"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie has tags related to Tommy Lee Jones?",
                "answer": "Rules of Engagement"
            },
            {
                "question": "What movie is associated with the tag 'Black Moon Rising'?",
                "answer": "tommy lee jones"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie starring Tommy Lee Jones, who also appears in a movie associated with the tag 'The Three Burials of Melquiades Estrada', has a tag related to 'Black Moon Rising'?",
            "answer": "Rules of Engagement is associated with the tag 'Black Moon Rising'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "What genre is the movie 'Venus in Fur'?",
                "answer": "The movie 'Venus in Fur' is a Drama."
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the genre of the movie 'Doing Time on Maple Drive'?",
                "answer": "The movie 'Doing Time on Maple Drive' is a Drama."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'Doing Time on Maple Drive'?",
                "answer": "The movie 'Doing Time on Maple Drive' was directed by Ken Olin."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "What genre is the movie 'Venus in Fur' and who directed the movie 'Doing Time on Maple Drive', which shares the same genre as 'Venus in Fur'?",
            "answer": "The movie 'Venus in Fur' is a Drama and the movie 'Doing Time on Maple Drive', which shares the same genre as 'Venus in Fur', was directed by Ken Olin."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Werewolf Woman'?",
                "answer": "Rino Di Silvestro"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was 'Werewolf Woman' released?",
                "answer": "1976"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was 'Two-Minute Warning' released?",
                "answer": "1976"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie did John Cassavetes star in?",
                "answer": "Two-Minute Warning"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie did John Cassavetes direct?",
                "answer": "A Child Is Waiting"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was written by Rino Di Silvestro and starred John Cassavetes, who also directed a movie released in the same year as 'Werewolf Woman'?",
            "answer": "Two-Minute Warning, released in 1976. John Cassavetes starred in this movie and directed 'A Child Is Waiting', which was also released in 1976."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Class of 1984'?",
                "answer": "Mark L. Lester"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie did Roddy McDowall star in, along with other actors?",
                "answer": "Class of 1984"
            },
            {
                "question": "In which movie did Roddy McDowall act?",
                "answer": "Circle of Iron"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Circle of Iron'?",
                "answer": "Stanley Mann"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who also wrote the movie 'The Mouse That Roared'?",
                "answer": "Stanley Mann"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actor, Roddy McDowall, acted in movies written by two different writers, Mark L. Lester and Stanley Mann?",
            "answer": "Roddy McDowall acted in 'Class of 1984', written by Mark L. Lester, and 'Circle of Iron', written by Stanley Mann."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'Rogue Cop' released?",
                "answer": "1954."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'It Should Happen to You' released?",
                "answer": "1954."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'It Should Happen to You'?",
                "answer": "George Cukor."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'Girls About Town'?",
                "answer": "George Cukor."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movies were directed by George Cukor and have the tag 'george cukor'?",
                "answer": "Girls About Town."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "In what year were the movies 'Rogue Cop' and 'It Should Happen to You' released, and who directed these movies as well as 'Girls About Town', which has the tag 'george cukor'?",
            "answer": "The movies 'Rogue Cop' and 'It Should Happen to You' were released in 1954, and they were directed by George Cukor, who also directed 'Girls About Town', which has the tag 'george cukor'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Henry Phillips star in Punching the Clown?",
                "answer": "Yes, Henry Phillips starred in Punching the Clown."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote Punching the Clown?",
                "answer": "Punching the Clown was written by Gregori Viens."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Who wrote Punching the Clown, the movie in which Henry Phillips starred?",
            "answer": "Gregori Viens wrote Punching the Clown, the movie in which Henry Phillips starred."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "In what year was Gracie's Choice released?",
                "answer": "2004"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was Puppet Master vs Demonic Toys released?",
                "answer": "2004"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote Puppet Master vs Demonic Toys?",
                "answer": "C. Courtney Joyner"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "In what year was Puppet Master vs Demonic Toys released, and who wrote it?",
            "answer": "2004, C. Courtney Joyner"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Battleground'?",
                "answer": "Ricardo Montalban"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Sweet Charity'?",
                "answer": "Ricardo Montalban"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Sweet Charity'?",
                "answer": "Ennio Flaiano"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie '8\u00bd'?",
                "answer": "Ennio Flaiano"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie starred Ricardo Montalban and was written by Ennio Flaiano?",
                "answer": "Sweet Charity"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie starred Marcello Mastroianni, was written by Ennio Flaiano, and Ricardo Montalban also starred in it after appearing in the movie 'Battleground'?",
            "answer": "Sweet Charity"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "In what language is the movie 'Journey of Hope'?",
                "answer": "The movie 'Journey of Hope' is in Turkish."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what language is the movie 'Three Monkeys'?",
                "answer": "The movie 'Three Monkeys' is in Turkish."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Three Monkeys'?",
                "answer": "Nuri Bilge Ceylan wrote the movie 'Three Monkeys'."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Clouds of May'?",
                "answer": "Nuri Bilge Ceylan wrote the movie 'Clouds of May'."
            },
            {
                "question": "What tags does the movie 'Clouds of May' have?",
                "answer": "The movie 'Clouds of May' has the tag 'nuri bilge ceylan'."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Clouds of May' and what language are the movies 'Journey of Hope' and 'Three Monkeys' in?",
            "answer": "Nuri Bilge Ceylan wrote the movie 'Clouds of May' and the movies 'Journey of Hope' and 'Three Monkeys' are in Turkish."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Phil Daniels star in the movie Quadrophenia?",
                "answer": "Yes, he did."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie Quadrophenia released?",
                "answer": "The movie Quadrophenia was released in the year 1979."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie All Quiet on the Western Front released?",
                "answer": "The movie All Quiet on the Western Front was also released in the year 1979."
            },
            {
                "question": "Is All Quiet on the Western Front a part of the national film registry?",
                "answer": "Yes, it is."
            },
            {
                "question": "Is Swing Time a part of the national film registry?",
                "answer": "Yes, Swing Time is a part of the national film registry as well."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Phil Daniels star in the movie Swing Time which was released in 1979 and is a part of the national film registry?",
            "answer": "No, Phil Daniels did not star in the movie Swing Time which was released in 1936 and is a part of the national film registry. The movies Quadrophenia and Swing Time don't have any direct connections based on the given tuples."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Madeline'?",
                "answer": "Nigel Hawthorne"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Amistad'?",
                "answer": "Nigel Hawthorne"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Anthony Hopkins'?",
                "answer": "This is not a correctly formatted question. Anthony Hopkins is an actor, not a movie."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie did Anthony Hopkins star in?",
                "answer": "Surviving Picasso"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actor starred in both 'Madeline' and 'Surviving Picasso', and was also in a movie tagged with 'anthony hopkins'?",
            "answer": "Nigel Hawthorne"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "What genre is the movie 'The Longest Yard'?",
                "answer": "The Longest Yard is a Drama."
            },
            {
                "question": "What genre is the movie 'Doing Time on Maple Drive'?",
                "answer": "Doing Time on Maple Drive is a Drama."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'Doing Time on Maple Drive'?",
                "answer": "Ken Olin"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "What genre is the movie 'The Longest Yard' and who directed the movie 'Doing Time on Maple Drive'?",
            "answer": "The Longest Yard is a Drama and Ken Olin directed the movie 'Doing Time on Maple Drive'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie \"Aces 'N' Eights\"?",
                "answer": "Ernest Borgnine"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie \"Another Harvest Moon\"?",
                "answer": "Doris Roberts"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie \"Play the Game\"?",
                "answer": "Andy Griffith"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actors starred in the movies \"Aces 'N' Eights\", \"Another Harvest Moon\", \"Play the Game\", and also includes Ernest Borgnine, Doris Roberts, and Andy Griffith?",
            "answer": "The actors who starred in those movies are Ernest Borgnine, Doris Roberts, and Andy Griffith. (Note: This answer is possible because Ernest Borgnine starred in \"Aces 'N' Eights\", Doris Roberts starred in \"Another Harvest Moon\", and Andy Griffith starred in \"Play the Game\". The other two actors in the tuples, namely \"Another Harvest Moon\" for Ernest Borgnine and \"Play the Game\" for Doris Roberts, are not relevant to the final complex question.)"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Was Confessions written by Kanae Minato?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the language of Come See the Paradise?",
                "answer": "Japanese."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was The Asthenic Syndrome released?",
                "answer": "1990."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was written by Kanae Minato and was originally released in the same year as Come See the Paradise, but in a different language than Japanese?",
            "answer": "Confessions was written by Kanae Minato and was originally released in the same year as Come See the Paradise, but in a different language than Japanese."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'The Color of Friendship'?",
                "answer": "Kevin Hooks"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'The Color of Friendship' released?",
                "answer": "2000"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'Water Drops on Burning Rocks' released?",
                "answer": "I cannot determine the release year of 'Water Drops on Burning Rocks' directly from the provided facts. However, I know that it was released after 'The Color of Friendship' as they share a common release year of 2000."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Swimming Pool'?",
                "answer": "Fran\u00e7ois Ozon"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Who directed 'The Color of Friendship' and also wrote 'Swimming Pool'?",
            "answer": "Kevin Hooks directed 'The Color of Friendship', but he is not connected to 'Swimming Pool' through the 'directed_by' or 'written_by' relations in the provided tuples. Fran\u00e7ois Ozon wrote 'Swimming Pool', but there is no connection to 'The Color of Friendship' through these relations either."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Sebastian Cabot star in The Jungle Book?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did The Jungle Book star Phil Harris?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Phil Harris star in Good-bye, My Lady?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Good-bye, My Lady star Walter Brennan?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Walter Brennan star in The Gnome-Mobile?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Sebastian Cabot and Walter Brennan both star in any movies together?",
            "answer": "No, they didn't. Sebastian Cabot starred in \"The Jungle Book\" and Walter Brennan in \"The Gnome-Mobile\", but they didn't appear together in any of the provided movies."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote \"Midnight in the Garden of Good and Evil\"?",
                "answer": "John Berendt"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is one of the tags for \"Midnight in the Garden of Good and Evil\"?",
                "answer": "reporter"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie shares a genre with \"Call Northside 777\"?",
                "answer": "He Ran All the Way"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Who wrote the crime film \"He Ran All the Way\", directly or indirectly through a shared genre with \"Call Northside 777\"?",
            "answer": "John Berendt, through the connection of \"Midnight in the Garden of Good and Evil\" sharing a tag 'reporter' with \"Call Northside 777\", and \"reporter\" being a tag for \"Midnight in the Garden of Good and Evil\", and \"Crime\" being a genre for both \"Call Northside 777\" and \"He Ran All the Way\"."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Frank Silvera star in Killer's Kiss?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was Killer's Kiss released?",
                "answer": "1955."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was Many Rivers to Cross released?",
                "answer": "Also 1955."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Robert Taylor star in Many Rivers to Cross?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Robert Taylor write The Nine Lives of Fritz the Cat?",
                "answer": "No, he starred in Many Rivers to Cross."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Frank Silvera star in a movie released in 1955 that was written by Robert Taylor?",
            "answer": "No, Frank Silvera starred in Killer's Kiss which was released in 1955 but it was not written by Robert Taylor."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Was Daniel E. Taylor one of the writers for The Score?",
                "answer": "Yes, he was."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie starred Angela Bassett?",
                "answer": "The Score"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie did Angela Bassett star in alongside Laurence Fishburne?",
                "answer": "Boyz n the Hood"
            },
            {
                "question": "What other movies has Laurence Fishburne been in?",
                "answer": "Assault on Precinct 13"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was written by Daniel E. Taylor and starred Angela Bassett, alongside Laurence Fishburne who was also in Assault on Precinct 13 and Boyz n the Hood?",
            "answer": "The Score and Boyz n the Hood"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Nicolas Bro star in the movie Murk?",
                "answer": "Yes, Nicolas Bro starred in Murk."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was written by Jannik Johansen?",
                "answer": "Murk was written by Jannik Johansen."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was written by Anders Thomas Jensen?",
                "answer": "The Green Butchers was written by Anders Thomas Jensen."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was starred by Nicolas Bro and written by Anders Thomas Jensen through a series of intermediate writers?",
            "answer": "The Green Butchers was starred by Nicolas Bro and written by Anders Thomas Jensen through a series of intermediate writers: Jannik Johansen and Stealing Rembrandt.\nAnswer: Murk was starred by Nicolas Bro and written by Anders Thomas Jensen through a series of intermediate writers: Jannik Johansen and Stealing Rembrandt. (There is another path from Nicolas Bro to Anders Thomas Jensen through Murk, Jannik Johansen, Stealing Rembrandt, and The Green Butchers)"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'Good Guys Wear Black' released?",
                "answer": "1978."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'Force 10 from Navarone' released?",
                "answer": "1978."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which actor starred in the movie 'Good Guys Wear Black'?",
                "answer": "I am not given information about who starred in 'Good Guys Wear Black'."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which actor starred in the movie 'Force 10 from Navarone'?",
                "answer": "Barbara Bach"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which actor starred in the movie 'Barbara Bach'?",
                "answer": "I am not given information about a movie titled 'Barbara Bach'."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which actor starred in the movie 'The Spy Who Loved Me'?",
                "answer": "Barbara Bach and Curd J\u00fcrgens"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which actors starred in the movie 'Force 10 from Navarone' and 'The Spy Who Loved Me'?",
                "answer": "Barbara Bach"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "In what year were the movies 'Good Guys Wear Black' and 'Force 10 from Navarone' released and which actor starred in both of these movies as well as 'The Spy Who Loved Me'?",
            "answer": "The movies 'Good Guys Wear Black' and 'Force 10 from Navarone' were released in 1978. Barbara Bach starred in both 'Force 10 from Navarone' and 'The Spy Who Loved Me'. However, I do not have information about which actors (if any) starred in 'Good Guys Wear Black' and 'The Spy Who Loved Me'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Lesley Ann Warren star in the movie Worth Winning?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Madeleine Stowe star in the movie Unlawful Entry?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Jonathan Kaplan direct the movie Unlawful Entry?",
                "answer": "No, he directed the movie Worth Winning."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Lesley Ann Warren and Madeleine Stowe both star in a movie directed by Jonathan Kaplan, who also directed the movie Bad Girls?",
            "answer": "No, but Lesley Ann Warren and Madeleine Stowe both starred in separate movies directed by Jonathan Kaplan: Lesley Ann Warren in 'Worth Winning' and Madeleine Stowe in 'Unlawful Entry'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Happy Christmas'?",
                "answer": "Lena Dunham"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Tiny Furniture'?",
                "answer": "Laurie Simmons"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actor starred in both 'Happy Christmas' and a movie where Laurie Simmons also starred?",
            "answer": "Lena Dunham starred in 'Happy Christmas' and also starred in 'Tiny Furniture' where Laurie Simmons appeared."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'Bilitis'?",
                "answer": "David Hamilton"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was Patti D'Arbanville a starring actor in?",
                "answer": "Bilitis"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was Dabney Coleman a starring actor in?",
                "answer": "Modern Problems"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which actor starred in the movies 'Bilitis' and 'Where the Heart Is'?",
                "answer": "Patti D'Arbanville and Dabney Coleman"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actor, starred in the movie 'Where the Heart Is', was directed by the director of 'Bilitis'?",
            "answer": "Dabney Coleman"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Fred Stone star in the movie Alice Adams?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "What genre does the movie Alice Adams belong to?",
                "answer": "The genre of Alice Adams is 'class'."
            },
            {
                "question": "In which movie can you watch Jamie Lee Curtis?",
                "answer": "You can watch Jamie Lee Curtis in the movie 'Trading Places'."
            },
            {
                "question": "What other movies share the 'jamie lee curtis' and 'A Fish Called Wanda' tags with 'Trading Places'?",
                "answer": "The only other movie that shares the 'jamie lee curtis' and 'A Fish Called Wanda' tags with 'Trading Places' is 'A Fish Called Wanda' itself."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Was Fred Stone an actor in Trading Places, which stars Jamie Lee Curtis and is connected to the movie A Fish Called Wanda through the shared 'jamie lee curtis' tag, and what is the genre of Alice Adams, the movie in which Fred Stone starred?",
            "answer": "No, Fred Stone did not act in 'Trading Places'. The genre of 'Alice Adams' is 'class'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Rachael Harris star in Diary of a Wimpy Kid?",
                "answer": "Yes, Rachael Harris starred in Diary of a Wimpy Kid."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was Diary of a Wimpy Kid released?",
                "answer": "Diary of a Wimpy Kid was released in the year 2010."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was Father of Invention released?",
                "answer": "Father of Invention was released in the year 2010."
            },
            {
                "question": "What genre is Diary of a Wimpy Kid?",
                "answer": "Diary of a Wimpy Kid is a Drama genre movie."
            },
            {
                "question": "What other genres share the Drama genre with Doing Time on Maple Drive?",
                "answer": "Father of Invention shares the Drama genre with Doing Time on Maple Drive."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Rachael Harris star in a Drama genre movie that was released in 2010, sharing the same genre as Doing Time on Maple Drive?",
            "answer": "Yes, Rachael Harris starred in the Drama genre movie Father of Invention, which was released in 2010 and shares the same genre as Doing Time on Maple Drive."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "What genre is the movie 'The Blacksmith'?",
                "answer": "The genre of 'The Blacksmith' is Short."
            },
            {
                "question": "What genre is the movie 'H\u00f4tel des Invalides'?",
                "answer": "The genre of 'H\u00f4tel des Invalides' is Documentary."
            },
            {
                "question": "What genre is the movie '10 Questions for the Dalai Lama'?",
                "answer": "The genre of '10 Questions for the Dalai Lama' is Documentary."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "What is the genre of 'The Blacksmith' and who wrote the movie '10 Questions for the Dalai Lama'?",
            "answer": "The genre of 'The Blacksmith' is Short and Rick Ray wrote the movie '10 Questions for the Dalai Lama'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Passionada'?",
                "answer": "Theresa Russell"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Physical Evidence'?",
                "answer": "Theresa Russell, Burt Reynolds"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Paternity'?",
                "answer": "Burt Reynolds, Beverly D'Angelo"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actors starred in the movies 'Passionada', 'Physical Evidence', 'Paternity' and also 'Theresa Russell' and 'Burt Reynolds' appeared in all three movies?",
            "answer": "Theresa Russell starred in 'Passionada' and 'Physical Evidence', Burt Reynolds starred in 'Physical Evidence' and 'Paternity', and both Theresa Russell and Burt Reynolds starred in all three movies."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "What is the IMDb rating of 'The Duel at Silver Creek'?",
                "answer": "The IMDb rating of 'The Duel at Silver Creek' is good."
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the genre of 'The Man in the Gray Flannel Suit'?",
                "answer": "The genre of 'The Man in the Gray Flannel Suit' is War."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie does Barbara Bach star in?",
                "answer": "Barbara Bach stars in 'Force 10 from Navarone'."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "What is the IMDb rating of 'The Man in the Gray Flannel Suit' and which movie does Barbara Bach star in?",
            "answer": "The IMDb rating of 'The Man in the Gray Flannel Suit' is good and Barbara Bach stars in 'Force 10 from Navarone'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Does Andy Garcia have any tags related to The Air I Breathe?",
                "answer": "Yes, Andy Garcia has the tag 'The Air I Breathe'."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie stars Julie Delpy?",
                "answer": "The Air I Breathe and Before Sunrise are some of the movies that star Julie Delpy."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which tags are related to Julie Delpy?",
                "answer": "Julie Delpy has the tags 'The Air I Breathe', 'Before Sunrise', and '2 Days in Paris'."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movies star Julie Delpy, who also has a tag related to The Air I Breathe?",
            "answer": "The Air I Breathe is the movie that stars Julie Delpy, who also has the tag 'The Air I Breathe'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Valerie Leon star in Blood from the Mummy's Tomb?",
                "answer": "Yes, Valerie Leon starred in Blood from the Mummy's Tomb."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Andrew Keir star in Attack on the Iron Coast?",
                "answer": "Yes, Andrew Keir starred in Attack on the Iron Coast."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Sue Lloyd star in Corruption?",
                "answer": "Yes, Sue Lloyd starred in Corruption."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Valerie Leon and Sue Lloyd both star in a movie together, and did that movie also star Andrew Keir?",
            "answer": "Yes, Valerie Leon and Sue Lloyd both starred in Blood from the Mummy's Tomb together with Andrew Keir."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Does 'Harold and Maude' have the tag 'existentialist'?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Does 'criterion' have the tag 'It's a Mad, Mad, Mad, Mad World'?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did 'Spencer Tracy' star in 'It's a Mad, Mad, Mad, Mad World'?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did 'Spencer Tracy' star in 'Judgment at Nuremberg' or 'Harold and Maude' or in a movie tagged as 'existentialist'?",
                "answer": "Yes, 'Spencer Tracy' starred in 'Judgment at Nuremberg'."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did 'Spencer Tracy' star in a movie that has the tag 'existentialist' or 'It's a Mad, Mad, Mad, Mad World' and also is tagged as 'criterion'?",
            "answer": "Yes, 'Spencer Tracy' starred in 'It's a Mad, Mad, Mad, Mad World' which has the tag 'criterion' but not 'existentialist'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Jessica Par\u00e9 star in the movie Suck?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Rob Stefaniuk star in the movie Suck?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did both Jessica Par\u00e9 and Rob Stefaniuk star in the movie Suck?",
            "answer": "Yes."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie Tideland?",
                "answer": "Mitch Cullin"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which author wrote the movie Tideland and in which year was it released?",
            "answer": "Mitch Cullin wrote the movie Tideland and it was released in the year 2005. (Note: Release year is not provided in the input tuple, so I am unable to give an exact answer for the complex question.)"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "What genre is the movie called 'Flood'?",
                "answer": "The genre of the movie 'Flood' is 'flood'."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which actor starred in the movie 'Flood'?",
                "answer": "Robert Carlyle starred in the movie 'Flood'."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was directed by Robert Carlyle?",
                "answer": "Go Now was directed by Robert Carlyle."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which other movies were directed by the director of 'Go Now'?",
                "answer": "Michael Winterbottom directed 'Code 46' and 'Go Now'."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which other movies were directed by the director of the movie 'Flood', who was also one of the actors in the same movie, 'Flood'?",
            "answer": "Michael Winterbottom, who directed 'Flood' and was also one of the actors in the same movie, also directed 'Code 46' and 'Go Now'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "In what year was 'Phantom of the Rue Morgue' released?",
                "answer": "1954"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was 'It Should Happen to You' released?",
                "answer": "1954"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed 'It Should Happen to You'?",
                "answer": "George Cukor"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed 'Girls About Town'?",
                "answer": "George Cukor"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie has tags 'george cukor'?",
                "answer": "Girls About Town"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was released in 1954 and was directed by the same person who directed 'Girls About Town' that has tags 'george cukor'?",
            "answer": "It Should Happen to You and Phantom of the Rue Morgue"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in 'That Championship Season'?",
                "answer": "Martin Sheen"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in 'When the Bough Breaks'?",
                "answer": "Martin Sheen"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in 'The City of Lost Children'?",
                "answer": "Ron Perlman"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actor starred in 'That Championship Season' and also has the tag 'ron perlman' for one of their movies?",
            "answer": "Martin Sheen (however, this answer is not accurate since the tag 'ron perlman' is actually for the movie 'The City of Lost Children' which stars Ron Perlman)"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Lonely Street'?",
                "answer": "Peter Ettinger"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which person wrote the movie 'Lonely Street' and what is the title of that movie?",
            "answer": "Peter Ettinger wrote the movie 'Lonely Street'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'I Am Number Four'?",
                "answer": "Marti Noxon and Jobie Hughes"
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Marti Noxon or Jobie Hughes write 'I Am Number Four'?",
                "answer": "Yes, both Marti Noxon and Jobie Hughes wrote 'I Am Number Four'."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which individuals are connected by the 'written_by' relation to 'I Am Number Four' and who are those individuals?",
            "answer": "The individuals connected by the 'written_by' relation to 'I Am Number Four' are Marti Noxon and Jobie Hughes."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Irvin Kershner direct RoboCop 2?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the tag of the movie RoboCop 2?",
                "answer": "Peter Weller."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie RoboCop?",
                "answer": "Peter Weller."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie Of Unknown Origin?",
                "answer": "Peter Weller."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie directed by Irvin Kershner has Peter Weller as a tag and stars Peter Weller in Of Unknown Origin?",
            "answer": "RoboCop 2."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Was N.C. Heikin involved in the writing of Kimjongilia?",
                "answer": "Yes, N.C. Heikin was the writer of Kimjongilia."
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the genre of Kimjongilia?",
                "answer": "The genre of Kimjongilia is Documentary."
            },
            {
                "question": "What is a genre of the documentary '10 Questions for the Dalai Lama'?",
                "answer": "The genre of the documentary '10 Questions for the Dalai Lama' is Documentary."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the documentary '10 Questions for the Dalai Lama' and was also involved in the writing of Kimjongilia?",
                "answer": "Rick Ray"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Who is the writer of both 'Kimjongilia' and the documentary '10 Questions for the Dalai Lama', and what is the genre of 'Kimjongilia' and the documentary '10 Questions for the Dalai Lama'?",
            "answer": "N.C. Heikin is the writer of 'Kimjongilia' and Rick Ray is the writer of the documentary '10 Questions for the Dalai Lama'. The genre of 'Kimjongilia' is Documentary and the genre of the documentary '10 Questions for the Dalai Lama' is also Documentary."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "What genre is 'Let the Bullets Fly'?",
                "answer": "'Let the Bullets Fly' has the tag 'china'."
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the genre of 'Farewell My Concubine'?",
                "answer": "'Farewell My Concubine' has the tag 'china'."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in 'Farewell My Concubine'?",
                "answer": "Leslie Cheung starred in 'Farewell My Concubine'."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in 'Happy Together'?",
                "answer": "Leslie Cheung starred in 'Happy Together'."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in 'Happy Together' with Patrick Dempsey?",
                "answer": "Leslie Cheung starred in 'Happy Together' with Patrick Dempsey."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "In what movies did Leslie Cheung and Patrick Dempsey act together, and what is the genre of those movies?",
            "answer": "Leslie Cheung and Patrick Dempsey acted together in 'Happy Together', which has the tag 'china'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Marcus Patrick star in Violet Tendencies?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed Violet Tendencies?",
                "answer": "Casper Andreas."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Casper Andreas star in Going Down in LA-LA Land?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote Going Down in LA-LA Land?",
                "answer": "Andy Zeffer."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Marcus Patrick star in a movie directed by Casper Andreas and written by Andy Zeffer?",
            "answer": "Yes, Marcus Patrick starred in Violet Tendencies which was directed by Casper Andreas and written by Andy Zeffer."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'Two Drifters' released?",
                "answer": "2005"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'Boy Eats Girl' released?",
                "answer": "2005"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'Boy Eats Girl'?",
                "answer": "Stephen Bradley"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "In what year was the movie 'Boy Eats Girl' directed by Stephen Bradley released?",
            "answer": "2005"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'Layer Cake'?",
                "answer": "Matthew Vaughn"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Kick-Ass'?",
                "answer": "Jane Goldman"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'The Debt'?",
                "answer": "Assaf Bernstein"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which director and writers were involved in the making of the movies 'Layer Cake', 'Kick-Ass', 'The Debt'?",
            "answer": "The director Matthew Vaughn and writers Jane Goldman and Assaf Bernstein were involved in the making of these movies."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'In Hell'?",
                "answer": "Ringo Lam"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'Maximum Risk'?",
                "answer": "Ringo Lam"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'Maximum Risk' released?",
                "answer": "1996"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'Beyond Hypothermia' released?",
                "answer": "The knowledge graph does not provide information about the release year of 'Beyond Hypothermia'."
            },
            {
                "question": "Does the movie 'Beyond Hypothermia' have tags related to 'hong kong'?",
                "answer": "Yes, it does."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Who directed the movies 'In Hell' and 'Maximum Risk', and in what year was the movie 'Beyond Hypothermia', which has tags related to 'hong kong', released?",
            "answer": "Ringo Lam directed the movies 'In Hell' and 'Maximum Risk'. The knowledge graph does not provide information about the release year of 'Beyond Hypothermia'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Garrett Strommen star in I Dreamed of Africa?",
                "answer": "Yes"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote I Dreamed of Africa?",
                "answer": "Kuki Gallmann"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Garrett Strommen star in a movie written by Kuki Gallmann?",
            "answer": "Yes, Garrett Strommen starred in I Dreamed of Africa, which was written by Kuki Gallmann."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in Beverly Hills Ninja?",
                "answer": "Nicollette Sheridan"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in Spy Hard?",
                "answer": "Nicollette Sheridan"
            },
            {
                "question": "What movie was written by Jason Friedberg?",
                "answer": "Spy Hard"
            },
            {
                "question": "What movie was written by Jason Friedberg and starred Matt Lanter?",
                "answer": "Vampires Suck"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie starring Nicollette Sheridan was written by Jason Friedberg and also starred an actor from Vampires Suck?",
            "answer": "Spy Hard and Beverly Hills Ninja. Spy Hard was written by Jason Friedberg and starred Nicollette Sheridan, and Matt Lanter, who starred in Vampires Suck, also appeared in Spy Hard."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Nowhere in Africa'?",
                "answer": "Caroline Link"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the language of the movie 'Nowhere in Africa'?",
                "answer": "German"
            },
            {
                "question": "What other movie is in German, besides 'Nowhere in Africa'?",
                "answer": "Water Drops on Burning Rocks"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Water Drops on Burning Rocks'?",
                "answer": "Fran\u00e7ois Ozon"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the next movie written by Fran\u00e7ois Ozon after 'Water Drops on Burning Rocks'?",
                "answer": "Swimming Pool"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Nowhere in Africa', which is in German, and what is the next movie written by the same person?",
            "answer": "Caroline Link wrote the movie 'Nowhere in Africa', which is in German. The next movie written by her is 'Swimming Pool'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'The Groundstar Conspiracy'?",
                "answer": "Lamont Johnson"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was 'The Groundstar Conspiracy' released?",
                "answer": "1972"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was 'The Effect of Gamma Rays on Man-in-the-Moon Marigolds' released?",
                "answer": "1972"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'The Effect of Gamma Rays on Man-in-the-Moon Marigolds'?",
                "answer": "Paul Zindel"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Up the Sandbox'?",
                "answer": "Paul Zindel"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "In what year was 'The Groundstar Conspiracy' directed by Lamont Johnson released, and who wrote the movies 'The Effect of Gamma Rays on Man-in-the-Moon Marigolds' and 'Up the Sandbox'?",
            "answer": "'The Groundstar Conspiracy' was released in 1972 and was directed by Lamont Johnson. Paul Zindel wrote the movies 'The Effect of Gamma Rays on Man-in-the-Moon Marigolds' and 'Up the Sandbox'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'The Home Song Stories'?",
                "answer": "Tony Ayres"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which person is responsible for writing the movie 'The Home Song Stories' and what is the title of that movie?",
            "answer": "Tony Ayres is responsible for writing the movie 'The Home Song Stories'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Cheyenne Jackson star in The Green?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Jason Butler Harner star in The Green?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actors, Cheyenne Jackson and Jason Butler Harner, both starred in the movie The Green?",
            "answer": "Cheyenne Jackson and Jason Butler Harner both starred in The Green."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who is one of the stars of the movie 'St. Elmo's Fire'?",
                "answer": "Andrew McCarthy"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie stars Demi Moore?",
                "answer": "Disclosure"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which actor is connected to the tag 'demi moore' through a movie?",
                "answer": "The movie 'Disclosure' has the tag 'demi moore' and stars Demi Moore."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actor from the movie 'St. Elmo's Fire' is connected to the tag 'demi moore' through a movie?",
            "answer": "Andrew McCarthy is connected to the tag 'demi moore' through the movie 'Disclosure' which stars Demi Moore."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who is one of the writers of 'The Nanny Diaries'?",
                "answer": "Nicola Kraus"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who is the director of 'Girl Most Likely'?",
                "answer": "Robert Pulcini"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was starred by Darren Criss?",
                "answer": "Girl Most Likely"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which director of 'The Nanny Diaries' also directed a movie starred by the actor of 'A Very Potter Musical'?",
                "answer": "Robert Pulcini"
            }
        ],
        "complex": null
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Was Intersection written by Claude Sautet?",
                "answer": "Yes, Intersection was written by Claude Sautet."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was starred by Richard Gere?",
                "answer": "Intersection was starred by Richard Gere."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was released in 1978?",
                "answer": "Bloodbrothers was released in 1978."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was released in the same year as Bloodbrothers and was also starred by an actor who starred in Intersection, that was written by Claude Sautet?",
                "answer": "Force 10 from Navarone was released in the same year as Bloodbrothers and was also starred by an actor who starred in Intersection, that was written by Claude Sautet."
            }
        ],
        "complex": null
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Brave'?",
                "answer": "Irene Mecchi"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'The Lion King'?",
                "answer": "Irene Mecchi"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Beauty and the Beast'?",
                "answer": "Linda Woolverton"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie did Robby Benson star in?",
                "answer": "Beauty and the Beast"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was written by the person who also wrote the movie that Robby Benson starred in, and was also written by the person who wrote 'The Lion King'?",
            "answer": "Beauty and the Beast\nAnswer: Linda Woolverton"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Robert Webber star in the movie '10'?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did the number '10' star in the movie 'Julie Andrews'?",
                "answer": "No, the correct relationship is that Julie Andrews starred in the movie '10'."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Julie Andrews star in the movie 'S.O.B.'?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did the movie 'S.O.B.' star in the movie 'William Holden'?",
                "answer": "No, the correct relationship is that William Holden starred in the movie 'S.O.B.'."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did William Holden star in the movie 'Escape from Fort Bravo'?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Robert Webber and William Holden both star in movies that also featured Julie Andrews?",
            "answer": "Yes, both Robert Webber and William Holden starred in movies that also featured Julie Andrews. Specifically, Robert Webber starred in the movie '10' and William Holden starred in the movie 'S.O.B.'. Both of these movies featured Julie Andrews."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Does Mars have a tag in the movie Total Recall?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie Total Recall?",
                "answer": "Jon Povill."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Does Mars have a tag in the movie Total Recall, and who wrote that movie?",
            "answer": "Yes, Mars has a tag in the movie Total Recall, and it was written by Jon Povill."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Does the movie 'The Boys from Brazil' have the genre 'Thriller'?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Does the genre 'Thriller' have the genre 'Trans-Europ-Express'?",
                "answer": "No, a genre does not have other genres. The correct relationship should be: 'The Boys from Brazil' has_genre 'Trans-Europ-Express'."
            },
            {
                "question": "Does the movie 'Trans-Europ-Express' star the actor 'Christian Barbier'?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie has the genre 'Thriller' and also stars the actor 'Christian Barbier'?",
            "answer": "The movie 'Trans-Europ-Express' has the genre 'Thriller' and also stars the actor 'Christian Barbier'. The initial statement that 'The Boys from Brazil' has the genre 'Thriller' is not accurate because a movie cannot have the genre 'Thriller' and also star an actor. Movies and genres are different types of entities."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'Karate Girl' released?",
                "answer": "2011"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was 'The Well-Digger's Daughter' released?",
                "answer": "2011"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which actor starred in 'The Well-Digger's Daughter'?",
                "answer": "Daniel Auteuil"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie does Daniel Auteuil star in?",
                "answer": "My Favorite Season"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what language is the movie 'My Favorite Season' in?",
                "answer": "French"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "In what year was 'My Favorite Season', a French movie where Daniel Auteuil has a role, released?",
            "answer": "I cannot provide a specific release year for 'My Favorite Season' with the given knowledge graph fragments. However, Daniel Auteuil starred in 'My Favorite Season', and we know that it's in French and was released in the same year as 'The Well-Digger's Daughter', which is 2011."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'Hair Show'?",
                "answer": "Leslie Small"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which actors starred in the movie 'Hair Show'?",
                "answer": "Mo'Nique"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie stars 'Mo'Nique'?",
                "answer": "Hair Show"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie marks the acting debut of 'Mo'Nique'?",
                "answer": "Precious"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which director is associated with the movie where 'Mo'Nique' made her acting debut and also directed the movie 'Hair Show' that stars 'Mo'Nique'?",
            "answer": "Leslie Small"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie Willow?",
                "answer": "Bob Dolman"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie Willow released?",
                "answer": "1988"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie Stand and Deliver released?",
                "answer": "1988"
            },
            {
                "question": "What type of setting does the movie Stand and Deliver have?",
                "answer": "High school"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the release year and setting of the movies connected to Bob Dolman through the knowledge graph?",
                "answer": "The movie Willow, written by Bob Dolman, was released in 1988 and its setting is high school, which is also associated with the movie Stand and Deliver, released in the same year. Additionally, the movie John Tucker Must Die is also associated with the high school setting.\nAnswer: 1988 and high school"
            }
        ],
        "complex": null
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'The Girl with the Dragon Tattoo'?",
                "answer": "David Fincher"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'Fight Club'?",
                "answer": "David Fincher"
            },
            {
                "question": "What are some tags associated with 'Fight Club'?",
                "answer": "David Fincher"
            },
            {
                "question": "What are some tags associated with 'Gone Girl'?",
                "answer": "David Fincher"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie starred Neil Patrick Harris and was directed by an individual who also directed a movie tagged as 'david fincher' and a movie titled 'Gone Girl'?",
                "answer": "The Girl with the Dragon Tattoo"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie starring Neil Patrick Harris have connections to both 'Fight Club' and 'Gone Girl' through their director?",
            "answer": "The Girl with the Dragon Tattoo"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in Flash Gordon's Trip to Mars?",
                "answer": "Buster Crabbe and Frank Shannon"
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Buster Crabbe and Frank Shannon star in the same movie?",
                "answer": "Yes, they both starred in Flash Gordon's Trip to Mars."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was it where Buster Crabbe acted alongside the actor who also starred in Flash Gordon's Trip to Mars?",
            "answer": "Flash Gordon's Trip to Mars"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote 'New York'?",
                "answer": "Sandeep Srivastava"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed 'New York'?",
                "answer": "Kabir Khan"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the genre of 'Kabul Express'?",
                "answer": "Drama"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Who wrote 'Kabul Express', which was directed by the person who also directed 'New York', a movie written by the person who wrote 'New York' in 'New York'?",
            "answer": "Sandeep Srivastava"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who directed Rubber Johnny?",
                "answer": "Chris Cunningham"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote Rubber Johnny?",
                "answer": "Aphex Twin"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Who directed the movie written by Aphex Twin?",
            "answer": "Chris Cunningham directed the movie written by Aphex Twin, which is Rubber Johnny."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Was Kristian Fraga involved in writing the movie Severe Clear?",
                "answer": "Yes, Kristian Fraga was the writer of Severe Clear."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie Severe Clear released?",
                "answer": "Severe Clear was released in the year 2009."
            },
            {
                "question": "Was the movie He's Just Not That Into You released in the same year as Severe Clear?",
                "answer": "No, He's Just Not That Into You was not released in the year 2009. It was released in a different year."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Liz Tuccillo and Kristian Fraga both write movies that were released in the year 2009?",
            "answer": "No, Liz Tuccillo and Kristian Fraga did not both write movies that were released in the year 2009. Although Liz Tuccillo is a writer of He's Just Not That Into You, it was not released in the year 2009."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'I Never Promised You a Rose Garden'?",
                "answer": "Joanne Greenberg"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'I Never Promised You a Rose Garden' released?",
                "answer": "1977"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'The Island of Dr. Moreau' released?",
                "answer": "1996"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'Beyond Hypothermia' released?",
                "answer": "Cannot determine, not provided in the given tuples."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Who wrote the movie 'I Never Promised You a Rose Garden', and in what year was this movie released along with 'The Island of Dr. Moreau'?",
            "answer": "Joanne Greenberg and 1977 for 'I Never Promised You a Rose Garden', and 1996 for 'The Island of Dr. Moreau'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Does the movie 'Sal\u00f2, or the 120 Days of Sodom' have the tag 'controversial'?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Sal\u00f2, or the 120 Days of Sodom'?",
                "answer": "Pier Paolo Pasolini."
            },
            {
                "question": "What movie was written by Pier Paolo Pasolini?",
                "answer": "The Canterbury Tales."
            },
            {
                "question": "Does the movie 'The Canterbury Tales' have the tag 'pier paolo pasolini'?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was written by 'pier paolo pasolini' and has the tag 'The Gospel According to St. Matthew'?",
                "answer": "The Gospel According to St. Matthew."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was written by the person who wrote the controversial movie 'Sal\u00f2, or the 120 Days of Sodom' and also has the tag 'The Gospel According to St. Matthew'?",
            "answer": "The Gospel According to St. Matthew was written by Pier Paolo Pasolini, who also wrote the controversial movie 'Sal\u00f2, or the 120 Days of Sodom'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Does the movie 'Giallo' have the tag 'bd-r'?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Does the tag 'bd-r' have the movie 'Rocco and His Brothers'?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'Rocco and His Brothers' released?",
                "answer": "1960."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'Visit to a Small Planet' released?",
                "answer": "1960."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie starred the actor 'Jerry Lewis' and was released in the year 1960?",
                "answer": "Visit to a Small Planet"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie released in 1960 has the tag 'bd-r' and starred the actor 'Jerry Lewis'?",
            "answer": "The movie 'Visit to a Small Planet' was released in the year 1960, has the tag 'bd-r' and starred the actor 'Jerry Lewis'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'My Left Eye Sees Ghosts' released?",
                "answer": "2002"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'Men with Brooms' released?",
                "answer": "2002"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which actor starred in the movie 'Men with Brooms'?",
                "answer": "Molly Parker"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which actor starred in the movie 'The Center of the World'?",
                "answer": "Molly Parker"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie has tags including 'molly parker'?",
                "answer": "The Center of the World"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "In what year were the movies 'My Left Eye Sees Ghosts' and 'Men with Brooms' released, and which actor starred in both 'Men with Brooms' and a movie with tags including 'molly parker'?",
            "answer": "The movies 'My Left Eye Sees Ghosts' and 'Men with Brooms' were released in the year 2002. Molly Parker starred in both 'Men with Brooms' and 'The Center of the World', which has tags including 'molly parker'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'The Patsy'?",
                "answer": "King Vidor"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'Comrade X'?",
                "answer": "King Vidor"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was starred by Clark Gable and directed by King Vidor?",
                "answer": "Comrade X"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was starred by Clark Gable and Joan Crawford?",
                "answer": "Strange Cargo"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was directed by the person who also directed a movie starred by the actor who starred in a movie with Joan Crawford?",
            "answer": "The Patsy"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Helter Skelter'?",
                "answer": "Steve Railsback"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Helter Skelter'?",
                "answer": "John Gray"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'The Day Lincoln Was Shot'?",
                "answer": "John Gray"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'The Nature of the Beast'?",
                "answer": "Lance Henriksen"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was written by John Gray and starred an actor who also starred in a movie directed by the same person who directed a movie in which Steve Railsback starred?",
            "answer": "The Day Lincoln Was Shot. Lance Henriksen starred in this movie, and he also starred in 'The Nature of the Beast', which was directed by Roger Christian, who also directed 'Helter Skelter' where Steve Railsback starred."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote 'The Toolbox Murders'?",
                "answer": "Ann Kindberg and Neva Friedenn"
            },
            {
                "question": "Was 'The Toolbox Murders' written by Ann Kindberg?",
                "answer": "Yes"
            },
            {
                "question": "Was 'The Toolbox Murders' written by Neva Friedenn?",
                "answer": "Yes"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Who are the writers of 'The Toolbox Murders'?",
            "answer": "Ann Kindberg and Neva Friedenn"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'What We Did on Our Holiday'?",
                "answer": "Rosamund Pike"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Surrogates'?",
                "answer": "Rosamund Pike"
            },
            {
                "question": "What are the tags for 'James Cromwell'?",
                "answer": "has tags 'I, Robot' and 'Surrogates'"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movies star 'James Cromwell' and have the tag 'I, Robot'?",
                "answer": "I, Robot"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actor, known for their role in 'What We Did on Our Holiday', starred in another movie that shares a tag with a movie where 'James Cromwell' appears?",
            "answer": "Rosamund Pike appears in the movie 'Surrogates' which shares the tag 'james cromwell' with the movie 'I, Robot' where 'James Cromwell' also appears."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the book 'Speak'?",
                "answer": "Laurie Halse Anderson"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which book was written by Laurie Halse Anderson, considering the relationship 'written_by'?",
            "answer": "Speak"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'I, Frankenstein'?",
                "answer": "Stuart Beattie"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was written by Stuart Beattie?",
                "answer": "Tomorrow, When the War Began"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Tomorrow, When the War Began'?",
                "answer": "Caitlin Stasey"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Who wrote the movie 'I, Frankenstein' and who starred in the movie written by that person?",
            "answer": "Stuart Beattie wrote 'I, Frankenstein' and Caitlin Stasey starred in the movie 'Tomorrow, When the War Began' which was written by Stuart Beattie."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'The Hurricane'?",
                "answer": "Sam Chaiton"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie starred Mary Astor?",
                "answer": "The Hurricane"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie starred Mary Astor and Meet Me in St. Louis?",
                "answer": "Mary Astor starred in 'The Hurricane' and Meet Me in St. Louis."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which actor starred in 'Our Vines Have Tender Grapes' and Meet Me in St. Louis, The Hurricane?",
                "answer": "Margaret O'Brien starred in 'Our Vines Have Tender Grapes', Meet Me in St. Louis, and was also in The Hurricane, although not as a main actor."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actor starred in 'Our Vines Have Tender Grapes', Meet Me in St. Louis, The Hurricane and was written by the writer of The Hurricane?",
            "answer": "There is no actor who starred in all four: 'Our Vines Have Tender Grapes', Meet Me in St. Louis, The Hurricane and was also the writer of The Hurricane. Sam Chaiton, the writer of The Hurricane, is not an actor in any of these movies."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'My Gun Is Quick'?",
                "answer": "Mickey Spillane"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'My Gun Is Quick'?",
                "answer": "George White"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was written by Mickey Spillane and directed by George White?",
            "answer": "My Gun Is Quick"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Was David Hines involved in writing the movie 'Whore'?",
                "answer": "Yes, David Hines was involved in writing the movie 'Whore'."
            },
            {
                "question": "In which year was the movie 'Whore' released?",
                "answer": "The movie 'Whore' was released in the year 1991."
            },
            {
                "question": "Was Wes Craven involved in writing the movie 'The People Under the Stairs'?",
                "answer": "Yes, Wes Craven was involved in writing the movie 'The People Under the Stairs'."
            },
            {
                "question": "In which year was the movie 'The People Under the Stairs' released?",
                "answer": "The movie 'The People Under the Stairs' was released in the year 1991."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Wes Craven write the movie 'Paris, je t'aime'?",
                "answer": "Yes, Wes Craven wrote the movie 'Paris, je t'aime'."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did David Hines and Wes Craven both write movies that were released in the year 1991?",
            "answer": "Yes, David Hines wrote 'Whore' and Wes Craven wrote 'The People Under the Stairs', both of which were released in the year 1991."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie Lady in Cement?",
                "answer": "Richard Conte"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie Lady in Cement?",
                "answer": "Gordon Douglas"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was directed by Gordon Douglas in the year 1940?",
                "answer": "Saps at Sea"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie Dr. Ehrlich's Magic Bullet released, which was directed by the same person who directed Saps at Sea?",
                "answer": "1940"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Who starred in the movie Lady in Cement, which was directed by the same person who directed Saps at Sea, a movie released in the same year as Dr. Ehrlich's Magic Bullet?",
            "answer": "Richard Conte"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Was Fair Game written by Paula Gosling?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Paula Gosling write Cobra?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Brigitte Nielsen star in Cobra?",
                "answer": "No, but she starred in the movie 'Cobra's written by Paula Gosling, which is 'Fair Game'."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Brigitte Nielsen star in Red Sonja?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Richard Fleischer direct Red Sonja?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was written by Paula Gosling and directed by Richard Fleischer and starred Brigitte Nielsen?",
            "answer": "Red Sonja was written by Paula Gosling, directed by Richard Fleischer and starred Brigitte Nielsen. Answer: Fair Game was written by Paula Gosling, directed by Richard Fleischer and starred Brigitte Nielsen. (This answer is not accurate because only Red Sonja meets all the conditions in the complex question.)"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Zero Effect'?",
                "answer": "Bill Pullman"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Lake Placid'?",
                "answer": "Bill Pullman"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Lake Placid'?",
                "answer": "David E. Kelley"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'To Gillian on Her 37th Birthday'?",
                "answer": "David E. Kelley"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'To Gillian on Her 37th Birthday' and 'Zero Effect'?",
                "answer": "Michael Brady wrote 'To Gillian on Her 37th Birthday', while 'Zero Effect' was written by Scott Frank."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Lake Placid' and was also involved in the creation of 'To Gillian on Her 37th Birthday' and 'Zero Effect'?",
            "answer": "David E. Kelley wrote 'Lake Placid' and was involved in the writing of 'To Gillian on Her 37th Birthday'. He was not directly involved in the writing of 'Zero Effect', but Scott Frank, who wrote 'Zero Effect', did not have any connections to 'Lake Placid' or 'To Gillian on Her 37th Birthday'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'The Burglar' released?",
                "answer": "The movie 'The Burglar' was released in the year 1957."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'The True Story of Jesse James' released?",
                "answer": "The movie 'The True Story of Jesse James' was released in the year 1957."
            },
            {
                "question": "What are the tags for the movie 'Rocco and His Brothers'?",
                "answer": "The tags for the movie 'Rocco and His Brothers' are 'bd-r'."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "In what year were the movies 'The Burglar' and 'Rocco and His Brothers' released, and what are the tags for the movie 'Rocco and His Brothers'?",
            "answer": "The movie 'The Burglar' was released in the year 1957 and the movie 'Rocco and His Brothers' was released in the year 1960. The tags for the movie 'Rocco and His Brothers' are 'bd-r'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'The Money Pit'?",
                "answer": "Shelley Long"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Irreconcilable Differences'?",
                "answer": "Shelley Long, Drew Barrymore"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Riding in Cars with Boys'?",
                "answer": "Drew Barrymore"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'Riding in Cars with Boys'?",
                "answer": "Penny Marshall"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actor starred in the movies 'The Money Pit' and 'Irreconcilable Differences', and was later directed by Penny Marshall in 'Riding in Cars with Boys'?",
            "answer": "Shelley Long"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Daisy Eagan star in the movie Ripe?",
                "answer": "Yes, Daisy Eagan starred in the movie Ripe."
            },
            {
                "question": "What genre is the movie Ripe?",
                "answer": "The genre of Ripe is Drama."
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the genre of the movie Doing Time on Maple Drive?",
                "answer": "The genre of the movie Doing Time on Maple Drive is Drama."
            },
            {
                "question": "Was Doing Time on Maple Drive directed by Ken Olin?",
                "answer": "Yes, Doing Time on Maple Drive was directed by Ken Olin."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Daisy Eagan star in the Drama movie Doing Time on Maple Drive, which was directed by Ken Olin?",
            "answer": "Yes, Daisy Eagan starred in the Drama movie Doing Time on Maple Drive, which was directed by Ken Olin."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Cry-Baby'?",
                "answer": "Susan Tyrrell"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Forbidden Zone'?",
                "answer": "Susan Tyrrell"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Forbidden Zone'?",
                "answer": "Richard Elfman"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actor starred in both 'Cry-Baby' and 'Forbidden Zone', and who wrote 'Forbidden Zone'?",
            "answer": "Susan Tyrrell starred in both 'Cry-Baby' and 'Forbidden Zone', and Richard Elfman wrote 'Forbidden Zone'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Does Annette Bening have a tag for The Kids Are All Right?",
                "answer": "Yes, Annette Bening has the tag 'The Kids Are All Right'."
            },
            {
                "question": "In which movie did Colin Firth star with Annette Bening?",
                "answer": "Valmont\n\nComplex"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie did Annette Bening and Colin Firth both star in, given that Annette Bening has the tag 'The Kids Are All Right' and Colin Firth starred in 'Apartment Zero'?",
                "answer": "Valmont"
            }
        ],
        "complex": null
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Does the movie 'The Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy' have the tag 'mos def'?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "What movie has the actor 'Danny Glover'?",
                "answer": "Be Kind Rewind."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie has the tag 'mos def' and also stars the actor 'Danny Glover'?",
            "answer": "Be Kind Rewind. Answer: <Answer> is both tagged with 'mos def' and stars 'Danny Glover'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in Return from Witch Mountain?",
                "answer": "Bette Davis"
            },
            {
                "question": "In which movie did Bette Davis star?",
                "answer": "Of Human Bondage"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the release year of Of Human Bondage?",
                "answer": "1934"
            },
            {
                "question": "In which year was The Cat's-Paw released?",
                "answer": "1934"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was written by Clarence Budington Kelland and released in the same year as Of Human Bondage?",
                "answer": "The Cat's-Paw"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Who starred in a movie written by Clarence Budington Kelland and released in the same year as Of Human Bondage, which was also the release year of Return from Witch Mountain?",
            "answer": "The Cat's-Paw was written by Clarence Budington Kelland and released in the same year as Of Human Bondage, which was 1934. The actors in The Cat's-Paw are different from those in Return from Witch Mountain, and Bette Davis starred in Of Human Bondage."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "What genre is 'Godzilla, King of the Monsters!'?",
                "answer": "The genre of 'Godzilla, King of the Monsters!' is 'giant monster'."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what language is 'Godzilla, King of the Monsters!'?",
                "answer": "'Godzilla, King of the Monsters!' is in the 'English' language."
            },
            {
                "question": "What language is 'Map of the Human Heart' in?",
                "answer": "'Map of the Human Heart' is in the 'English' language."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which actor starred in 'Map of the Human Heart'?",
                "answer": "Robert Joamie starred in 'Map of the Human Heart'."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actor starred in 'Map of the Human Heart', which is in the same language as 'Godzilla, King of the Monsters!', and is also a part of the 'giant monster' genre?",
            "answer": "There is no actor who starred in 'Map of the Human Heart', which has the same language as 'Godzilla, King of the Monsters!', and is also a part of the 'giant monster' genre. The genres and the languages of the movies are not related."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'The Pope of Greenwich Village'?",
                "answer": "Eric Roberts"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'The Nature of the Beast'?",
                "answer": "Eric Roberts"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'The Horror Show'?",
                "answer": "Lance Henriksen"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actor starred in both 'The Pope of Greenwich Village' and a movie that also starred Lance Henriksen, who was in 'The Horror Show' which has the tag 'lance henriksen'?",
            "answer": "Eric Roberts"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Rita Moreno star in The Night of the Following Day?",
                "answer": "Yes, Rita Moreno starred in The Night of the Following Day."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Richard Boone star in The Kremlin Letter?",
                "answer": "Yes, Richard Boone starred in The Kremlin Letter."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did John Huston write The Kremlin Letter?",
                "answer": "Yes, John Huston wrote The Kremlin Letter."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did John Huston star in Winter Kills?",
                "answer": "Yes, John Huston starred in Winter Kills."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Rita Moreno and Richard Boone both star in a movie that was written by John Huston?",
            "answer": "No, Rita Moreno and Richard Boone did not both star in a movie that was written by John Huston. While Rita Moreno starred in \"The Night of the Following Day\" and Richard Boone starred in \"The Kremlin Letter\", John Huston only wrote \"The Kremlin Letter\" and did not star in it."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Charlie Chan in Panama'?",
                "answer": "Sidney Toler"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Castle in the Desert'?",
                "answer": "Sidney Toler"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'Castle in the Desert' released?",
                "answer": "1942"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'Tortilla Flat' released?",
                "answer": "1942"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which actor starred in the movies 'Charlie Chan in Panama' and 'Tortilla Flat'?",
                "answer": "Hedy Lamarr starred in the movies 'Charlie Chan in Panama' and 'Tortilla Flat'. (Note: Hedy Lamarr did not star in 'Charlie Chan in Panama', but this is the complex question requested.)"
            }
        ],
        "complex": null
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie Among Giants?",
                "answer": "Sam Miller"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which actor starred in the movie Among Giants?",
                "answer": "James Thornton"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actor was directed by Sam Miller in the movie Among Giants?",
            "answer": "James Thornton was directed by Sam Miller in the movie Among Giants."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "What tags does the movie 'Across to Singapore' have?",
                "answer": "The movie 'Across to Singapore' has tags 'william nigh'."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'Across to Singapore' released?",
                "answer": "The movie 'Across to Singapore' was released in the year 1928."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'A Lady of Chance' released?",
                "answer": "The movie 'A Lady of Chance' was released in the year 1928."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'A Lady of Chance'?",
                "answer": "The movie 'A Lady of Chance' was written by 'Leroy Scott'."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Who wrote the movie 'A Lady of Chance' which was released in the same year as 'Across to Singapore' and was tagged with 'william nigh'?",
            "answer": "The movie 'A Lady of Chance', released in the year 1928 and tagged with 'william nigh', was written by 'Leroy Scott'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Stella Street'?",
                "answer": "Peter Richardson"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which actor starred in the movie 'Stella Street'?",
                "answer": "John Sessions"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actor was starred in the movie written by Peter Richardson?",
            "answer": "John Sessions was starred in the movie 'Stella Street' which was written by Peter Richardson."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Was The Loved One written by Christopher Isherwood?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "What tags does The Loved One have?",
                "answer": "bd-r."
            },
            {
                "question": "What tags does bd-r have?",
                "answer": "Rocco and His Brothers."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was Rocco and His Brothers released?",
                "answer": "1960."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was The Loved One or Visit to a Small Planet released?",
                "answer": "The Loved One was released in 1960 and Visit to a Small Planet was also released in 1960.\n\nAnswer:"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "In what year was The Loved One or Visit to a Small Planet released and what tags does The Loved One have?",
            "answer": "The Loved One was released in 1960 and it has the tag bd-r. Visit to a Small Planet was also released in 1960."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Odds Against Tomorrow'?",
                "answer": "William P. McGivern and Abraham Polonsky"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was written by Abraham Polonsky?",
                "answer": "'Odds Against Tomorrow' and 'Body and Soul'"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Body and Soul'?",
                "answer": "John Garfield"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was starred by John Garfield?",
                "answer": "'Body and Soul' and 'Tortilla Flat'"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was written by Abraham Polonsky and starred John Garfield?",
            "answer": "The movie 'Body and Soul' was written by Abraham Polonsky and starred John Garfield."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Lust for Love'?",
                "answer": "Anton King"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which actors starred in the movie 'Lust for Love'?",
                "answer": "Beau Garrett"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actors starred in the movie written by Anton King?",
            "answer": "Beau Garrett starred in the movie 'Lust for Love' which was written by Anton King."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'Love and Honor' released?",
                "answer": "The movie 'Love and Honor' was released in the year 2013."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'The Girl on the Train' released?",
                "answer": "The movie 'The Girl on the Train' was released in the year 2013."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'The Girl on the Train'?",
                "answer": "The movie 'The Girl on the Train' was written by Larry Brand."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "In what year was 'The Girl on the Train' released and who wrote it?",
            "answer": "The movie 'The Girl on the Train' was released in the year 2013 and it was written by Larry Brand."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Arthur Malet star in The Secret of NIMH?",
                "answer": "Yes, he did."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Derek Jacobi star in The Human Factor?",
                "answer": "Yes, he did."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Graham Greene write The Human Factor?",
                "answer": "Yes, he did."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Graham Greene also write Travels with My Aunt?",
                "answer": "Yes, he did."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Arthur Malet star in a movie written by Graham Greene, who also wrote a movie where Derek Jacobi appeared?",
            "answer": "No, they did not directly work together on the same project. While Arthur Malet starred in 'The Secret of NIMH' and Derek Jacobi starred in 'The Human Factor',  Graham Greene wrote both 'The Human Factor' and 'Travels with My Aunt', but there is no direct connection between these actors and the author within these movies."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Sweet Charity'?",
                "answer": "Ennio Flaiano"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie '8\u00bd'?",
                "answer": "Ennio Flaiano"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie did Marcello Mastroianni star in?",
                "answer": "8\u00bd"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie did 'What?' star in?",
                "answer": "This is not a valid entity. However, if we assume the entity to be 'Sydne Rome', then she starred in the movie 'What?'."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was written by the person who also wrote '8\u00bd', and starred an actor who starred in a movie with the title 'What?'?",
            "answer": "Sweet Charity. Ennio Flaiano wrote both 'Sweet Charity' and '8\u00bd'. Marcello Mastroianni, who starred in '8\u00bd', also starred in the movie 'What?' along with Sydne Rome."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Arliss Howard star in The Man Who Captured Eichmann?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was The Man Who Captured Eichmann released?",
                "answer": "1996."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was Beyond Hypothermia released?",
                "answer": "1996."
            },
            {
                "question": "Does Beyond Hypothermia have tags related to hong kong?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Does The God of Cookery have tags related to hong kong?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Arliss Howard star in any movie released in 1996 that has tags related to hong kong and The God of Cookery?",
            "answer": "No. The movie \"The Man Who Captured Eichmann\" was released in 1996 and starred Arliss Howard, but it does not have tags related to hong kong or The God of Cookery. The only movie mentioned that has tags related to hong kong is \"Beyond Hypothermia\" and there is no direct relation between it and \"The God of Cookery\"."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Jerry Springer star in The Defender?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Dolph Lundgren star in The Defender?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Dolph Lundgren star in Command Performance?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the language of Command Performance?",
                "answer": "Russian."
            },
            {
                "question": "What other movie is in Russian besides Only Old Men Are Going to Battle?",
                "answer": "Command Performance."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Jerry Springer and Dolph Lundgren both star in a Russian movie?",
            "answer": "Yes, both Jerry Springer and Dolph Lundgren starred in the Russian movie, Command Performance.\nAnswer:\n\nComplex: Did Jerry Springer and Dolph Lundgren both star in a movie that is also in Russian?\nAnswer: Yes, both Jerry Springer and Dolph Lundgren starred in the movie Command Performance, which is in Russian."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie Zatoichi and the Fugitives?",
                "answer": "Kimiyoshi Yasuda"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie Zatoichi and the Fugitives released?",
                "answer": "1968"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie The Horse in the Gray Flannel Suit released?",
                "answer": "1968"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the genre of the movie The Horse in the Gray Flannel Suit?",
                "answer": "Family"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the genre of the movie Andy Hardy Meets Debutante?",
                "answer": "Family"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "In what year was the movie Zatoichi and the Fugitives directed by Kimiyoshi Yasuda released, and what is the genre of the movie Andy Hardy Meets Debutante?",
            "answer": "The movie Zatoichi and the Fugitives was released in 1968, and the genre of the movie Andy Hardy Meets Debutante is Family."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Pay It Forward'?",
                "answer": "Leslie Dixon"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was directed by Mimi Leder that was released in 2009?",
                "answer": "Thick as Thieves"
            },
            {
                "question": "What movie was released in the same year as 'He's Just Not That Into You'?",
                "answer": "Thick as Thieves"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Pay It Forward' which was directed by Mimi Leder and released in the same year as 'He's Just Not That Into You'?",
            "answer": "Leslie Dixon"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Allan Love star in The Apple?",
                "answer": "Yes, Allan Love starred in The Apple."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote The Apple?",
                "answer": "The Apple was written by Mohsen Makhmalbaf."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Mohsen Makhmalbaf star in Close-Up?",
                "answer": "Yes, Mohsen Makhmalbaf starred in Close-Up."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote Close-Up?",
                "answer": "Close-Up was written by Abbas Kiarostami."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote The Wind Will Carry Us?",
                "answer": "The Wind Will Carry Us was written by Abbas Kiarostami."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Allan Love, who starred in The Apple which was written by Mohsen Makhmalbaf who also starred in Close-Up which was written by Abbas Kiarostami who finally wrote The Wind Will Carry Us, play a role in any movie written by the same writer who wrote The Apple?",
            "answer": "No, Allan Love did not star in any movie written by Mohsen Makhmalbaf, who wrote The Apple."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'A Love Song for Bobby Long'?",
                "answer": "Ronald Everett Capps"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the genre of the movie 'A Love Song for Bobby Long'?",
                "answer": "Drama"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the genre of the movie 'Doing Time on Maple Drive'?",
                "answer": "Drama"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'Doing Time on Maple Drive'?",
                "answer": "Ken Olin"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Who wrote the drama 'A Love Song for Bobby Long', which belongs to the same genre as 'Doing Time on Maple Drive', and who directed 'Doing Time on Maple Drive'?",
            "answer": "Ronald Everett Capps wrote the drama 'A Love Song for Bobby Long' and Ken Olin directed 'Doing Time on Maple Drive'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'The Front Line'?",
                "answer": "David Gleeson"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which person wrote the movie 'The Front Line' and what other movies has he written?",
            "answer": "David Gleeson wrote the movie 'The Front Line'. He has also written other movies, but specific information about those movies is not provided in the given tuple."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Marisa Paredes star in The Skin I Live In?",
                "answer": "Yes, she did."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote The Skin I Live In?",
                "answer": "Pedro Almod\u00f3var"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was written by Pedro Almod\u00f3var and has the tag 'pedro almod\u00f3var'?",
                "answer": "Talk to Her"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movies were written by Pedro Almod\u00f3var and have the tags 'pedro almod\u00f3var' and 'What Have I Done to Deserve This?'?",
                "answer": "I cannot determine a movie that was written by Pedro Almod\u00f3var and has both tags, as 'What Have I Done to Deserve This?' is a different movie than 'Talk to Her'."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movies were written by the director who was starred by Marisa Paredes in The Skin I Live In and have the tags 'pedro almod\u00f3var' or 'What Have I Done to Deserve This'?",
            "answer": "Talk to Her and What Have I Done to Deserve This?"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the comedy movie 'Die, Mommie, Die!'?",
                "answer": "Charles Busch"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the genre of the movie 'O Lucky Man!'?",
                "answer": "Drama"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which drama genre did Charles Busch star in, that is connected to the comedy genre of 'Die, Mommie, Die!' and also connected to the drama genre of 'O Lucky Man!' and finally connected to the drama genre of 'Doing Time on Maple Drive'?",
            "answer": "The drama genre of 'O Lucky Man!' is connected to all the other mentioned genres and entities."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie Mostly Martha?",
                "answer": "Sergio Castellitto"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie Mostly Martha released?",
                "answer": "2001"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie God Is Great and I'm Not released?",
                "answer": "2001"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which actor starred in both Mostly Martha and God Is Great and I'm Not?",
                "answer": "The graph does not provide information about an actor who starred in both movies."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Who starred in Mostly Martha, which was released in the same year as God Is Great and I'm Not starring Edouard Baer?",
            "answer": "Sergio Castellitto and Edouard Baer"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Eddie Griffin star in Urban Justice?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Carmen Serano star in Urban Justice?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Eddie Griffin and Carmen Serano both star in Urban Justice?",
            "answer": "Yes, Eddie Griffin and Carmen Serano both starred in Urban Justice."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote 'Whose Life Is It Anyway?'?",
                "answer": "Brian Clark"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was 'Whose Life Is It Anyway?' released?",
                "answer": "1981"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was 'Take This Job and Shove It' released?",
                "answer": "1981"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie did Robert Hays star in, released in 1981?",
                "answer": "Take This Job and Shove It"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie did Brian Clark write, and in which Robert Hays starred in 1981?",
                "answer": "Whose Life Is It Anyway? and Take This Job and Shove It\n\nAnswer:"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie did Brian Clark write, and which movie was released in the same year in which Robert Hays starred in 'Take This Job and Shove It' and also appeared in a movie released in 1981?",
            "answer": "Whose Life Is It Anyway? and Take This Job and Shove It"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in Charlie Chan in Honolulu?",
                "answer": "Sidney Toler"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in Castle in the Desert?",
                "answer": "Sidney Toler"
            },
            {
                "question": "When was Castle in the Desert released?",
                "answer": "1942"
            },
            {
                "question": "When was Tortilla Flat released?",
                "answer": "1942"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie starring Hedy Lamarr was released in the same year as Castle in the Desert?",
                "answer": "Tortilla Flat\n\nComplex"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in a movie released in 1942, and also acted in a movie with Hedy Lamarr?",
                "answer": "Sidney Toler (starred in 'Castle in the Desert', released in 1942, and acted in 'Castle in the Desert' with Hedy Lamarr)"
            }
        ],
        "complex": null
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie Darkness Falls?",
                "answer": "Emma Caulfield"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actor starred in the movie Darkness Falls and can you also name the movie?",
            "answer": "Emma Caulfield starred in the movie Darkness Falls."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Does Lucy Walker have tags for The Crash Reel?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote The Crash Reel?",
                "answer": "Lucy Walker"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Who is the person that wrote The Crash Reel, using the term 'The Crash Reel' has the tags of the person who wrote it?",
            "answer": "Lucy Walker is the person who wrote The Crash Reel, and The Crash Reel has the tags of Lucy Walker."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Was Rudy De Luca involved in writing Transylvania 6-5000?",
                "answer": "Yes, Rudy De Luca was involved in writing Transylvania 6-5000."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was Jeff Goldblum one of the starred actors in?",
                "answer": "Transylvania 6-5000"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie has the tag 'jeff goldblum'?",
                "answer": "Independence Day"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was written by Rudy De Luca, starring Jeff Goldblum, who also starred in Independence Day, a movie with the tag 'jeff goldblum', and has Morning Glory as another one of its tags?",
                "answer": "Transylvania 6-5000"
            }
        ],
        "complex": null
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Michel C\u00f4t\u00e9 star in the movie Father and Guns?",
                "answer": "Yes, Michel C\u00f4t\u00e9 starred in the movie Father and Guns."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie Father and Guns released?",
                "answer": "The movie Father and Guns was released in the year 2"
            }
        ],
        "complex": null
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Does the movie 'indians' have the tag 'Dances with Wolves'?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Does the movie 'Dances with Wolves' have the tag 'national film registry'?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Does the movie 'national film registry' have the tag 'Swing Time'?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'Swing Time' released?",
                "answer": "1936."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'Three Smart Girls' released, which is also related to the release year of 'Swing Time'?",
                "answer": "The movie 'Three Smart Girls' was also released in the year 1936."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Does the movie 'indians' have the tag 'national film registry' through the relation 'has\\_tags' and is it also related to the release year of 'Three Smart Girls'?",
            "answer": "No, the movie 'indians' is not directly related to the 'national film registry' tag or the release year of 'Three Smart Girls'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'A Date with Judy'?",
                "answer": "Richard Thorpe"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'The Prodigal'?",
                "answer": "Richard Thorpe"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie starred Lana Turner?",
                "answer": "The Prodigal"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie starred Lana Turner and is in English?",
                "answer": "The Postman Always Rings Twice"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie directed by Richard Thorpe and in English, does Lana Turner star in?",
            "answer": "The Postman Always Rings Twice"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Marika Lagercrantz star in All Things Fair?",
                "answer": "Yes, she did."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was All Things Fair released?",
                "answer": "All Things Fair was released in the year 1995."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was How to Make an American Quilt released?",
                "answer": "How to Make an American Quilt was also released in the year 1995."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote How to Make an American Quilt?",
                "answer": "How to Make an American Quilt was written by Whitney Otto."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Marika Lagercrantz star in How to Make an American Quilt, which was written by Whitney Otto and released in the same year as All Things Fair, 1995?",
            "answer": "No, Marika Lagercrantz did not star in How to Make an American Quilt."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'A Dangerous Man' released?",
                "answer": "2009"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'He's Just Not That Into You' released?",
                "answer": "2009"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who is one of the writers of 'He's Just Not That Into You'?",
                "answer": "Liz Tuccillo"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "In what year was 'He's Just Not That Into You' released, and who is one of the writers of this movie that was also released in the same year as 'A Dangerous Man'?",
            "answer": "'He's Just Not That Into You' was released in the year 2009, and Liz Tuccillo is one of the writers of this movie that was also released in the same year as 'A Dangerous Man'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Bedtime Story'?",
                "answer": "Marlon Brando"
            },
            {
                "question": "In which movie did Marlon Brando star?",
                "answer": "Reflections in a Golden Eye"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie has the tag 'marlon brando'?",
                "answer": "Reflections in a Golden Eye"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie has the tag 'The Island of Dr. Moreau' and what is its release year?",
                "answer": "The Island of Dr. Moreau, 1996"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie starring Marlon Brando was released in 1996 and also has the tag 'The Island of Dr. Moreau'?",
            "answer": "The Island of Dr. Moreau"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Roxane Mesquida star in Fat Girl?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote Fat Girl?",
                "answer": "Catherine Breillat"
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Sarah Pratt star in Brief Crossing?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Roxane Mesquida, who starred in Fat Girl which was written by Catherine Breillat, also star in Brief Crossing which was also written by Catherine Breillat?",
            "answer": "No, Roxane Mesquida did not star in Brief Crossing."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie Black Moon Rising?",
                "answer": "Harley Cokeliss"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie stars Tommy Lee Jones?",
                "answer": "Black Moon Rising"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie stars Tommy Lee Jones and has the tag 'tommy lee jones'?",
                "answer": "The Three Burials of Melquiades Estrada"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie stars Tommy Lee Jones and has the tags 'tommy lee jones' and 'Rules of Engagement'?",
                "answer": "No such movie exists in the provided tuples."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was directed by Harley Cokeliss and stars an actor who also stars in a movie with the tag 'Rules of Engagement'?",
            "answer": "Black Moon Rising was directed by Harley Cokeliss and Tommy Lee Jones, who stars in The Three Burials of Melquiades Estrada and Rules of Engagement."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie Cheetah?",
                "answer": "Keith Coogan"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie Adventures in Babysitting?",
                "answer": "Keith Coogan, Anthony Rapp"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movies feature the star actors Keith Coogan and Anthony Rapp?",
            "answer": "Cheetah, Adventures in Babysitting"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Hello Down There'?",
                "answer": "Ivan Tors and John McGreevey"
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Ivan Tors write 'Hello Down There' alone?",
                "answer": "No, Ivan Tors co-wrote 'Hello Down There' with John McGreevey"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movies were written by either Ivan Tors or John McGreevey?",
            "answer": "The movies 'Hello Down There' were written by both Ivan Tors and John McGreevey."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'The First Grader'?",
                "answer": "Oliver Litondo"
            },
            {
                "question": "What tags are associated with 'The First Grader'?",
                "answer": "true story"
            },
            {
                "question": "What tags are associated with the number '21'?",
                "answer": "true story"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie does Kate Bosworth have a starring role in and what number is associated with a true story tag?",
                "answer": "Kate Bosworth starred in the movie '21' and '21' is associated with a true story tag."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Who starred in the movie 'The First Grader', and which movie shares a true story tag with the number '21' and also has Kate Bosworth as a starring actor?",
            "answer": "Oliver Litondo starred in the movie 'The First Grader'. Kate Bosworth starred in the movie '21', which shares a true story tag with the number '21'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Was Robert Holles involved in writing Guns at Batasi?",
                "answer": "Yes, Robert Holles was a writer for Guns at Batasi."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which actors starred in Guns at Batasi?",
                "answer": "Jack Hawkins starred in Guns at Batasi."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movies did Jack Hawkins appear in?",
                "answer": "Jack Hawkins starred in Land of the Pharaohs."
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the format of Land of the Pharaohs?",
                "answer": "The format of Land of the Pharaohs is Blu-ray Disc (BD-R)."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which other movie shares the same format as Rocco and His Brothers?",
                "answer": "Land of the Pharaohs shares the same format (Blu-ray Disc - BD-R) as Rocco and His Brothers."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actor starred in a movie written by Robert Holles and appeared in another movie that shares the same format as Rocco and His Brothers?",
            "answer": "Jack Hawkins starred in Guns at Batasi, which was written by Robert Holles, and also appeared in Land of the Pharaohs, which shares the same format (Blu-ray Disc - BD-R) as Rocco and His Brothers."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Above the Rim'?",
                "answer": "Barry Michael Cooper"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was starred by Duane Martin?",
                "answer": "Above the Rim"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was starred by Duane Martin and released in 2003?",
                "answer": "Deliver Us from Eva"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was released in the same year as 'Deliver Us from Eva'?",
                "answer": "How to Lose a Guy in 10 Days"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Above the Rim', starring Duane Martin, who also starred in the movie 'Deliver Us from Eva' which was released in the same year as 'How to Lose a Guy in 10 Days'?",
            "answer": "Barry Michael Cooper"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Was Phillip Schneider written by Swimfan?",
                "answer": "No, Phillip Schneider wrote Swimfan."
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the release year of Swimfan?",
                "answer": "The release year of Swimfan is 2002."
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the release year of Men with Brooms?",
                "answer": "The release year of Men with Brooms is also 2"
            }
        ],
        "complex": null
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "In what language is the movie 'After the Rain'?",
                "answer": "The movie 'After the Rain' is in Japanese."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what language is the movie 'Come See the Paradise'?",
                "answer": "The movie 'Come See the Paradise' is also in Japanese."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'Come See the Paradise' released?",
                "answer": "The movie 'Come See the Paradise' was released in the year 1990."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'The Asthenic Syndrome' released?",
                "answer": "The movie 'The Asthenic Syndrome' was released in the same year, 1990."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie, written by Kira Muratova, was released in 1990 and is in the same language as After the Rain?",
                "answer": "The movie 'The Asthenic Syndrome', written by Kira Muratova, was released in 1990 and is in Japanese, the same language as 'After the Rain'.\n\nComplex"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie written by Kira Muratova, in the same language as After the Rain and released in 1990, also shares its release year with Come See the Paradise?",
                "answer": "The movie 'The Asthenic Syndrome', written by Kira Muratova, is in Japanese, the same language as 'After the Rain', and was released in 1990, the same year as 'Come See the Paradise'."
            }
        ],
        "complex": null
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Betsy Drake star in Will Success Spoil Rock Hunter?",
                "answer": "Yes, Betsy Drake starred in Will Success Spoil Rock Hunter."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Jayne Mansfield star in Kiss Them for Me?",
                "answer": "Yes, Jayne Mansfield starred in Kiss Them for Me."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was Kiss Them for Me released?",
                "answer": "Kiss Them for Me was released in 1957."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Betsy Drake and Jayne Mansfield both star in a movie released in 1957 along with another actress?",
                "answer": "Yes, Betsy Drake and Jayne Mansfield both starred in the movie 'Will Success Spoil Rock Hunter?' along with Jayne Mansfield in 1957. And another movie 'The True Story of Jesse James' was also released in the same year 1957."
            }
        ],
        "complex": null
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'The End'?",
                "answer": "David Monteagudo and Jorge Guerricaechevarr\u00eda"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was written by Jorge Guerricaechevarr\u00eda?",
                "answer": "The End"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movies were written by David Monteagudo and Jorge Guerricaechevarr\u00eda?",
            "answer": "The End was written by both David Monteagudo and Jorge Guerricaechevarr\u00eda."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'The Phantom Light'?",
                "answer": "Milton Rosmer"
            },
            {
                "question": "What language is the movie 'The Phantom Light' in?",
                "answer": "Welsh"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the language of the movie 'The Corn Is Green'?",
                "answer": "Welsh"
            },
            {
                "question": "What genre is the movie 'The Corn Is Green'?",
                "answer": "Drama"
            },
            {
                "question": "What genre does the movie 'Drama' belong to?",
                "answer": "Doing Time on Maple Drive belongs to the genre 'Drama'."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Who starred in the Welsh movie 'The Phantom Light' which has the same genre as 'The Corn Is Green' and 'Doing Time on Maple Drive'?",
            "answer": "Milton Rosmer starred in the Welsh movie 'The Phantom Light' which has the same genre as 'The Corn Is Green' and 'Doing Time on Maple Drive', which is 'Drama'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Was Michael Richter a writer for the movie Torn?",
                "answer": "Yes"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which actor starred in the movie Torn, which was written by Michael Richter?",
                "answer": "Faran Tahir"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actor starred in the movie Torn, which was written by Michael Richter and written by whom did Faran Tahir star in the movie Torn?",
            "answer": "Faran Tahir starred in the movie Torn, which was written by Michael Richter."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "What genre is the movie 'An American Werewolf in Paris'?",
                "answer": "The movie 'An American Werewolf in Paris' is a Comedy."
            },
            {
                "question": "What genre is the movie 'O Lucky Man!'?",
                "answer": "The movie 'O Lucky Man!' is a Drama."
            },
            {
                "question": "What genre is the movie 'Doing Time on Maple Drive'?",
                "answer": "The movie 'Doing Time on Maple Drive' is a Drama."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "What is the genre of the movie 'An American Werewolf in Paris', and who directed the movie 'Doing Time on Maple Drive'?",
            "answer": "The movie 'An American Werewolf in Paris' is a Comedy, and the movie 'Doing Time on Maple Drive' was directed by Ken Olin."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Balls of Fury'?",
                "answer": "Christopher Walken"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Excess Baggage'?",
                "answer": "Christopher Walken"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'Excess Baggage'?",
                "answer": "Marco Brambilla"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'Destricted'?",
                "answer": "Marco Brambilla"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'Destricted' and which movie was directed by that person?",
                "answer": "Marco Brambilla directed both 'Destricted' and 'Excess Baggage'."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movies were starred by Christopher Walken and which movies were directed by the person who directed 'Excess Baggage'?",
                "answer": "Christopher Walken starred in 'Balls of Fury' and 'Excess Baggage'. Marco Brambilla directed 'Excess Baggage' and 'Destricted'."
            }
        ],
        "complex": null
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Irene Chen star in The Home Song Stories?",
                "answer": "Yes, Irene Chen starred in The Home Song Stories."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote The Home Song Stories?",
                "answer": "Tony Ayres wrote The Home Song Stories."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Who wrote The Home Song Stories, and did Irene Chen star in it?",
            "answer": "Tony Ayres wrote The Home Song Stories, and Yes, Irene Chen starred in The Home Song Stories."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'The Call of Cthulhu'?",
                "answer": "Andrew Leman"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'The Whisperer in Darkness'?",
                "answer": "Andrew Leman"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'The Whisperer in Darkness' released?",
                "answer": "2011"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'The Well-Digger's Daughter' released?",
                "answer": "2011"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie starred the actor Daniel Auteuil and was released in 2011?",
                "answer": "The Well-Digger's Daughter"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie directed by the person who wrote 'The Whisperer in Darkness' and released in the same year as 'The Well-Digger's Daughter' was starred by the actor Daniel Auteuil?",
            "answer": "The Whisperer in Darkness"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Does Ingmar Bergman's movie 'Shame' have Max von Sydow in it?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Max von Sydow act in the movie 'Hawaii'?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Julie Andrews star in the movie 'Hawaii'?",
                "answer": "No, she starred in 'S.O.B.'."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Ingmar Bergman's movie 'Shame' have any connection with Julie Andrews' movie 'S.O.B.'?",
            "answer": "Yes, they both starred Max von Sydow."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Was Michael Radford written by Dancing at the Blue Iguana?",
                "answer": "No, the relation is in the opposite direction. Dancing at the Blue Iguana was written by Michael Radford."
            },
            {
                "question": "What tags does Dancing at the Blue Iguana have?",
                "answer": "Dancing at the Blue Iguana has the tag 'strippers'."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie, written by Michael Radford, has the tag 'strippers'?",
            "answer": "Dancing at the Blue Iguana was written by Michael Radford and has the tag 'strippers'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Does Sharon Stone have any tags?",
                "answer": "Yes, Sharon Stone has the tag 'Intersection'."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was written by Claude Sautet?",
                "answer": "The movie 'Intersection' was written by Claude Sautet."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which language is the movie 'The Things of Life' in?",
                "answer": "The movie 'The Things of Life' is in the French language."
            },
            {
                "question": "Can you tell me a chain of information starting from Sharon Stone and ending with the language of 'Two Men in Manhattan'?",
                "answer": "Sharon Stone has the tag 'Intersection', 'Intersection' was written by Claude Sautet, Claude Sautet also wrote 'The Things of Life', 'The Things of Life' is in the French language, and the French language is also used in 'Two Men in Manhattan'.\nAnswer:"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Starting from Sharon Stone, can you trace a path to a connection with 'Two Men in Manhattan' and mention the language used in 'Two Men in Manhattan'?",
            "answer": "Yes, Sharon Stone has the tag 'Intersection', 'Intersection' was written by Claude Sautet, Claude Sautet also wrote 'The Things of Life' which is in the French language, and the French language is used in 'Two Men in Manhattan'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie \"Where's Poppa?\"?",
                "answer": "Robert Klane"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie did Ruth Gordon star in?",
                "answer": "Where's Poppa?"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie \"The Marrying Kind\"?",
                "answer": "Ruth Gordon"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie did Aldo Ray star in?",
                "answer": "The Marrying Kind"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie \"Dead Heat on a Merry-Go-Round\"?",
                "answer": "Aldo Ray"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was written by the person who starred in \"The Marrying Kind\" and also starred in the movie written by the person who wrote \"Where's Poppa?\"?",
            "answer": "Dead Heat on a Merry-Go-Round\nAnswer Explanation: The Marrying Kind was written by Ruth Gordon and she starred in Where's Poppa?, which was written by Robert Klane. Aldo Ray starred in Dead Heat on a Merry-Go-Round, which connects all the given tuples."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie Reality?",
                "answer": "Loredana Simioli"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was written by Matteo Garrone?",
                "answer": "Reality"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was written by the writer of Reality?",
                "answer": "First Love"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movies were written by the same writer as First Love?",
                "answer": "The movie written by the same writer as First Love is Reality."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was starred by an actor who appeared in a film written by the writer of Reality and First Love?",
            "answer": "Reality was starred by an actor who appeared in a film written by the writer of Reality and First Love. (Loredana Simioli appeared in Reality and the movie was written by Matteo Garrone, who also wrote First Love)"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie Lucrezia Borgia?",
                "answer": "Gabriel Gabrio"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie Lucrezia Borgia released?",
                "answer": "1935"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie I Dream Too Much released?",
                "answer": "1935"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie I Dream Too Much?",
                "answer": "John Cromwell"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie Of Human Bondage?",
                "answer": "John Cromwell"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie directed by John Cromwell in 1935, where Gabriel Gabrio starred in a film released the same year as I Dream Too Much, is called Lucrezia Borgia?",
            "answer": "Lucrezia Borgia"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Does Hiroshi Koizumi have any tags related to movies?",
                "answer": "Yes, Hiroshi Koizumi has the tag 'Mothra'."
            },
            {
                "question": "When was the movie 'Mothra' released?",
                "answer": "The movie 'Mothra' was released in the year 1961."
            },
            {
                "question": "In which year was the movie 'A Woman Is a Woman' released?",
                "answer": "The movie 'A Woman Is a Woman' was released in the year 1961."
            },
            {
                "question": "What genre does the movie 'A Woman Is a Woman' belong to?",
                "answer": "The movie 'A Woman Is a Woman' belongs to the genre 'Comedy'."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie belongs to the genre 'O Lucky Man!'?",
                "answer": "The movie 'O Lucky Man!' belongs to the genre 'Comedy'."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was released in 1961 and has the same genre as the movie 'O Lucky Man!'?",
            "answer": "The movie 'A Woman Is a Woman' was released in 1961 and belongs to the genre 'Comedy', which is the same as the genre of 'O Lucky Man!'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie '10,000 BC'?",
                "answer": "Roland Emmerich"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was written by Roland Emmerich?",
                "answer": "Stargate"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie did Viveca Lindfors star in?",
                "answer": "Stargate"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie did Viveca Lindfors and Tom Tryon both star in?",
                "answer": "The Story of Ruth"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was written by the person who also wrote the movie starred by the actor who starred in a movie with Tom Tryon?",
            "answer": "The Story of Ruth was written by the person who also wrote the movie '10,000 BC', which is Roland Emmerich."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Was Kevin Grevioux a writer for I, Frankenstein?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie I, Frankenstein?",
                "answer": "Kevin Grevioux and Stuart Beattie."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Stuart Beattie write Tomorrow, When the War Began?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie did Caitlin Stasey star in, that was written by Stuart Beattie?",
                "answer": "Tomorrow, When the War Began."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was written by Kevin Grevioux and Stuart Beattie, and starred Caitlin Stasey?",
            "answer": "Tomorrow, When the War Began. Answer based on the given tuples, but according to the knowledge graph, Caitlin Stasey did not star in I, Frankenstein."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Lena Headey star in the movie 300?",
                "answer": "Yes, Lena Headey starred in the movie 300."
            },
            {
                "question": "What are the tags for the movie 300?",
                "answer": "The tags for the movie 300 include thermopylae."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Lena Headey star in a movie related to thermopylae?",
            "answer": "Yes, Lena Headey starred in the movie 300, which has the tag thermopylae."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie Lassie Come Home?",
                "answer": "Eric Knight"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie Lassie Come Home?",
                "answer": "Fred M. Wilcox"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie Forbidden Planet?",
                "answer": "Fred M. Wilcox"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie did Warren Stevens star in?",
                "answer": "Forbidden Planet"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was written by Eric Knight, directed by Fred M. Wilcox and starred Warren Stevens?",
            "answer": "Forbidden Planet was written by Eric Knight, directed by Fred M. Wilcox and starred Warren Stevens."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie The Faculty?",
                "answer": "Laura Harris"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actors starred in the movies mentioned in the knowledge graph?",
            "answer": "The knowledge graph does not provide a list of movies, but based on the given tuple, Laura Harris starred in the movie The Faculty."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "What movie did Norman Taurog have the direction credit for?",
                "answer": "The Broadway Melody of 1940"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the Broadway Melody of 1940?",
                "answer": "Norman Taurog"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was directed by Norman Taurog and released in 1938?",
                "answer": "The Adventures of Tom Sawyer"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie Boy Meets Girl released?",
                "answer": "1938"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was directed by Norman Taurog and released in the same year as Boy Meets Girl?",
            "answer": "The Adventures of Tom Sawyer, which was released in 1938."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'The Case of the Lucky Legs' released?",
                "answer": "1935"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'I Dream Too Much' released?",
                "answer": "1935"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'I Dream Too Much'?",
                "answer": "John Cromwell"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'Of Human Bondage'?",
                "answer": "John Cromwell"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'Of Human Bondage' released?",
                "answer": "1934"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "In what year were the movies 'The Case of the Lucky Legs' and 'Of Human Bondage' released, and who directed 'I Dream Too Much' and 'Of Human Bondage'?",
            "answer": "The Case of the Lucky Legs was released in 1935, Of Human Bondage was released in 1934, and John Cromwell directed both I Dream Too Much and Of Human Bondage."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Richard Jordan star in Raise the Titanic?",
                "answer": "Yes, Richard Jordan starred in Raise the Titanic."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Jason Robards star in Divorce American Style?",
                "answer": "Yes, Jason Robards starred in Divorce American Style."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote The Night They Raided Minsky's?",
                "answer": "Norman Lear"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Richard Jordan and Jason Robards both star in a movie that was written by the same person who wrote \"The Night They Raided Minsky's\"?",
            "answer": "Yes, Richard Jordan starred in Raise the Titanic and Jason Robards starred in Divorce American Style, which were both written by Norman Lear who also wrote \"The Night They Raided Minsky's\"."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie K-PAX?",
                "answer": "Gene Brewer"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie K-PAX?",
                "answer": "Iain Softley"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which genre is the movie The Wings of the Dove?",
                "answer": "Drama"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which genre is the movie that was directed by the person who also directed the movie K-PAX, written by Gene Brewer and is known as K-PAX?",
            "answer": "The genre of the movie that was directed by Iain Softley, written by Gene Brewer and is known as K-PAX, is Drama. (Note: This is inferred from the provided tuples, as there is no direct relation between Gene Brewer, K-PAX and the genre Drama. The Wings of the Dove is connected to Drama and Iain Softley, who directed K-PAX.)"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Sleep with Me'?",
                "answer": "Rory Kelly"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie did Craig Sheffer star in?",
                "answer": "Sleep with Me"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie did Tom Skerritt star in with Craig Sheffer?",
                "answer": "A River Runs Through It"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie did Tom Skerritt star in, and who also starred in 'Redwood Highway'?",
                "answer": "Tom Skerritt starred in 'A River Runs Through It' and Craig Sheffer starred in 'Redwood Highway'."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Who wrote 'Sleep with Me', and which movie did the starred actor of 'Sleep with Me' star in with the starred actor of 'A River Runs Through It' who also starred in 'Redwood Highway'?",
            "answer": "Rory Kelly wrote 'Sleep with Me', and Craig Sheffer starred in 'Sleep with Me' with Tom Skerritt who also starred in 'A River Runs Through It' and 'Redwood Highway'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Bats star in Above the Rim?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Leon star in Deliver Us from Eva?",
                "answer": "No."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Duane Martin star in a movie released in 2003?",
                "answer": "Yes, Deliver Us from Eva."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Bats, who starred in a movie with Leon, also star in a movie with Duane Martin, who in turn starred in a movie released in 2003 with Gabrielle Union?",
            "answer": "Yes."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Robyn Lively star in The Karate Kid, Part III?",
                "answer": "Yes, Robyn Lively starred in The Karate Kid, Part III."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed The Karate Kid, Part III?",
                "answer": "John G. Avildsen directed The Karate Kid, Part III."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did John G. Avildsen direct Happy New Year?",
                "answer": "Yes, John G. Avildsen directed Happy New Year."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in Happy New Year?",
                "answer": "Claude Lelouch starred in Happy New Year."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed A Man and a Woman?",
                "answer": "Claude Lelouch directed A Man and a Woman."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Robyn Lively, who starred in The Karate Kid, Part III, which was directed by John G. Avildsen, who also directed Happy New Year, where Claude Lelouch starred, and he himself directed A Man and a Woman?",
            "answer": "Yes."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'The Longshots'?",
                "answer": "Fred Durst"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie did Ice Cube star in?",
                "answer": "The Longshots"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie did Ice Cube star in and who directed it?",
                "answer": "Ice Cube starred in the movie 'The Longshots' and it was directed by Fred Durst."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'Are We Done Yet?'?",
                "answer": "Steve Carr"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie did Steve Carr direct and who starred in it?",
                "answer": "Steve Carr directed the movie 'Are We Done Yet?' and Ice Cube starred in it."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie did Steve Carr direct and who starred in it, and who directed 'The Longshots' where this actor starred?",
                "answer": "Steve Carr directed the movie 'Are We Done Yet?' and Ice Cube starred in it. Steve Carr also directed 'Next Friday'. The movie 'The Longshots', where Ice Cube starred, was directed by Fred Durst."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Who directed 'Next Friday' and which movie was directed by the same person where Ice Cube starred in a movie directed by Fred Durst?",
            "answer": "Steve Carr directed 'Next Friday' and 'Are We Done Yet?', where Ice Cube starred. Ice Cube also starred in the movie 'The Longshots' which was directed by Fred Durst."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'The Assault'?",
                "answer": "Fons Rademakers"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie did Monique van de Ven star in?",
                "answer": "The Assault"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie does Monique van de Ven star in along with Turkish Delight?",
                "answer": "The Assault and Turkish Delight"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'Turkish Delight'?",
                "answer": "Paul Verhoeven"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie did Paul Verhoeven direct along with Spetters?",
                "answer": "Turkish Delight and Spetters"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was directed by Paul Verhoeven and starred Monique van de Ven who also starred in a movie directed by Fons Rademakers?",
            "answer": "Turkish Delight and The Assault"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Mar\u00eda Alche star in The Holy Girl?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Carlos Belloso star in The Holy Girl?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Mar\u00eda Alche and Carlos Belloso both star in The Holy Girl?",
            "answer": "Yes, Mar\u00eda Alche and Carlos Belloso both starred in The Holy Girl."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Daniel Olbrychski star in the movie Salt?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Chiwetel Ejiofor star in the movie Redbelt?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie did Daniel Olbrychski and Chiwetel Ejiofor both star in, that also has tags related to Chiwetel Ejiofor and the movie American Gangster?",
            "answer": "There is no such movie. Daniel Olbrychski starred in the movie Salt with Chiwetel Ejiofor, but the knowledge graph does not show any tags related to both Chiwetel Ejiofor and the movie American Gangster for either Salt or Redbelt."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Corruption'?",
                "answer": "Derek Ford"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which actress starred in the movie 'Corruption'?",
                "answer": "Kate O'Mara"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was written by Derek Ford and starred Kate O'Mara?",
            "answer": "Corruption"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie Capote?",
                "answer": "Philip Seymour Hoffman"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie The Ides of March?",
                "answer": "Philip Seymour Hoffman"
            },
            {
                "question": "What are some tags associated with the movie The Ides of March?",
                "answer": "evan rachel wood"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie Whatever Works?",
                "answer": "Evan Rachel Wood"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie Whatever Works and also appeared in the movie The Ides of March?",
                "answer": "Evan Rachel Wood"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Who starred in the movie Capote and has also appeared in a movie associated with the tag 'evan rachel wood' and starred in a movie with Larry David?",
            "answer": "Philip Seymour Hoffman"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Alexandra Hay star in Model Shop?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Gary Lockwood star in Model Shop?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did both Alexandra Hay and Gary Lockwood star in Model Shop?",
            "answer": "Yes, Alexandra Hay and Gary Lockwood both starred in Model Shop."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Keeping Mum'?",
                "answer": "Rowan Atkinson"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie starred Rowan Atkinson?",
                "answer": "The Witches"
            },
            {
                "question": "What are the tags of the movie 'The Witches'?",
                "answer": "bd-r"
            },
            {
                "question": "What movie has the tag 'bd-r' and which other movie shares this tag?",
                "answer": "The movie with the tag 'bd-r' is 'Rocco and His Brothers' and the other movie that shares this tag is 'The Witches'."
            },
            {
                "question": "In which year was 'Rocco and His Brothers' released?",
                "answer": "1960"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actor starred in 'Keeping Mum' and in which year was the movie 'Rocco and His Brothers', which shares a tag with 'The Witches', released?",
            "answer": "Rowan Atkinson starred in 'Keeping Mum' and 'Rocco and His Brothers' was released in 1960."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Does the movie 'Willow' have the tag 'sword and sorcery'?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Willow'?",
                "answer": "Bob Dolman"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was written by Bob Dolman and starred Nicole Kidman?",
                "answer": "Far and Away"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which sword and sorcery movie was written by the same person who wrote a movie starring Nicole Kidman, who in turn starred in a movie based on a book series?",
            "answer": "The movie 'Willow', which was tagged as 'sword and sorcery' and written by Bob Dolman, is connected to Nicole Kidman through the movie 'Far and Away', and ultimately to 'The Golden Compass' as it is based on a book series."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Cockneys vs Zombies'?",
                "answer": "Matthias Hoene"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which director is known for writing the movie 'Cockneys vs Zombies'?",
            "answer": "Matthias Hoene is known for writing the movie 'Cockneys vs Zombies'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'Eight Days a Week' released?",
                "answer": "1997"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'I Think I Do' released?",
                "answer": "1997"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the genre of the movie 'I Think I Do'?",
                "answer": "Comedy"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the genre of the movie 'O Lucky Man!'?",
                "answer": "Drama"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "In what year were the movies 'Eight Days a Week' and 'I Think I Do' released, and what genres are associated with the movies 'I Think I Do' and 'O Lucky Man!'?",
            "answer": "The movies 'Eight Days a Week' and 'I Think I Do' were released in the year 1997. The genre associated with the movie 'I Think I Do' is Comedy, and the genre associated with the movie 'O Lucky Man!' is Drama."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'This Time Around'?",
                "answer": "Brian Austin Green"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actor starred in the movie 'This Time Around' and who is the leading actor in that movie?",
            "answer": "Brian Austin Green starred in the movie 'This Time Around'. However, I cannot determine if he is the leading actor as the knowledge graph does not provide that information."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "In what year was My Stepmother Is an Alien released?",
                "answer": "1988."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was Stand and Deliver released?",
                "answer": "1988."
            },
            {
                "question": "What type of setting does Stand and Deliver have?",
                "answer": "High school."
            },
            {
                "question": "What type of setting does John Tucker Must Die have?",
                "answer": "High school."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which actor starred in John Tucker Must Die?",
                "answer": "Sophia Bush."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "In what year were My Stepmother Is an Alien and Stand and Deliver released, and which actor starred in a high school movie with Sophia Bush?",
            "answer": "My Stepmother Is an Alien and Stand and Deliver were both released in 1988, and Sophia Bush starred in the high school movie John Tucker Must Die."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Was Jill Sprecher involved in writing \"Thirteen Conversations About One Thing\"?",
                "answer": "Yes, Jill Sprecher was a writer for \"Thirteen Conversations About One Thing\"."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was \"Thirteen Conversations About One Thing\" released?",
                "answer": "\"Thirteen Conversations About One Thing\" was released in the year 2001."
            },
            {
                "question": "Was \"God Is Great and I'm Not\" released in the same year as \"Thirteen Conversations About One Thing\"?",
                "answer": "Yes, \"God Is Great and I'm Not\" was also released in the year 2001."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Edouard Baer play a role in \"God Is Great and I'm Not\"?",
                "answer": "Yes, Edouard Baer was one of the starred actors in \"God Is Great and I'm Not\"."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Jill Sprecher write \"God Is Great and I'm Not\" and did Edouard Baer play a role in that movie, which was released in the same year as \"Thirteen Conversations About One Thing\"?",
            "answer": "No, Jill Sprecher was not involved in writing \"God Is Great and I'm Not\" and Edouard Baer's role in the movie is limited to \"God Is Great and I'm Not\", not \"Thirteen Conversations About One Thing\"."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "What genre is the movie 'Analyze This' tagged as?",
                "answer": "The movie 'Analyze This' is tagged as 'gangster'."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie does Billy Crystal star in?",
                "answer": "Billy Crystal stars in the movie 'Analyze This'."
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the genre of the movie '700 Sundays'?",
                "answer": "The genre of the movie '700 Sundays' is 'Biography'."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which genre does Billy Crystal's performance in '700 Sundays' belong to?",
                "answer": "Billy Crystal's performance in '700 Sundays' belongs to the genre 'Biography'."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "What genre of movie does Billy Crystal star in, that is tagged as 'gangster' and has a performance by him that also belongs to a genre associated with the movie 'Riding in Cars with Boys'?",
            "answer": "Billy Crystal stars in the 'gangster' tagged movie 'Analyze This', and his performance in '700 Sundays' belongs to the genre 'Biography', which is associated with the movie 'Riding in Cars with Boys'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "What genre is the movie Colonel Redl?",
                "answer": "Colonel Redl is a Drama."
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the genre of the movie Doing Time on Maple Drive?",
                "answer": "The genre of the movie Doing Time on Maple Drive is Drama."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie Doing Time on Maple Drive?",
                "answer": "Ken Olin directed the movie Doing Time on Maple Drive."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "What genre of movie is Colonel Redl, and who directed the Drama Doing Time on Maple Drive?",
            "answer": "Colonel Redl is a Drama, and Ken Olin directed the Drama Doing Time on Maple Drive."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie \"The Sky's the Limit\"?",
                "answer": "Edward H. Griffith"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie \"The Animal Kingdom\"?",
                "answer": "Edward H. Griffith"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie did Ann Harding star in?",
                "answer": "The Animal Kingdom"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie did Ann Harding and Myrna Loy both star in?",
                "answer": "Double Harness"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie \"Double Harness\"?",
                "answer": "Edward Poor Montgomery"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was directed by Edward H. Griffith, starred Ann Harding, and was written by Edward Poor Montgomery?",
            "answer": "Double Harness\nAnswer: The Animal Kingdom (if assuming only one movie meets all the criteria)"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'Sweet Home Alabama'?",
                "answer": "Andy Tennant"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'Anna and the King'?",
                "answer": "Andy Tennant"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'Anna and the King' released?",
                "answer": "1999"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'No One Writes to the Colonel' released?",
                "answer": "The release year for the movie 'No One Writes to the Colonel' is not provided, but it is known that the movie 'Anna and the King' was released in 1999."
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the language of the movie 'No One Writes to the Colonel'?",
                "answer": "Spanish"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie directed by Andy Tennant, released in the same year as 'No One Writes to the Colonel' and in a language other than Spanish, is it 'Anna and the King' or 'Sweet Home Alabama'?",
            "answer": "The movie 'Anna and the King' was directed by Andy Tennant and released in 1999, which matches the given conditions. However, the language of 'Anna and the King' is not specified in the provided tuples, but 'No One Writes to the Colonel' is confirmed to be in Spanish. Therefore, 'Anna and the King' was released in 1999, in a language different from Spanish. We cannot confirm if it's specifically in a different language than Spanish, as the exact language is not provided for 'Anna and the King'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Romy Schneider star in Good Neighbor Sam?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Dorothy Provine star in Good Neighbor Sam?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Romy Schneider and Dorothy Provine both star in Good Neighbor Sam?",
            "answer": "Yes, Romy Schneider and Dorothy Provine both starred in Good Neighbor Sam."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Carmen Maura star in What Have I Done to Deserve This?",
                "answer": "Yes, Carmen Maura starred in What Have I Done to Deserve This."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what language is What Have I Done to Deserve This?",
                "answer": "What Have I Done to Deserve This is in Spanish."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what language is Women on the Verge of a Nervous Breakdown?",
                "answer": "Women on the Verge of a Nervous Breakdown is also in Spanish."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Antonio Banderas star in Women on the Verge of a Nervous Breakdown?",
                "answer": "No, Antonio Banderas did not star in Women on the Verge of a Nervous Breakdown."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Antonio Banderas star in Aut\u00f3mata?",
                "answer": "Yes, Antonio Banderas starred in Aut\u00f3mata."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which Spanish movie starring Carmen Maura has Antonio Banderas also starred in a later movie directed in the same language?",
            "answer": "Women on the Verge of a Nervous Breakdown is a Spanish movie where Carmen Maura starred, and Antonio Banderas later starred in the Spanish movie Aut\u00f3mata."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Held Up'?",
                "answer": "Jamie Foxx"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Law Abiding Citizen'?",
                "answer": "Jamie Foxx"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Law Abiding Citizen'?",
                "answer": "Kurt Wimmer"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Equilibrium'?",
                "answer": "Kurt Wimmer"
            },
            {
                "question": "Is Emily Watson associated with the movie 'Equilibrium'?",
                "answer": "Yes, 'Equilibrium' has the tag 'emily watson'"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Is Emily Watson associated with any movie that Jamie Foxx starred in, or any movie written by Kurt Wimmer?",
            "answer": "No, Emily Watson is not directly associated with any movie that Jamie Foxx starred in, or any movie written by Kurt Wimmer, based on the given knowledge graph."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Was Olaug Nilssen involved in writing the movie 'Turn Me On, Dammit!'?",
                "answer": "Yes, Olaug Nilssen was involved in writing 'Turn Me On, Dammit!'"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'Turn Me On, Dammit!' released?",
                "answer": "The movie 'Turn Me On, Dammit!' was released in the year 2011."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie \"The Well-Digger's Daughter\" released?",
                "answer": "The movie \"The Well-Digger's Daughter\" was released in the year 2011."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie starred the actor Daniel Auteuil?",
                "answer": "The actor Daniel Auteuil starred in the movie \"The Well-Digger's Daughter\"."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie did the actor Daniel Auteuil star in, that was also released in the same year as 'Turn Me On, Dammit!'?",
                "answer": "The actor Daniel Auteuil starred in the movie \"The Well-Digger's Daughter\" which was released in the same year as 'Turn Me On, Dammit!', which is 2011."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actor starred in a movie written by Olaug Nilssen and released in the same year as 'The Well-Digger's Daughter'?",
            "answer": "There is no actor who starred in a movie written by Olaug Nilssen and released in the same year as 'The Well-Digger's Daughter' as there is no such movie written by Olaug Nilssen that was released in 2011."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Was Maurice Valency a writer for The Visit?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie did Ingrid Bergman star in, called The Visit?",
                "answer": "The Visit."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie did Ingrid Bergman star in, known as For Whom the Bell Tolls?",
                "answer": "For Whom the Bell Tolls."
            },
            {
                "question": "What are the tags for the movie For Whom the Bell Tolls?",
                "answer": "The tag for For Whom the Bell Tolls is 'ingrid bergman'."
            },
            {
                "question": "What are the tags for Ingrid Bergman?",
                "answer": "The tags for Ingrid Bergman are 'The Bells of St. Mary's' and 'ingrid bergman'."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Who wrote The Visit and what are the tags for the movies that Ingrid Bergman starred in and the tags for Ingrid Bergman herself?",
            "answer": "Maurice Valency wrote The Visit. The tags for the movies that Ingrid Bergman starred in are 'ingrid bergman' and 'The Bells of St. Mary's'. The tags for Ingrid Bergman are 'The Bells of St. Mary's' and 'ingrid bergman'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Dwayne Hickman star in How to Stuff a Wild Bikini?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Brian Donlevy star in Command Decision?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did George Froeschel write The Story of Three Loves?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Dwayne Hickman and Brian Donlevy both star in a movie written by George Froeschel?",
            "answer": "No, Dwayne Hickman starred in How to Stuff a Wild Bikini, which was not written by George Froeschel. Brian Donlevy starred in Command Decision, which was written by George Froeschel, but Hickman did not star in that movie."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie Bachelor Party?",
                "answer": "Adrian Zmed"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actor appeared in the movie Bachelor Party and can you name the movie?",
            "answer": "Adrian Zmed starred in the movie Bachelor Party."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie Little Boy Blue?",
                "answer": "Antonio Tibaldi"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie Little Boy Blue released?",
                "answer": "1997"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie I Think I Do released?",
                "answer": "1997"
            },
            {
                "question": "What genre is the movie I Think I Do?",
                "answer": "Comedy"
            },
            {
                "question": "What genre is the movie O Lucky Man!?",
                "answer": "Comedy"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was directed by Antonio Tibaldi and was released in the same year as the comedy movie I Think I Do and shares its genre with the movie O Lucky Man!?",
            "answer": "Little Boy Blue and O Lucky Man! share the same genre 'Comedy' with I Think I Do and were released in the same year '1997' as I Think I Do. However, Little Boy Blue was directed by Antonio Tibaldi."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie Sealed Cargo?",
                "answer": "Edmund Gilligan"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which person wrote the movie Sealed Cargo and what other movies were written by this individual?",
            "answer": "Edmund Gilligan wrote the movie Sealed Cargo. I don't have information about other movies written by this individual."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Theresa Russell'?",
                "answer": "Theresa Russell starred in the movie 'Physical Evidence'."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Physical Evidence'?",
                "answer": "Burt Reynolds starred in the movie 'Physical Evidence'."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Burt Reynolds'?",
                "answer": "Burt Reynolds starred in the movie 'Paternity'."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Paternity'?",
                "answer": "Beverly D'Angelo starred in the movie 'Paternity'."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Beverly D'Angelo'?",
                "answer": "Beverly D'Angelo starred in the movie \"National Lampoon's Vacation\"."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actors starred in the movies 'Theresa Russell', 'Physical Evidence', 'Burt Reynolds', 'Paternity', and \"Beverly D'Angelo\"?",
            "answer": "Theresa Russell starred in 'Physical Evidence', Burt Reynolds starred in 'Physical Evidence' and 'Paternity', Beverly D'Angelo starred in 'Paternity' and \"National Lampoon's Vacation\". Answer the following question: \"Who starred in the movie 'Theresa Russell'?\"\nAnswer: Theresa Russell starred in the movie 'Physical Evidence'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'Lilies of the Field'?",
                "answer": "Ralph Nelson"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who was directed by Ralph Nelson in the movie 'Duel at Diablo'?",
                "answer": "Not applicable, Ralph Nelson is the director of 'Duel at Diablo'."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Duel at Diablo'?",
                "answer": "Marvin H. Albert"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who was written by Marvin H. Albert in the movie 'Lady in Cement'?",
                "answer": "Not applicable, Marvin H. Albert is the writer of 'Lady in Cement'."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'Lady in Cement'?",
                "answer": "Gordon Douglas"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Can you tell me about the connection between all these entities?",
            "answer": "Sure, 'Lilies of the Field' was directed by Ralph Nelson. Ralph Nelson also directed 'Duel at Diablo', which was written by Marvin H. Albert. Marvin H. Albert also wrote 'Lady in Cement', which was directed by Gordon Douglas. So, we have a chain of director and writer connections between these movies."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Where the Wild Things Are'?",
                "answer": "Max Records"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is one of the tags for the movie 'Where the Wild Things Are'?",
                "answer": "lauren ambrose"
            },
            {
                "question": "What movie has a tag associated with 'lauren ambrose'?",
                "answer": "Can't Hardly Wait"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who is one of the writers of the movie 'Can't Hardly Wait'?",
                "answer": "Deborah Kaplan"
            },
            {
                "question": "What movie has Deborah Kaplan as one of its writers?",
                "answer": "Josie and the Pussycats"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was starred by Max Records and has Deborah Kaplan as one of its writers through a chain of tags and written_by relations?",
            "answer": "Josie and the Pussycats\nAnswer Explanation: Max Records starred in 'Where the Wild Things Are', one of the tags for this movie is 'lauren ambrose'. Lauren ambrose is connected to 'Can't Hardly Wait' movie, which has Deborah Kaplan as one of its writers, and Deborah Kaplan also wrote 'Josie and the Pussycats'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'So Much So Fast'?",
                "answer": "Jeanne Jordan"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the genre of the movie 'So Much So Fast'?",
                "answer": "Documentary"
            },
            {
                "question": "What movie shares a genre with 'Documentary'?",
                "answer": "10 Questions for the Dalai Lama"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie '10 Questions for the Dalai Lama'?",
                "answer": "Rick Ray"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Who wrote the movies 'So Much So Fast' and '10 Questions for the Dalai Lama'?",
            "answer": "Jeanne Jordan and Rick Ray"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Was Anthony Minghella the writer of Cold Mountain?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "What movies or TV shows has Anthony Minghella been tagged in?",
                "answer": "Cold Mountain and The English Patient."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was The English Patient released?",
                "answer": "1996."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie or TV show was released in the same year as Beyond Hypothermia and was written by Anthony Minghella?",
                "answer": "The English Patient.\n\nAnswer:"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie or TV show was released in the same year as Beyond Hypothermia, was written by the person who also wrote Cold Mountain, and was the movie that Anthony Minghella was tagged in?",
            "answer": "The English Patient."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie Macabre?",
                "answer": "William Prince"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was directed by William Castle?",
                "answer": "Macabre"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was directed by William Castle and written by Ursula Curtiss?",
                "answer": "I Saw What You Did"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie What Ever Happened to Aunt Alice?",
                "answer": "Ursula Curtiss"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was directed by William Castle, starred William Prince, and was written by Ursula Curtiss who also wrote What Ever Happened to Aunt Alice?",
            "answer": "I Saw What You Did"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "What genre is the movie Jauja?",
                "answer": "Jauja is a Drama."
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the genre of the movie Doing Time on Maple Drive?",
                "answer": "Doing Time on Maple Drive is a Drama."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie Doing Time on Maple Drive?",
                "answer": "Ken Olin"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "What genre of movie was directed by Ken Olin and can also be associated with the movie Jauja?",
            "answer": "Drama"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Was The Sterile Cuckoo written by John Nichols?",
                "answer": "Yes"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was The Sterile Cuckoo released?",
                "answer": "1969"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie I Like It Like That released?",
                "answer": "1994"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie written by John Nichols was released in the same year as Don't Drink the Water?",
            "answer": "The Sterile Cuckoo and Don't Drink the Water were both released in the year 1969."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Does the production of 'The Dark Knight Rises' have any tags?",
                "answer": "Yes, the production of 'The Dark Knight Rises' has the tag 'The Dark Knight Rises'."
            },
            {
                "question": "Does 'The Dark Knight Rises' have any tags?",
                "answer": "Yes, 'The Dark Knight Rises' has the tag 'new york city'."
            },
            {
                "question": "Does 'new york city' have any tags?",
                "answer": "Yes, 'new york city' has the tag 'Definitely, Maybe'."
            },
            {
                "question": "Does 'Definitely, Maybe' have any tags?",
                "answer": "Yes, 'Definitely, Maybe' has the tag 'divorce'."
            },
            {
                "question": "Does 'divorce' have any tags?",
                "answer": "Yes, 'divorce' has the tag 'Under the Tuscan Sun'."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Does the production of 'The Dark Knight Rises' have any tags that are related to 'divorce' through the movie 'Under the Tuscan Sun'?",
            "answer": "Yes, the production of 'The Dark Knight Rises' has the tag 'new york city' which is related to 'Definitely, Maybe' and 'divorce' through the movie 'Definitely, Maybe' and finally to 'Under the Tuscan Sun'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Carl Ng star in Boarding Gate?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Michael Madsen star in Boarding Gate?",
                "answer": "Yes, he did."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Michael Madsen star in Piranhaconda?",
                "answer": "Yes, he did."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Rachel Hunter star in Piranhaconda?",
                "answer": "No, but she starred in a movie called 'Just a Little Harmless Sex'."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Carl Ng and Rachel Hunter both star in any movies together?",
                "answer": "No, they didn't. They starred in different movies."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Carl Ng and Rachel Hunter both star in any movies together with Michael Madsen?",
            "answer": "No, they didn't. Although Carl Ng starred in 'Boarding Gate' with Michael Madsen, Rachel Hunter starred in 'Just a Little Harmless Sex' which didn't have either of them."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'The First Grader'?",
                "answer": "Oliver Litondo"
            },
            {
                "question": "What tag is associated with 'The First Grader'?",
                "answer": "true story"
            },
            {
                "question": "What number is related to the tag 'true story'?",
                "answer": "21"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie does Kate Bosworth star in that is related to the number 21?",
                "answer": "21"
            },
            {
                "question": "In which movie does Kate Bosworth star along with Oliver Litondo?",
                "answer": "None, Kate Bosworth stars in '21' and Oliver Litondo stars in 'The First Grader', they do not star together in any movie."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie does Kate Bosworth star in, that tells a true story related to the number 21, where Oliver Litondo also stars?",
            "answer": "None, Kate Bosworth stars in '21' and Oliver Litondo stars in 'The First Grader', they do not star together in any movie and '21' is not a true story related to the number 21."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Hayley Atwell star in The Sweeney?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was The Sweeney released?",
                "answer": "2012."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was How to Make Money Selling Drugs released?",
                "answer": "Also 2012."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Susan Sarandon star in How to Make Money Selling Drugs?",
                "answer": "No, but she starred in The Great Waldo Pepper."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Hayley Atwell and Susan Sarandon both star in a movie that was released in 2012?",
            "answer": "No, they did not. Hayley Atwell starred in The Sweeney, which was released in 2"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Was Joe Simon written by Captain America?",
                "answer": "No, Joe Simon is the writer of Captain America."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was Captain America released?",
                "answer": "Captain America was released in the year 1979."
            },
            {
                "question": "Was All Quiet on the Western Front released in the year 1979?",
                "answer": "Yes, All Quiet on the Western Front was released in the year 1979."
            },
            {
                "question": "Does All Quiet on the Western Front have the tag 'national film registry'?",
                "answer": "Yes, All Quiet on the Western Front has the tag 'national film registry'."
            },
            {
                "question": "Does the 'national film registry' have the tag 'Swing Time'?",
                "answer": "Yes, the 'national film registry' has the tag 'Swing Time'."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Was Joe Simon involved in the creation of a movie that was released in 1979 and is part of the national film registry?",
            "answer": "No, Joe Simon's written work, Captain America, was not released in 1979 and is not part of the national film registry."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Standing Up'?",
                "answer": "Brock Cole"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which actors starred in the movie 'Standing Up'?",
                "answer": "Annalise Basso"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actors starred in the movie 'Standing Up', which was written by Brock Cole?",
            "answer": "Annalise Basso"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Does Shawn Levy have any tags related to 'Night at the Museum'?",
                "answer": "Yes, 'Night at the Museum' is one of the movies directed by Shawn Levy."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was directed by Shawn Levy, that he also has a 'has\\_tags' relationship with?",
                "answer": "'Night at the Museum'"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote 'Real Steel'?",
                "answer": "Richard Matheson"
            },
            {
                "question": "What movie was directed by Shawn Levy and was written by Richard Matheson?",
                "answer": "Real Steel"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Who wrote 'The Devil Rides Out' and which movie was directed by Shawn Levy, that he also has a 'has\\_tags' relationship with, and was written by the same writer of 'The Devil Rides Out'?",
            "answer": "Richard Matheson, Night at the Museum. The Devil Rides Out and Night at the Museum are both written by Richard Matheson, Night at the Museum is one of the movies directed by Shawn Levy, and he also has a 'has\\_tags' relationship with Night at the Museum."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Does the movie 'Spring Break' have the tag 'bd-r'?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Does the tag 'bd-r' have the tag 'Rocco and His Brothers'?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'Rocco and His Brothers' released?",
                "answer": "1960."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'Visit to a Small Planet' released?",
                "answer": "1960."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which actor starred in the movie 'Visit to a Small Planet'?",
                "answer": "Jerry Lewis."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actor starred in the movie that shares the same release year as 'Rocco and His Brothers' and is tagged as 'bd-r' in the 'Spring Break' movie?",
            "answer": "Jerry Lewis."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Tortured'?",
                "answer": "Nolan Lebovitz"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which individual is connected to Nolan Lebovitz through the movie 'Tortured'?",
            "answer": "The relation between Nolan Lebovitz and the movie 'Tortured' is 'written_by'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Three Smart Girls Grow Up'?",
                "answer": "Nan Grey"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'Three Smart Girls Grow Up'?",
                "answer": "Henry Koster"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie did Henry Koster direct in the year 1936?",
                "answer": "Three Smart Girls"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie directed by Henry Koster in 1936 did Nan Grey star in, that is a sequel to 'Three Smart Girls Grow Up'?",
            "answer": "There seems to be a misunderstanding in the input data. 'Three Smart Girls' was released in 1936 and directed by Henry Koster, but it's not a sequel to 'Three Smart Girls Grow Up'. Also, Nan Grey did not star in 'Three Smart Girls'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Does Patrick McGoohan have any tags related to movies?",
                "answer": "Yes, Patrick McGoohan has the tag 'Scanners'."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was written by David Cronenberg?",
                "answer": "Scanners was written by David Cronenberg."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was directed by David Cronenberg and starred Christopher Walken?",
                "answer": "The Dead Zone was directed by David Cronenberg and starred Christopher Walken."
            },
            {
                "question": "In which movies did Christopher Walken star?",
                "answer": "Christopher Walken starred in The Dead Zone and Excess Baggage."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was directed by the person who wrote the movie that Patrick McGoohan has a tag for and starred an actor who also starred in a movie directed by the writer of that movie?",
            "answer": "The Dead Zone was directed by David Cronenberg who wrote Scanners, the movie that Patrick McGoohan has a tag for. Additionally, Christopher Walken starred in The Dead Zone and also starred in Excess Baggage, a movie directed by David Cronenberg."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "What genre is the movie 'Man on the Moon'?",
                "answer": "The genre of 'Man on the Moon' is Drama."
            },
            {
                "question": "What genre is 'Doing Time on Maple Drive'?",
                "answer": "The genre of 'Doing Time on Maple Drive' is Drama."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'Doing Time on Maple Drive'?",
                "answer": "The movie 'Doing Time on Maple Drive' was directed by Ken Olin."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Who directed the movie 'Doing Time on Maple Drive' which shares a genre with the movie 'Man on the Moon' that has the tag 'courtney love'?",
            "answer": "Ken Olin directed the movie 'Doing Time on Maple Drive', which shares a genre with 'Man on the Moon', and has the tag 'courtney love'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'Madadayo' released?",
                "answer": "1993"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'Addams Family Values' released?",
                "answer": "1993"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Addams Family Values'?",
                "answer": "Paul Rudnick"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Isn't She Great'?",
                "answer": "Paul Rudnick"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'Isn't She Great' released, which was written by the same person who wrote 'Addams Family Values' and the movie 'Madadayo' was released in 1993?",
                "answer": "2000\n\nComplex Answer: 2000\nAnswer was derived from the tuples: (('Madadayo', 'release_year', '1993'), ('1993', 'release_year', 'Addams Family Values'), ('Addams Family Values', 'written_by', 'Paul Rudnick'), ('Paul Rudnick', 'written_by', \"Isn't She Great\"), (\"Isn't She Great\", 'release_year', '2000'))"
            }
        ],
        "complex": null
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Wendell Corey star in the movie Loving You?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie Loving You?",
                "answer": "Herbert Baker"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was written by Herbert Baker apart from Loving You?",
                "answer": "The Girl Can't Help It"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie The Girl Can't Help It released?",
                "answer": "1956"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was released in the same year as The Girl Can't Help It?",
                "answer": "Tension at Table Rock"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Wendell Corey star in a movie written by Herbert Baker that was released in the same year as Tension at Table Rock?",
            "answer": "Yes, Wendell Corey starred in the movie Loving You, which was written by Herbert Baker and released in the same year as Tension at Table Rock (1956)."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Does Stacy Peralta have any relation to the movie Dogtown and Z-Boys?",
                "answer": "Yes, Stacy Peralta has the tag 'Dogtown and Z-Boys'."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie Dogtown and Z-Boys?",
                "answer": "Dogtown and Z-Boys was written by Stacy Peralta."
            },
            {
                "question": "What movie was written by Stacy Peralta and has the tag 'skateboarding'?",
                "answer": "Lords of Dogtown"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was written by the person who has the tag 'Dogtown and Z-Boys' and also has the tag 'Grind' related to skateboarding?",
            "answer": "Lords of Dogtown"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "What genre is the movie with ID 1?",
                "answer": "The movie with ID 1 has the genre Drama."
            },
            {
                "question": "What movie has the genre Doing Time on Maple Drive?",
                "answer": "The movie Doing Time on Maple Drive has the genre Drama."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie Doing Time on Maple Drive?",
                "answer": "The movie Doing Time on Maple Drive was directed by Ken Olin."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "What is the genre of the movie with ID 1, and who directed the movie that has the same genre as Doing Time on Maple Drive?",
            "answer": "The movie with ID 1 has the genre Drama, and the movie Doing Time on Maple Drive, which shares the same genre as the movie with ID 1, was directed by Ken Olin."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'National Velvet'?",
                "answer": "Mickey Rooney"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'The Bridges at Toko-Ri'?",
                "answer": "Mickey Rooney"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'The Bridges at Toko-Ri' together with Mickey Rooney?",
                "answer": "Fredric March"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Design for Living'?",
                "answer": "Fredric March"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie starring Fredric March also has the tag 'fredric march'?",
                "answer": "Design for Living"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actors starred in movies together with Mickey Rooney and Fredric March?",
            "answer": "The Bridges at Toko-Ri (Mickey Rooney and Fredric March)"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "What genre is the movie \"It's Kind of a Funny Story\"?",
                "answer": "The movie \"It's Kind of a Funny Story\" has the tag/genre of Drama."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie \"Father of Invention\" released?",
                "answer": "The movie \"Father of Invention\" was released in the year 2010."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "What genre is the movie directed by Ryan Fleck that was released in the same year as \"Father of Invention\" and shares a genre with the movie \"Doing Time on Maple Drive\"?",
            "answer": "The movie directed by Ryan Fleck that was released in the same year as \"Father of Invention\" and shares a genre with the movie \"Doing Time on Maple Drive\" is \"It's Kind of a Funny Story\", and its genre is Drama."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Illegal Tender'?",
                "answer": "Franc. Reyes"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which person wrote the movie 'Illegal Tender' and what is the name of that movie?",
            "answer": "Franc. Reyes wrote 'Illegal Tender'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'The Human Race'?",
                "answer": "Eddie McGee"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'The Human Race'?",
                "answer": "Paul Hough"
            },
            {
                "question": "In which movie did Paul Hough star?",
                "answer": "The Backyard"
            },
            {
                "question": "When was the movie 'The Backyard' released?",
                "answer": "2002"
            },
            {
                "question": "In which year was the movie 'Men with Brooms' released?",
                "answer": "2002"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was written by Paul Hough and starred Eddie McGee, and what is the release year of the movie where Paul Hough was one of the actors and was released in the same year as 'Men with Brooms'?",
            "answer": "The Human Race was written by Paul Hough and starred Eddie McGee. The Backyard is the movie where Paul Hough was one of the actors and it was released in the same year as 'Men with Brooms', which is 2002."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Saving Sarah Cain'?",
                "answer": "Beverly Lewis"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'Saving Sarah Cain' released?",
                "answer": "2007"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was the movie 'For the Bible Tells Me So' released?",
                "answer": "2007"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was written by Daniel G. Karslake and released in the same year as 'Saving Sarah Cain'?",
                "answer": "For the Bible Tells Me So\n\nComplex"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote 'Saving Sarah Cain' and 'For the Bible Tells Me So' which were both released in 2007?",
                "answer": "Beverly Lewis and Daniel G. Karslake"
            }
        ],
        "complex": null
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "What genre is the movie Bicentennial Man?",
                "answer": "The genre of the movie Bicentennial Man is Drama."
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the genre of Drama?",
                "answer": "The genre of Drama includes movies like Doing Time on Maple Drive."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie Doing Time on Maple Drive?",
                "answer": "The movie Doing Time on Maple Drive was directed by Ken Olin."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Who directed the movie Bicentennial Man, which is a Drama and was written by Isaac Asimov?",
            "answer": "The movie Bicentennial Man, which is a Drama and was written by Isaac Asimov, was not directed by Ken Olin. (Note: The knowledge graph does not provide enough information to determine if Isaac Asimov directly wrote the movie Bicentennial Man or if he just provided the source material.)"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Was Breach written by Adam Mazer?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote Breach?",
                "answer": "Adam Mazer."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Billy Ray write The Hunger Games?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "What movie has the tag 'woody harrelson'?",
                "answer": "The Hunger Games."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was tagged with 'White Men Can't Jump' and was written by someone who also wrote a movie that was tagged with 'woody harrelson'?",
                "answer": "The Hunger Games was written by Billy Ray and it was tagged with 'woody harrelson'. Billy Ray also wrote 'Breach', but it wasn't tagged with 'White Men Can't Jump'. However, 'Breach' was written by Adam Mazer, who wrote 'Breach', which was tagged with 'woody harrelson'."
            }
        ],
        "complex": null
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Was Philippe Godeau involved in the writing of the movie '11.6'?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie did Fran\u00e7ois Cluzet star in, that was written by Philippe Godeau?",
                "answer": "'11.6'"
            },
            {
                "question": "In which movie did Fran\u00e7ois Cluzet and Guillaume Canet act together?",
                "answer": "They didn't act together in any of the given movies."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movies were written by Philippe Godeau and Guillaume Canet, and starred Fran\u00e7ois Cluzet and actors from their respective movies?",
                "answer": "'11.6' was written by Philippe Godeau and starred Fran\u00e7ois Cluzet. 'Little White Lies' was written by Guillaume Canet, but Fran\u00e7ois Cluzet didn't star in it. 'Hunting and Gathering' was written and starred by Guillaume Canet, but Fran\u00e7ois Cluzet didn't star in it either."
            }
        ],
        "complex": null
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "In what year was 'The Passion of Ayn Rand' released?",
                "answer": "1999."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what language was 'No One Writes to the Colonel' released?",
                "answer": "Spanish."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie starred Antonio Banderas?",
                "answer": "Women on the Verge of a Nervous Breakdown."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "In what language was 'The Passion of Ayn Rand' released, and which movie starred Antonio Banderas?",
            "answer": "The Passion of Ayn Rand was released in 1999, and Women on the Verge of a Nervous Breakdown starred Antonio Banderas, which was released in Spanish."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie The Marksman?",
                "answer": "Anthony Warren"
            },
            {
                "question": "What genre is the movie The Marksman?",
                "answer": "Action"
            },
            {
                "question": "What genre is the movie In China They Eat Dogs?",
                "answer": "Action"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie In China They Eat Dogs?",
                "answer": "Lasse Spang Olsen"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Anthony Warren star in a movie directed by Lasse Spang Olsen and is that movie an action film?",
            "answer": "No, Anthony Warren did not star in a movie directed by Lasse Spang Olsen and that movie is not an action film. (This answer is based on the provided knowledge graph, and there is no evidence that Anthony Warren starred in a movie directed by Lasse Spang Olsen, and In China They Eat Dogs, which is directed by Lasse Spang Olsen, is not an action film but rather a crime/comedy film.)"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Joker'?",
                "answer": "Shirish Kunder"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the language of the movie 'Joker'?",
                "answer": "Hindi"
            },
            {
                "question": "In what language was the movie 'Happy New Year' made?",
                "answer": "Hindi"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie starred Claude Lelouch?",
                "answer": "Happy New Year"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'A Man and a Woman'?",
                "answer": "Claude Lelouch"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actor was directed by Claude Lelouch and wrote the movie 'Joker' which was made in Hindi, the same language as 'Happy New Year'?",
            "answer": "Claude Lelouch was directed by Shirish Kunder. However, it's important to note that Shirish Kunder directed 'Joker' and Claude Lelouch acted in 'Happy New Year'. There's no common entity that both wrote and acted in movies made in Hindi."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie \"Floating Skyscrapers\"?",
                "answer": "Bartosz Gelner"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actor starred in the movie \"Floating Skyscrapers\" and can you name that movie?",
            "answer": "Bartosz Gelner starred in the movie \"Floating Skyscrapers\".\nAnswer: Bartosz Gelner starred in \"Floating Skyscrapers\"."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Does Jemaine Clement have any tags related to the movie Rio 2?",
                "answer": "Yes, Jemaine Clement has the tag 'Rio 2'."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was written by Don Rhymer?",
                "answer": "Rio 2"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which genre is associated with the movie Big Momma's House?",
                "answer": "Crime"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was written by Don Rhymer and shares a genre connection with Big Momma's House through the genre Crime, all the way to the movie He Ran All the Way?",
            "answer": "Rio 2 is the movie written by Don Rhymer that shares a genre connection with Big Momma's House through the Crime genre, ultimately connecting to He Ran All the Way."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "What year was the movie 'Force Majeure' released?",
                "answer": "The movie 'Force Majeure' was not released in the provided tuple."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was 'A Girl Walks Home Alone at Night' released?",
                "answer": "'A Girl Walks Home Alone at Night' was released in 2014."
            },
            {
                "question": "What country is 'A Girl Walks Home Alone at Night' associated with?",
                "answer": "'A Girl Walks Home Alone at Night' is associated with Iran."
            },
            {
                "question": "In what year was 'The Song of Sparrows' released?",
                "answer": "'The Song of Sparrows' was released in 2008."
            },
            {
                "question": "What movies were released in the same year as 'The Song of Sparrows' and are associated with Iran?",
                "answer": "'A Girl Walks Home Alone at Night' was released in the same year as 'The Song of Sparrows' and is associated with Iran."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "What movie released in 2014 is associated with a country that also has a movie called 'The Song of Sparrows', released in 2008?",
            "answer": "'A Girl Walks Home Alone at Night' was released in 2014 and is associated with Iran, which also has a movie called 'The Song of Sparrows', released in 2008."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Something Wicked This Way Comes'?",
                "answer": "Diane Ladd"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Carnosaur'?",
                "answer": "Diane Ladd"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Carnosaur'?",
                "answer": "John Brosnan"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actor starred in 'Something Wicked This Way Comes' and was also in a movie written by John Brosnan?",
            "answer": "Diane Ladd starred in 'Something Wicked This Way Comes' and was also in the movie 'Carnosaur', which was written by John Brosnan."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did Aldo Giuffr\u00e8 star in The Four Days of Naples?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Jean Sorel star in Short Night of Glass Dolls?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Aldo Lado write The Humanoid?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Did Aldo Giuffr\u00e8 and Jean Sorel both star in a movie written by Aldo Lado?",
            "answer": "Yes, Aldo Giuffr\u00e8 starred in \"The Four Days of Naples\" and Jean Sorel starred in \"Short Night of Glass Dolls\", both of which were written by Aldo Lado."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Did David Bennent star in the movie Legend?",
                "answer": "Yes."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was directed by Ridley Scott, where David Bennent starred?",
                "answer": "Legend"
            },
            {
                "question": "In which movie did Ridley Scott and David Bennent collaborate in the year 1996?",
                "answer": "The movie is White Squall."
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was released in the same year as Beyond Hypothermia, and was directed by Ridley Scott where David Bennent starred in the movie Legend?",
                "answer": "White Squall and Beyond Hypothermia were both released in the year 1996. While David Bennent starred in Legend, which was directed by Ridley Scott."
            }
        ],
        "complex": null
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Some Girls'?",
                "answer": "Patrick Dempsey"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Lucky 7'?",
                "answer": "Patrick Dempsey"
            },
            {
                "question": "What are the tags for the movie 'Lucky 7'?",
                "answer": "patrick dempsey"
            },
            {
                "question": "What are the tags for the actor 'patrick dempsey'?",
                "answer": "Can't Buy Me Love"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who directed the movie 'Can't Buy Me Love'?",
                "answer": "Steve Rash"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actor starred in the movie 'Some Girls' and was also tagged in the movie 'Lucky 7', and directed the movie 'Can't Buy Me Love'?",
            "answer": "Patrick Dempsey was tagged in the movie 'Lucky 7' and he starred in the movie 'Some Girls'. He also directed the movie 'Can't Buy Me Love'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in Tarzan's Greatest Adventure?",
                "answer": "Anthony Quayle and Gordon Scott"
            },
            {
                "question": "In which movie did Anthony Quayle act?",
                "answer": "Tarzan's Greatest Adventure"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who are the actors in the same movie as Gordon Scott?",
                "answer": "Anthony Quayle"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie did Anthony Quayle and Gordon Scott both star in?",
            "answer": "Tarzan's Greatest Adventure"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Under the Skin'?",
                "answer": "Walter Campbell"
            },
            {
                "question": "<not provided>",
                "answer": "<not provided>"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was written by Walter Campbell?",
            "answer": "Under the Skin"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Black Christmas'?",
                "answer": "Keir Dullea"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Mail Order Bride'?",
                "answer": "Keir Dullea"
            },
            {
                "question": "What are the tags for the format 'bd-r'?",
                "answer": "Rocco and His Brothers"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the release year of 'Rocco and His Brothers'?",
                "answer": "1960"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actor starred in 'Black Christmas' and also appeared in a movie that shares a format tag with 'Rocco and His Brothers', which was released in 1960?",
            "answer": "Keir Dullea"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Finding Bliss'?",
                "answer": "Julie Davis"
            },
            {
                "question": "What movie was written by Julie Davis?",
                "answer": "\"I Love You, Don't Touch Me!\""
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie did Mitchell Whitfield star in?",
                "answer": "\"I Love You, Don't Touch Me!\""
            },
            {
                "question": "What other movie did Mitchell Whitfield star in?",
                "answer": "'My Cousin Vinny'"
            },
            {
                "question": "What genre is 'My Cousin Vinny' associated with?",
                "answer": "trial"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Who wrote 'Finding Bliss', and which movies were acted in by the actor who starred in the movie written by that writer?",
            "answer": "Julie Davis wrote 'Finding Bliss'. Mitchell Whitfield starred in 'I Love You, Don't Touch Me!', which was written by Julie Davis, and also in 'My Cousin Vinny'.\n\nAnswer:\n\nThe final complex question based on the given tuples would be: \"Who wrote 'Finding Bliss', and which movies were acted in by the actor who starred in the movie written by that writer?\"\n\nThe answer to this question would be: Julie Davis wrote 'Finding Bliss'. Mitchell Whitfield starred in 'I Love You, Don't Touch Me!', which was written by Julie Davis, and also in 'My Cousin Vinny'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Blood Ties'?",
                "answer": "Jacques Maillot and Guillaume Canet"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie did Guillaume Canet star in?",
                "answer": "Hunting and Gathering"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which actor starred in the movie 'Hunting and Gathering'?",
                "answer": "Fran\u00e7oise Bertin"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actors starred in a movie written by the director of 'Blood Ties'?",
            "answer": "Fran\u00e7oise Bertin, she starred in 'Hunting and Gathering', which was written by Guillaume Canet, who wrote 'Blood Ties'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Who Framed Roger Rabbit'?",
                "answer": "Gary K. Wolf"
            },
            {
                "question": "What genre does the movie 'Who Framed Roger Rabbit' belong to?",
                "answer": "fantasy"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie shares the same genre as 'fantasy'?",
                "answer": "The Imaginarium of Doctor Parnassus"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the genre of the movie 'The Imaginarium of Doctor Parnassus'?",
                "answer": "Fantasy"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie is of the genre 'Fantasy' and is also tagged as 'The Imaginarium of Doctor Parnassus'?",
                "answer": "At the Earth's Core"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was written by Gary K. Wolf and shares the same genre as 'The Imaginarium of Doctor Parnassus' and 'At the Earth's Core'?",
            "answer": "Who Framed Roger Rabbit"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who is the writer of 'Window to Paris'?",
                "answer": "Yuri Mamin"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the IMDb rating of 'Window to Paris'?",
                "answer": "good"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the IMDb rating of 'The Man in the Gray Flannel Suit'?",
                "answer": "good"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the genre of 'The Man in the Gray Flannel Suit'?",
                "answer": "War"
            },
            {
                "question": "What is the genre of 'Force 10 from Navarone'?",
                "answer": "War"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "What is the genre of the movie written by the same person who wrote 'Window to Paris' and has an IMDb rating equal to 'Window to Paris'?",
            "answer": "War (As 'The Man in the Gray Flannel Suit' has the same IMDb rating as 'Window to Paris', and it belongs to the War genre)"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'At Five in the Afternoon'?",
                "answer": "Samira Makhmalbaf"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'The Apple'?",
                "answer": "Mohsen Makhmalbaf"
            },
            {
                "question": "Did Mohsen Makhmalbaf star in 'Close-Up'?",
                "answer": "Yes"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Close-Up'?",
                "answer": "Abbas Kiarostami"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was written by Samira Makhmalbaf and starred Mohsen Makhmalbaf, and who wrote the movie that Samira Makhmalbaf wrote and Mohsen Makhmalbaf starred in?",
            "answer": "The Apple was written by Samira Makhmalbaf and starred Mohsen Makhmalbaf, and 'Close-Up' was written by Abbas Kiarostami."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'Rat Pfink a Boo Boo'?",
                "answer": "Carolyn Brandt"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actress starred in the movie 'Rat Pfink a Boo Boo' and can you provide the name of this movie?",
            "answer": "Carolyn Brandt starred in the movie 'Rat Pfink a Boo Boo'."
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie \"Music Box\"?",
                "answer": "Jessica Lange"
            },
            {
                "question": "In which movie did Jessica Lange star?",
                "answer": "Men Don't Leave"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie \"Men Don't Leave\"?",
                "answer": "Barbara Benedek"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which movie was written by Barbara Benedek?",
                "answer": "Sabrina"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie \"Sabrina\"?",
                "answer": "Ernest Lehman"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which movie was written by Barbara Benedek and also starred Jessica Lange, who also starred in the movie \"Music Box\"?",
            "answer": "Men Don't Leave"
        }
    },
    {
        "simple": [
            {
                "question": "Who starred in the movie 'The Woman on the Beach'?",
                "answer": "Charles Bickford"
            },
            {
                "question": "In which movie did Charles Bickford star?",
                "answer": "Branded"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who wrote the movie 'Branded'?",
                "answer": "Aleksandr Dulerayn"
            }
        ],
        "complex": {
            "question": "Which actor starred in 'The Woman on the Beach' and who wrote the movie 'Branded' that the actor appeared in?",
            "answer": "Charles Bickford starred in 'The Woman on the Beach' and Aleksandr Dulerayn wrote the movie 'Branded' that the actor appeared in."
        }
    }
]